<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/yumetodo/unofficial-windows-message-center-rss</id><title>Windows message center - Recent announcements</title><updated>2024-08-11T00:32:23Z</updated><author><name>direek</name></author><author><name>Microsoft</name></author><link href="https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center" type="text/html" /><link href="https://yumetodo.github.io/unofficial-windows-message-center-rss/feed/atom10.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3367</id><title type="html">60-Day Reminder: Upcoming end of servicing date for some editions of Windows 11, versions 21H2 and 22H2</title><updated>2024-08-08T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;On October 8, 2024, Windows 11, version 21H2 (&lt;a href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-11-enterprise-and-education" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank"&gt;Enterprise&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-11-enterprise-and-education" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Education&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-11-iot-enterprise" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;IoT Enterprise&lt;/a&gt; editions) and Windows 11, version 22H2 (&lt;a href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-11-home-and-pro" data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Home and Pro&lt;/a&gt; editions) will reach end of servicing. The upcoming October 2024 security update, to be released on October 8, 2024, will be the last update available for these editions. After this date, devices running these editions will no longer receive monthly security and preview updates containing protections from the latest security threats.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;To help keep you protected and productive, Windows Update will automatically initiate a feature update for Windows 11 Home and Pro devices that are not managed by IT departments when these are nearing end of servicing. Moving to &lt;a href="https://aka.ms/W11/how-to-get-23H2" data-linktype="external" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 11, version 23H2&lt;/a&gt; keeps your device supported and receiving monthly updates that are critical to security and ecosystem health.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;For detailed information, see the &lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-11-enterprise-and-education"&gt;Windows 11 Enterprise and Education&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-11-iot-enterprise" data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 11 IoT Enterprise&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-11-home-and-pro" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 11 Home and Pro&lt;/a&gt; lifecycle pages. For information about servicing timelines and lifecycle, see &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/windows11-release-information" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Windows 11 release information&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="/en-us/lifecycle/faq/windows" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Lifecycle FAQ - Windows&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/?terms=windows" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank"&gt;Microsoft Lifecycle Policy search tool&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows11-release-information" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3362</id><title type="html">Get started with July 2024 improvements in Windows 11</title><updated>2024-07-31T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you’re an IT professional or decision maker, start using the newest Windows 11 capabilities with helpful tips and actionable steps summarized in one place. Read &lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-11-news-you-can-use-july-2024/ba-p/4204680" target="_blank"&gt;this month’s recap&lt;/a&gt; of improvements in Windows security, device management, Windows Server, productivity and collaboration, lifecycle milestones, and preview opportunities. Get started with Secure Boot protections, checkpoint cumulative updates, security baselines and cross-region disaster recovery for Windows 365, Windows Server preview opportunities, IoT LTSC, and other improvements released in July.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-11-news-you-can-use-july-2024/ba-p/4204680" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3363</id><title type="html">July skilling snacks: Bite-sized learning for IT pros</title><updated>2024-07-31T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Visit our updated learning series on all things Windows. This month, we published the following learning bites:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Our &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-skilling-snacks-bite-sized-learning-for-it-pros/ba-p/3725923" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;growing skilling snack library&lt;/a&gt; now contains 42 learning journeys. Each one of these consists of specially selected articles, videos, and other resources, designed for you to consume in about two hours or less. This professional development opportunity is appropriate for all skill levels and is updated every other week.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-11-news-you-can-use-july-2024/ba-p/4204680" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3359</id><title type="html">Windows resiliency: Best practices and the path forward</title><updated>2024-07-25T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The broad, open nature and scale of the Windows computing ecosystem is part of what makes it a powerful and unmatched choice across the globe. The recent &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://blogs.microsoft.com/blog/2024/07/20/helping-our-customers-through-the-crowdstrike-outage/" data-linktype="external"&gt;CrowdStrike incident&lt;/a&gt; underscores the need for mission-critical resiliency within every organization, and our unique ability to support the change required. This incident shows that Windows must prioritize change and innovation in the area of end-to-end resilience. Our goal is to be your trusted partner as you leverage technology and the end-to-end Microsoft stack to deliver amazing value for your workforce, your customers, and your partners. &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://aka.ms/WindowsResiliency" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Read more&lt;/a&gt; about how we are working in close cooperation to improve resiliency across the Windows ecosystem and explore best practices you can use to support resiliency in your organization.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://aka.ms/WindowsResiliency" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3353</id><title type="html">(Updated) CrowdStrike issue impacting Windows endpoints causing an error message on a blue screen</title><updated>2024-07-25T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Updated on July 25, 2024: &lt;/strong&gt;Microsoft released further guidance on &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://aka.ms/WindowsResiliency"&gt;Windows resiliency: Best practices and the path forward&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;. &lt;/strong&gt;Read more about how we are working in close cooperation to improve resiliency across the Windows ecosystem and explore best practices you can use to support resiliency in your organization.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Updated on July 22, 2024:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Microsoft has released a third mitigation option for the CrowdStrike Falcon agent issue impacting Windows clients and servers. If devices are unable to recover with the two previous options, IT admins can use PXE to remediate. See the revised&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/intune-customer-success/new-recovery-tool-to-help-with-crowdstrike-issue-impacting/ba-p/4196959" data-linktype="external" target="_blank"&gt;New Recovery Tool to help with CrowdStrike issue impacting Windows endpoints&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;for detailed instructions on prerequisites and configurations to use PXE Recovery.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Updated on July 21, 2024: &lt;/strong&gt;As a follow-up to the CrowdStrike Falcon agent issue impacting Windows clients and servers, Microsoft has released an&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;updated&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;recovery tool with&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;two repair options&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;to help IT admins expedite the repair process. Based on customer feedback, this new release includes a new option for recovery using safe boot, the option to generate ISO or USB, a fix for ADK detection when the Windows Driver Kit is installed, and a fix for the USB disk size check. See the revised &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/intune-customer-success/new-recovery-tool-to-help-with-crowdstrike-issue-impacting/ba-p/4196959"&gt;New Recovery Tool to help with CrowdStrike issue impacting Windows endpoints&lt;/a&gt; for detailed instructions on using the &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" href="https://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?linkid=2280386" target="_blank"&gt;signed Microsoft Recovery Tool&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Updated on July 20, 2024:&lt;/strong&gt; Microsoft has released &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://support.microsoft.com/topic/0d7741f7-aca1-4487-8a54-bd431cb49455"&gt;KB5042426&lt;/a&gt;, which contains step-by-step guidance for Windows Servers hosted on-premises that are running the CrowdStrike Falcon agent and encountering a 0x50 or 0x7E error message on a blue screen. We will continue to work with CrowdStrike to provide the most up-to-date information available on this issue.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;A new USB Recovery Tool is available to help IT admins expedite the repair process. The new tool can be found in the &lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?linkid=2280386" target="_blank"&gt;Microsoft Download Center&lt;/a&gt;. Read more about the new recovery tool and usage instructions at &lt;a href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/intune-customer-success/new-recovery-tool-to-help-with-crowdstrike-issue-impacting/ba-p/4196959" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;New Recovery Tool to help with CrowdStrike issue impacting Windows endpoints&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Updated on July 19, 2024:&lt;/strong&gt; A new Knowledge Base article, &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/topic/b1c700e0-7317-4e95-aeee-5d67dd35b92f" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;KB5042421&lt;/a&gt;, with additional step-by-step guidance is now available for Windows 11 and Windows 10 clients. We will continue to work with CrowdStrike to provide up-to-date mitigation information as it becomes available.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Microsoft has identified an issue impacting Windows endpoints that are running the CrowdStrike Falcon agent.&amp;nbsp;These endpoints may encounter an error message on a blue screen and experience a continual restarting state.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We have received reports of successful recovery from some customers attempting multiple restart operations on affected Windows endpoints.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;To mitigate this issue, follow these steps:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;For Windows Virtual Machines running on Azure follow the mitigation steps in &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://azure.status.microsoft/status" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Azure status&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Additional details from CrowdStrike are available here: &lt;a href="https://www.crowdstrike.com/blog/statement-on-windows-sensor-update/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;Statement on Windows Sensor Update - CrowdStrike Blog&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/intune-customer-success/new-recovery-tool-to-help-with-crowdstrike-issue-impacting/ba-p/4196959" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3347</id><title type="html">The July 2024 Windows non-security preview update is now available for Windows 11, versions 23H2 and 22H2</title><updated>2024-07-25T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The July&amp;nbsp;2024 non-security preview update is now available for Windows 11, versions 23H2 and 22H2. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" target="_blank"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article. Information about the contents of this update is available from the release notes, which are accessible from the &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5040527" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt; update history page. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see &lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://aka.ms/Windows/MonthlyUpdates" target="_blank"&gt;Windows monthly updates explained&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on X &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://x.com/windowsupdate"&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11, versions 23H2 and 22H2 update:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;REMINDER&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;The October 2024 security update is the last security release for&amp;nbsp;Enterprise and Education editions of&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/windows11-release-information" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 11, version 21H2&lt;/a&gt; and Home and Pro editions of&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="/en-us/windows/release-health/windows11-release-information" data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 11, version 22H2&lt;/a&gt;. After this date, devices running these editions will no longer receive monthly security and preview updates containing protections from the latest security threats. Supported editions of Windows 11, versions 23H2 and 22H2 will continue to have support through their specific lifecycle dates, which can be found at the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/windows11-release-information" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Windows 11 release information page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5040527" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3357</id><title type="html">The July 2024 Windows non-security preview update is now available for Windows 10, version 22H2</title><updated>2024-07-23T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The July&amp;nbsp;2024 non-security preview update is now available for Windows 10, version 22H2. The non-security preview update for Windows 11, versions 23H2 and 22H2 will be available soon.&amp;nbsp;For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" target="_blank"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article. Information about the contents of this update is available from the release notes, which are accessible from the &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5040525" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;update history page. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://aka.ms/Windows/MonthlyUpdates" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows monthly updates explained&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on X &lt;a data-linktype="external" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://x.com/windowsupdate"&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 10, version 22H2 update:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5040525" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3340</id><title type="html">Introducing Windows 11 checkpoint cumulative updates</title><updated>2024-07-15T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;In late 2024, checkpoint cumulative updates will be introduced for devices running Windows 11, version 24H2 or later and Windows Server 2025. This means that updating your Windows devices will involve smaller update files, resulting in a quicker and more efficient update experience. You will begin to receive checkpoint cumulative updates automatically, with no action required from you. Today, you can preview this experience in &lt;a href="https://aka.ms/wip-dev-7-15" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows Insider’s Preview Build 26120.1252 (Dev Channel)&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Read more in &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/introducing-windows-11-checkpoint-cumulative-updates/ba-p/4182552"&gt;Introducing Windows 11 checkpoint cumulative updates&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/introducing-windows-11-checkpoint-cumulative-updates/ba-p/4182552" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3348</id><title type="html">90-Day Reminder: The second phase of Kerberos PAC signature validation vulnerability mitigation begins October 15, 2024</title><updated>2024-07-15T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Starting October 15, 2024, the &lt;strong&gt;Enforced by Default &lt;/strong&gt;phase of Kerberos&amp;nbsp;PAC signature validation mitigation begins. This second phase will move all Windows domain controllers and clients in the environment to&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Enforced&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;mode, enforcing the secure behavior by default. The&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Enforced by Default&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;settings can be overridden by an Administrator to revert to&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Compatibility&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;mode.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;To help protect your environment and prevent outages, see &lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5037754" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;KB5037754: How to manage PAC Validation changes related to CVE-2024-26248 and CVE-2024-29056&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5037754" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3349</id><title type="html">How to install WMIC Feature on Demand on Windows 11</title><updated>2024-07-12T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you’re an IT pro using Windows Management Instrumentation Command line (WMIC), learn how to install it as a Feature on Demand (FoD). It’s a temporary solution while you migrate to PowerShell or a similar tool as WMIC undergoes deprecation. A new article shows you how to check if you have WMIC as a FoD and how you can install it if you don’t. Remember that later this year, WMIC FoD will be disabled by default on the next version of Windows 11 and Windows Server. Read more at &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/how-to-install-wmic-feature-on-demand-on-windows-11/ba-p/4189530" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;How to install WMIC Feature on Demand on Windows 11&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/how-to-install-wmic-feature-on-demand-on-windows-11/ba-p/4189530" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3323</id><title type="html">(Updated) The July 2024 Windows security update is now available</title><updated>2024-07-09T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;Updated on July 16, 2024&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The July 2024 security update is now available for all supported versions of Windows. We recommend that you install these updates promptly. For more information about the contents of this update, see the release notes, which are easily accessible from the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5040442"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5040427" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;update history pages. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article.&amp;nbsp;To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://aka.ms/Windows/MonthlyUpdates" data-linktype="external" target="_blank"&gt;Windows monthly updates explained&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on X &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://x.com/windowsupdate" data-linktype="external"&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11, versions 23H2 and 22H2 update:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Short on time? Watch our &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AYcyrclL-ZY&amp;amp;list=PLs_2OKVJH7eOAqCwuvUnj9gDpuXmCZ0l9" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 11 release notes video&lt;/a&gt; for this month's tips.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;REMINDER&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;The October 2024 security update is the last security release for&amp;nbsp;Enterprise and Education editions of&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/windows11-release-information" data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 11, version 21H2&lt;/a&gt; and Home and Pro editions of&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/windows11-release-information" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Windows 11, version 22H2&lt;/a&gt;. After this date, devices running these editions will no longer receive monthly security and preview updates containing protections from the latest security threats. Supported editions of Windows 11, versions 23H2 and 22H2 will continue to have support through their specific lifecycle dates, which can be found at the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/windows11-release-information" data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 11 release information page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: This post was updated as we previously shared that a resolution for a Windows Installer issue was available in this update. This resolution will be available in a future update.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5040442" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3341</id><title type="html">90-Day Reminder: Upcoming end of servicing date for some editions of Windows 11, versions 21H2 and 22H2</title><updated>2024-07-08T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;On October 8, 2024, Windows 11, version 21H2 (&lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-11-enterprise-and-education"&gt;Enterprise&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-11-enterprise-and-education"&gt;Education&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-11-iot-enterprise"&gt;IoT Enterprise&lt;/a&gt; editions) and Windows 11, version 22H2 (&lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-11-home-and-pro"&gt;Home and Pro&lt;/a&gt; editions) will reach end of servicing. The upcoming October 2024 security update, to be released on October 8, 2024, will be the last update available for these editions. After this date, devices running these editions will no longer receive monthly security and preview updates containing protections from the latest security threats.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;To help keep you protected and productive, Windows Update will automatically initiate a feature update for Windows 11 business devices not managed by IT departments when these are nearing end of servicing. Moving to &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://aka.ms/W11/how-to-get-23H2" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 11, version 23H2&lt;/a&gt; keeps your device supported and receiving monthly updates that are critical to security and ecosystem health.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;For detailed information, see the &lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-11-enterprise-and-education" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 11 Enterprise and Education&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-11-iot-enterprise"&gt;Windows 11 IoT Enterprise&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-11-home-and-pro" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 11 Home and Pro&lt;/a&gt; lifecycle pages. For information about servicing timelines and lifecycle, see &lt;a href="/en-us/windows/release-health/windows11-release-information" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 11 release information&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="/en-us/lifecycle/faq/windows" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Lifecycle FAQ - Windows&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/?terms=windows" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Microsoft Lifecycle Policy search tool&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows11-release-information" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3332</id><title type="html">WSUS driver synchronization is on its way out</title><updated>2024-06-28T17:30:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If your organization uses driver synchronization updates via Windows Server Update Services (WSUS), get ready for change. WSUS is planning to deprecate its driver synchronization feature on April 18, 2025. This lifecycle update is due to the availability of today’s cloud-based driver services.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Drivers will continue to be made available on the Microsoft Update catalog, but you will no longer be able to import them into WSUS. If you wish to continue operating your network on-premises, you will need to use an alternative means to import drivers and distribute them across your devices. We recommend &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/windows-hardware/manufacture/desktop/device-drivers-and-deployment-overview?view=windows-11" data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank"&gt;Device Driver Packages&lt;/a&gt; for this purpose.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Read the full announcement at &lt;a data-linktype="external" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/deprecation-of-wsus-driver-synchronization/ba-p/4177831"&gt;Deprecation of WSUS driver synchronization&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/deprecation-of-wsus-driver-synchronization/ba-p/4177831" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3343</id><title type="html">Get started with June 2024 improvements in Windows 11</title><updated>2024-06-28T17:30:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you’re an IT professional or decision maker, start using the newest Windows 11 capabilities with helpful tips and actionable steps summarized in one place. Read &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-news-you-can-use-june-2024/ba-p/4177793" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;this month’s recap&lt;/a&gt; of improvements in Windows security, device management, Windows Server, and productivity and collaboration. And since you’ve asked, we’ve included sections on lifecycle milestones and preview opportunities. You can now improve your management and security strategy with innovations across Microsoft Intune, Windows Hello, Windows Autopatch, Windows Server, Copilot+ PCs, Windows Settings, and more.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-news-you-can-use-june-2024/ba-p/4177793" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3342</id><title type="html">Introducing Config Refresh for mobile device management </title><updated>2024-06-27T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;A new Windows 11 feature is available to help you manage your company’s policies using mobile device management (MDM). Starting with the May 2024 non-security update, you can now use Config Refresh to configure policy refresh timing to be as short as 30 minutes or as long as 24 hours. This helps improve security and compliance as you monitor that settings don’t drift from your intent. Learn how you can use the Microsoft Intune Settings Catalog to manage Config Refresh and troubleshoot it in the Event Viewer. Find more details in &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/intro-to-config-refresh-a-refreshingly-new-mdm-feature/ba-p/4176921"&gt;Intro to Config Refresh – a refreshingly new MDM feature&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/intro-to-config-refresh-a-refreshingly-new-mdm-feature/ba-p/4176921" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3339</id><title type="html">June skilling snacks: Bite-sized learning for IT pros</title><updated>2024-06-26T20:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Visit our updated learning series on all things Windows. This month, we published the following learning bites:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Our &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-skilling-snacks-bite-sized-learning-for-it-pros/ba-p/3725923" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;growing skilling snack library&lt;/a&gt; now contains 40 learning journeys. Each one of these consists of specially selected articles, videos, and other resources, designed for you to consume in about two hours or less. This professional development opportunity is appropriate for all skill levels and is updated every other week.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-skilling-snacks-bite-sized-learning-for-it-pros/ba-p/3725923" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3324</id><title type="html">The June 2024 Windows non-security preview update is now available</title><updated>2024-06-25T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The June 2024 non-security preview update is now available for Windows 11, versions 23H2 and 22H2 and Windows 10, version 22H2. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article. Information about the contents of this update is available from the release notes, which are accessible from the &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5039302" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt; and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5039299" data-linktype="external" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;update history pages. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see &lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://aka.ms/Windows/MonthlyUpdates" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows monthly updates explained&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on X &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://x.com/windowsupdate"&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11, versions 23H2 and 22H2 update:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5039302" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3337</id><title type="html">We welcome your feedback on the Windows release health website</title><updated>2024-06-24T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Please take a moment to participate in this quick survey to help us improve the design and utility of the Windows release health site. &lt;a href="/en-us/windows/release-health/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Windows release health&lt;/a&gt; offers official information on Windows announcements, releases and servicing milestones, known issues and safeguards, and helpful resources. This anonymous survey will help us focus on what matters most to you. Get started here: &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://aka.ms/WRHsurvey2024" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows release health website feedback&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://aka.ms/WRHsurvey2024" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3331</id><title type="html">Out-of-band updates to address Azure Synapse SQL issue caused by Windows updates </title><updated>2024-06-20T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Microsoft has identified an issue wherein Azure Synapse SQL Serverless Pool databases enter a "Recovery pending" state, and has expedited a resolution. This issue is observed after installing the June 2024 Windows security update on Windows Server 2022 (&lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5039227" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;KB5039227&lt;/a&gt;), Windows Server, version 23H2 (&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5039236" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;KB5039236&lt;/a&gt;), and Azure Stack HCI versions 23H2 and 22H2 (&lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5039227"&gt;KB5039227&lt;/a&gt;). An out-of-band (OOB) update has been released for Windows Server 2022 and Azure Stack HCI, version 22H2 today, June 20, 2024, to address this issue. The resolution for the other platforms affected by this issue will be available in future Windows updates.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The OOB updates for Windows Server 2022 and Azure Stack HCI, version 22H2 are available on the Microsoft Update Catalog only. These are cumulative updates, so you do not need to apply any previous update before installing them, and they supersede all previous updates for affected versions. Installation of this OOB will require a device restart. If you haven’t deployed the June 2024 Windows security update yet, we recommend you apply this OOB update instead. For more information and instructions on how to install this update on your device, consult the below resources for your version of Windows:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5041054" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3330</id><title type="html">How to unlock new experiences on your Copilot+ PC</title><updated>2024-06-18T13:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Today, we’re excited to share more information about our new advanced AI experiences that enable you to do things you can’t on any other PC, helping you be more productive, creative and communicate more effectively. These experiences are only available on new &lt;a href="https://blogs.microsoft.com/blog/2024/05/20/introducing-copilot-pcs/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Copilot+ PCs&lt;/a&gt;, which are generally available beginning today, June 18.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;To learn more, see &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://blogs.windows.com/windowsexperience/?p=178881" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;How to unlock new experiences on your Copilot+ PC&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. For Microsoft Surface news, see &lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" href="https://blogs.windows.com/devices/?p=263496"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Top things to know about Copilot+ PCs from Microsoft Surface, available today&amp;nbsp;at Microsoft.com&lt;/u&gt;.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://blogs.windows.com/windowsexperience/?p=178881" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3320</id><title type="html">Windows Office Hours: June 20th, 2024</title><updated>2024-06-13T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you are an IT admin with questions about managing and updating Windows, we want to help. Every third Thursday of the month, we host a live chat-based event on the Tech Community called Windows Office Hours. Members of the Windows, Intune, Windows Autopilot, Windows Autopatch, and Windows 365 engineering teams will be standing by to answer your questions. We also have experts from FastTrack, the Customer Acceleration Team, and Microsoft public sector teams.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Want to attend the&amp;nbsp;June 20th&amp;nbsp;session of Office Hours? &lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-events/windows-office-hours-june-20-2024/ev-p/4020754" target="_blank"&gt;RSVP on the event page&lt;/a&gt; and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/gxcuf89792/downloadCalendar?message.id=4020754"&gt;click here to add it to your calendar&lt;/a&gt;. There is no video or live meeting component. Simply visit the event page, log in to the Tech Community, and leave your questions in the Comments section. You can also bookmark&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://aka.ms/Windows/OfficeHours" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;https://aka.ms/Windows/OfficeHours&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;for upcoming dates (and the ability to add this event to your calendar). We look forward to helping you.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-events/windows-office-hours-june-20-2024/ev-p/4020754" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3322</id><title type="html">The June 2024 Windows security update is now available</title><updated>2024-06-11T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The June 2024 security update is now available for Windows 11 and all supported versions of Windows 10. We recommend that you install these updates promptly. For more information about the contents of this update, see the release notes, which are easily accessible from the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5039212" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5039211" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;update history pages. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article.&amp;nbsp;To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see &lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://aka.ms/Windows/MonthlyUpdates"&gt;Windows monthly updates explained&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on X &lt;a href="https://x.com/windowsupdate" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" target="_blank"&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11, versions 23H2 and 22H2 update:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Short on time? Watch our &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yXfjZF5Phe4" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 11 release notes video&lt;/a&gt; for this month's tips.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;REMINDER&lt;/strong&gt; The June 2024 security update is the last security release for &lt;a href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-enterprise-and-education" data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Enterprise&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-enterprise-and-education" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Education&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-iot-enterprise" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;IoT Enterprise&lt;/a&gt; editions of &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-enterprise-and-education" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Windows 10, version 21H2&lt;/a&gt;. Windows 10, version 22H2, will be the final version of Windows 10, and all editions will remain in support with monthly security updates through &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank" href="/en-us/lifecycle/announcements/windows-10-22h2-end-of-support-update"&gt;October 14, 2025&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;Enterprise and IoT Enterprise &lt;a href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/?terms=windows 10 ltsc ltsb 21021" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank"&gt;LTSB/LTSC editions&lt;/a&gt; will continue to have support through their specific lifecycle dates, which can be found at the &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/release-information"&gt;Windows 10 release information page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5039212" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3321</id><title type="html">Windows 10, version 21H2 (Editions: Enterprise &amp; Education) has reached end of servicing - June 11, 2024</title><updated>2024-06-11T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;As of June 11, 2024,&amp;nbsp;Enterprise, Education, and IoT Enterprise editions of&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-enterprise-and-education" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 10, version 21H2&lt;/a&gt; have reached end of servicing. The June 2024 security update, released on June 11, 2024, is the last update available for this version. After this date, devices running this version will no longer receive monthly security and preview updates containing protections from the latest security threats.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;To help keep you protected and productive, Windows Update will automatically initiate a feature update for Windows 10 business devices not managed by IT departments when these are at, or within several months of reaching, end of servicing. Moving to Windows 10, version 22H2 keeps your device supported and receiving monthly updates that are critical to security and ecosystem health.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As always, we recommend that you upgrade eligible devices to&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://aka.ms/W11/how-to-get-23H2" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt;. For detailed information, see the &lt;a target="_blank" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-enterprise-and-education" data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 10 Enterprise and Education&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-iot-enterprise" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 10 IoT Enterprise&lt;/a&gt; lifecycle pages. For information about servicing timelines and lifecycle, see&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/release-information" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Windows 10 release information&lt;/a&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/windows11-release-information" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Windows 11 release information&lt;/a&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" href="/en-us/lifecycle/faq/windows" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Lifecycle FAQ - Windows&lt;/a&gt;, and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/?terms=windows" data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Microsoft Lifecycle Policy search tool&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-enterprise-ltsc-2021" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 10 Enterprise LTSC 2021&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-iot-enterprise-ltsc-2021" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Windows 10 IoT Enterprise LTSC 2021&lt;/a&gt; will continue to have mainstream support until January 12, 2027.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-enterprise-and-education" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3325</id><title type="html">Myths and misconceptions: Windows 11 and cloud native</title><updated>2024-06-11T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you’re an IT admin considering moving to Windows 11 and cloud-native management, you can effectively pursue both efforts in parallel. See five misconceptions and practical steps that you can take to help move your organization forward. First, there’s the misconception that to deploy Windows 11, you must also go full cloud native. Secondly, many wrongly think that a name change must mean a bigger change. The third myth is about application compatibility risks. The final two ideas involve business productivity and cost of ownership. Make informed decisions to modernize your environment by reading&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/myths-and-misconceptions-windows-11-and-cloud-native/ba-p/4162011" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Myths and misconceptions: Windows 11 and cloud native&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/myths-and-misconceptions-windows-11-and-cloud-native/ba-p/4162011" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3327</id><title type="html">Update on the Recall Preview Feature for Copilot+ PCs</title><updated>2024-06-07T16:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Today, we are sharing an update on the Recall (preview) feature for &lt;a href="https://blogs.microsoft.com/blog/2024/05/20/introducing-copilot-pcs" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Copilot+ PCs&lt;/a&gt;, including more information on the setup experience for Recall, privacy controls, and additional details on our approach to security.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Recall is a new way to instantly find something you’ve previously seen on your PC. To create an explorable visual timeline and find content on your Copilot+ PC with Recall, Windows periodically takes a snapshot of what appears on your screen. These images are encrypted, stored, and analyzed locally using on-device AI capabilities to understand their context.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are updating the set-up experience of Copilot+ PCs to give you a clearer choice to opt in to save snapshots using Recall. If you don’t proactively choose to turn it on, it will be off by default. Additionally, Windows Hello enrollment is required to enable Recall. To learn more about privacy controls and protections in Copilot+ PCs, read &lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://blogs.windows.com/windowsexperience/?p=178915"&gt;Update on the Recall Preview Feature for Copilot+ PCs&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://blogs.windows.com/windowsexperience/?p=178915" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3319</id><title type="html">Changes coming to the Azure Update Delivery service tag</title><updated>2024-05-31T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you use the Azure Update Delivery service tag to scan for Windows updates at your organization, get ready for change. Azure Firewall service tags are collections of IP addresses and ranges associated with a named resource. The Azure Update Delivery tag is being deprecated starting July 1, 2024. Instead, we recommend using Azure Firewall application rules. Read a &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://aka.ms/AUDServiceTagChanges"&gt;new article&lt;/a&gt; that provides further context and next steps for various scenarios.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://aka.ms/AUDServiceTagChanges" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3318</id><title type="html">Get started with May 2024 improvements in Windows 11</title><updated>2024-05-30T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you’re an IT professional or decision maker, start using the newest Windows 11 capabilities with helpful tips and actionable steps summarized in one place. This May, there are several new ways to help you improve your management and security strategy. Read &lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-news-you-can-use-may-2024/ba-p/4156258" data-linktype="external"&gt;this month’s recap&lt;/a&gt; to get started with improvements in Windows security, device management, Copilot, Windows Server, and productivity and collaboration. There are innovations across many of your familiar tools, including Microsoft Intune, Windows Autopatch, Windows Server, Copilot in Windows, and Windows Settings.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-news-you-can-use-may-2024/ba-p/4156258" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3312</id><title type="html">The May 2024 Windows non-security preview update is now available</title><updated>2024-05-29T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The May 2024 non-security preview update is now available for Windows 11 and all supported versions of Windows 10. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article. Information about the contents of this update is available from the release notes, which are accessible from the &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5037853"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt; and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="external" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5037849"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;update history pages. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://aka.ms/Windows/MonthlyUpdates" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows monthly updates explained&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on X &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://x.com/windowsupdate" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11, versions 22H2 and 23H2 update:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;REMINDER&lt;/strong&gt; The June 2024 security update is the last security release for &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-enterprise-and-education" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Enterprise&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-enterprise-and-education"&gt;Education&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a target="_blank" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-iot-enterprise" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;IoT Enterprise&lt;/a&gt; editions of &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-enterprise-and-education" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 10, version 21H2&lt;/a&gt;. Windows 10, version 22H2, will be the final version of Windows 10, and all editions will remain in support with monthly security updates through &lt;a href="/en-us/lifecycle/announcements/windows-10-22h2-end-of-support-update" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;October 14, 2025&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;Enterprise and IoT Enterprise &lt;a href="/en-us/windows/release-health/release-information" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;LTSB/LTSC editions&lt;/a&gt; will continue to have mainstream support until January 12, 2027.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5037853" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3314</id><title type="html">May skilling snacks: Bite-sized learning for IT pros</title><updated>2024-05-28T22:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Visit our updated learning series on all things Windows. In April and May, we published the following learning bites:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Our growing topics library for personalized learning now contains 38 learning journeys: &lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-skilling-snacks-bite-sized-learning-for-it-pros/ba-p/3725923"&gt;Windows skilling snacks: bite-sized learning for IT pros&lt;/a&gt;. This is where we package available resources on different topics in a way that is easy to consume in under two hours each. This professional development opportunity is appropriate for all skill levels and is updated every other week.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-skilling-snacks-bite-sized-learning-for-it-pros/ba-p/3725923" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3307</id><title type="html">Finding missing devices in Windows Update for Business reports</title><updated>2024-05-24T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you use &lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/windows/deployment/update/wufb-reports-overview" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Windows Update for Business reports&lt;/a&gt;, you may have noticed that devices will occasionally fail to send diagnostic data and end up missing from your reports. A newly released “DeviceDiagnosticDataNotReceived” alert helps you identify missing devices so that they are not overlooked for important troubleshooting. You can use either Log Analytics or Windows Update for Business reports to locate your missing devices. Learn how in &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/missing-devices-in-windows-update-for-business-reports/ba-p/4150561"&gt;Missing devices in Windows Update for Business reports?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/missing-devices-in-windows-update-for-business-reports/ba-p/4150561" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3313</id><title type="html">Out-of-band update to address failure to install the May 2024 Windows security update </title><updated>2024-05-23T23:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Microsoft has identified an issue wherein the &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/status-windows-10-1809-and-windows-server-2019#the-may-2024-security-update-might-fail-to-install" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;May 2024 Windows security update might fail to install&lt;/a&gt; and has expedited a resolution. An Out-of-band (OOB) update has been released for the affected versions of Windows today, May 23, 2024, to address this issue. This issue is observed only in Windows 10 Enterprise and IoT LTSC 2019 editions and Windows Server 2019.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The OOB update released to address this issue is available on all usual release channels. This update is cumulative, so customers do not need to apply any previous update before installing it, as it supersedes all previous updates. This update does not contain any additional security updates from those available in the 5B update. Installation of this OOB will require a device restart. If you haven’t deployed the May 2024 security update yet, we recommend you apply this OOB update instead.&amp;nbsp;For more information and instructions on how to install this update on your device, consult the below resources for your version of Windows:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5039705" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3308</id><title type="html">VBScript deprecation: Timelines and next steps</title><updated>2024-05-22T14:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" href="/en-us/office/vba/outlook/how-to/using-visual-basic-to-customize-outlook-forms/using-visual-basic-scripting-edition" data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;VBScript&lt;/a&gt; is being deprecated. VBScript is a coding language that has been widely used by developers to add dynamic interactivity and functionality to web pages.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Deprecation will happen in three phases, beginning in the second half of 2024, in which VBScript will be available as features on demand (FODs). The following phase is not planned until 2027 or later, allowing websites and apps running on VBScript ample time to migrate. We recommend moving your VBScript-dependent resources to either PowerShell or JavaScript before this time. Learn more in &lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/vbscript-deprecation-timelines-and-next-steps/ba-p/4148301"&gt;VBScript deprecation: Timelines and next steps&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/vbscript-deprecation-timelines-and-next-steps/ba-p/4148301" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3309</id><title type="html">More flexible Windows feature updates</title><updated>2024-05-21T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you’re an IT admin using the &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/windows/deployment/update/deployment-service-overview" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Windows Update for Business deployment service&lt;/a&gt;, you now have greater control over how feature updates are rolled out to your organization. You can now designate Windows feature updates as optional, allowing for more flexible installations, greater risk management, and minimal disruption to workflow. This feature is rolling out between May 21-24, 2024. Learn how to use Microsoft Intune to configure these deployments in &lt;a href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/more-flexible-windows-feature-updates/ba-p/4139230" data-linktype="external" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;More flexible Windows feature updates.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/more-flexible-windows-feature-updates/ba-p/4139230" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3301</id><title type="html">A new era of AI at work begins</title><updated>2024-05-20T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Microsoft is &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://blogs.microsoft.com/?p=52561752" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;revolutionizing the PC for AI era with the Copilot+ PC&lt;/a&gt;. Utilizing powerful new silicon with a neural processing unit (NPU) capable of more than 40 trillion operations per second, Copilot+ PCs can give you time back in your day so you can be more creative, more strategic, and more innovative. They can also unlock productivity with features like Recall, live captions with translation, and Windows Studio Effects. Get to know these new, business-ready devices and the benefits they can provide for organizations of all sizes.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://blogs.windows.com/windowsexperience/?p=178842" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3300</id><title type="html">Watch now: Microsoft Graph brings you programatic access to Windows information</title><updated>2024-05-17T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Learn how to use the Windows updates API, which is part of &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/graph/overview"&gt;Microsoft Graph&lt;/a&gt;, to programmatically access Windows information that is published here on the Windows release health site. The recording of our recent webinar is now available on the &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_PkLkqkcETE" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows IT Pro YouTube channel&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;In response to customer feedback about the need for faster, automated access to information about Windows updates, two new data classes have been released for Windows updates API, allowing access to &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-known-issues-and-product-lifecycle-in-graph-api/ba-p/4105047" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Windows known issues and product lifecycle in Graph API&lt;/a&gt;. In our webinar, we review use cases, helpful resources to get started, and discuss how this feature can work for you and your organization. Watch now on &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_PkLkqkcETE" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;YouTube: Windows known issues and product lifecycle in Graph API&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_PkLkqkcETE" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3293</id><title type="html">The May 2024 Windows security update is now available</title><updated>2024-05-14T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The May 2024 security update is now available for Windows 11 and all supported versions of Windows 10. We recommend that you install these updates promptly. For more information about the contents of this update, see the release notes, which are easily accessible from the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5037771" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5037768" data-linktype="external" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;update history pages. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article.&amp;nbsp;To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see &lt;a href="https://aka.ms/Windows/MonthlyUpdates" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows monthly updates explained&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on X &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://x.com/windowsupdate" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11, versions 23H2 and 22H2 update:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Short on time? Watch our &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BUqi_n86BFQ" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 11 release notes video&lt;/a&gt; for this month's tips.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;REMINDER&lt;/strong&gt; The June 2024 security update is the last security release for &lt;a target="_blank" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-enterprise-and-education" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Enterprise&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-enterprise-and-education" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Education&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-iot-enterprise"&gt;IoT Enterprise&lt;/a&gt; editions of &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-enterprise-and-education"&gt;Windows 10, version 21H2&lt;/a&gt;. Windows 10, version 22H2, will be the final version of Windows 10, and all editions will remain in support with monthly security updates through &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/lifecycle/announcements/windows-10-22h2-end-of-support-update" target="_blank"&gt;October 14, 2025&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;Enterprise and IoT Enterprise &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/release-information" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;LTSB/LTSC editions&lt;/a&gt; of version 21H2 will continue to have mainstream support until January 12, 2027.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5037771" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3295</id><title type="html">30-Day Reminder: Windows 10, version 21H2 end of servicing (Enterprise &amp; Education)</title><updated>2024-05-10T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;On June 11, 2024,&amp;nbsp;Enterprise, Education, and IoT Enterprise editions of&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-enterprise-and-education"&gt;Windows 10, version 21H2&lt;/a&gt; will reach end of servicing. The upcoming June 2024 security update, to be released on June 11, 2024, will be the last update available for this version. After this date, devices running this version will no longer receive monthly security and preview updates containing protections from the latest security threats.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;To help keep you protected and productive, Windows Update will automatically initiate a feature update for Windows 10 business devices not managed by IT departments when these are nearing end of servicing. Moving to Windows 10, version 22H2 keeps your device supported and receiving monthly updates that are critical to security and ecosystem health.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As always, we recommend that you upgrade eligible devices to&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://aka.ms/W11/how-to-get-23H2" data-linktype="external" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt;. For detailed information, see the &lt;a href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-enterprise-and-education" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 10 Enterprise and Education&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-iot-enterprise"&gt;Windows 10 IoT Enterprise&lt;/a&gt; lifecycle pages. For information about servicing timelines and lifecycle, see&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/release-information" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Windows 10 release information&lt;/a&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/windows11-release-information" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 11 release information&lt;/a&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" href="/en-us/lifecycle/faq/windows" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Lifecycle FAQ - Windows&lt;/a&gt;, and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/?terms=windows" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Microsoft Lifecycle Policy search tool&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-enterprise-ltsc-2021" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Windows 10 Enterprise LTSC 2021&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-iot-enterprise-ltsc-2021" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Windows 10 IoT Enterprise LTSC 2021&lt;/a&gt; will continue to have mainstream support until January 12, 2027.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-enterprise-and-education" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3296</id><title type="html">TLS server authentication: Deprecation of weak RSA certificates</title><updated>2024-05-09T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Weak RSA key lengths for certificates will be deprecated on future Windows OS releases later this year. We recommend you use a stronger solution of at least 2048 bits length or an ECDSA certificate, if possible. Support for the RSA algorithm itself won’t be affected. Find details and recommended next steps in &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://aka.ms/DeprecationOfWeakRSACerts"&gt;TLS server authentication: Deprecation of weak RSA certificates&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://aka.ms/DeprecationOfWeakRSACerts" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3294</id><title type="html">Windows Office Hours: May 16th, 2024</title><updated>2024-05-09T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you are an IT admin with questions about managing and updating Windows, we want to help. Every third Thursday of the month, we host a live chat-based event on the Tech Community called Windows Office Hours. Members of the Windows, Intune, Windows Autopilot, Windows Autopatch, and Windows 365 engineering teams will be standing by to answer your questions. We also have experts from FastTrack, the Customer Acceleration Team, and Microsoft public sector teams.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Want to attend the&amp;nbsp;May 16th&amp;nbsp;session of Office Hours? &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-events/windows-office-hours-may-16-2024/ec-p/4020748" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;RSVP on the event page&lt;/a&gt; and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/gxcuf89792/downloadCalendar?message.id=4020748"&gt;click here to add it to your calendar&lt;/a&gt;. There is no video or live meeting component. Simply visit the event page, log in to the Tech Community, and leave your questions in the Comments section. You can also bookmark&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://aka.ms/Windows/OfficeHours" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;https://aka.ms/Windows/OfficeHours&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;for upcoming dates (and the ability to add this event to your calendar). We look forward to helping you.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-events/windows-office-hours-may-16-2024/ec-p/4020748" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3289</id><title type="html">Get started with April 2024 improvements in Windows 11</title><updated>2024-04-30T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you’re an IT professional, find helpful tips on getting started with the newest Windows 11 capabilities that just came out in April. Catch up on the newest in policies and information access, cloud management, and security. This month, you can do more with Microsoft Graph, Microsoft Intune, Government Community Cloud, Windows Server, and Microsoft Copilot for Security. Read &lt;a href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-news-you-can-use-april-2024/ba-p/4126660" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;this month’s recap&lt;/a&gt; and start taking advantage of Windows 11 continuous innovation and delivery today.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-news-you-can-use-april-2024/ba-p/4126660" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3287</id><title type="html">Revoking vulnerable Windows Boot Managers</title><updated>2024-04-24T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Windows is making updates to address a known security vulnerability exploited by BlackLotus to bypass Windows Secure Boot. You now have the option to revoke trust of the Microsoft Windows Production PCA 2011. Get the details in our latest article, &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/revoking-vulnerable-windows-boot-managers/ba-p/4121735" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Revoking vulnerable Windows Boot Managers&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/revoking-vulnerable-windows-boot-managers/ba-p/4121735" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3288</id><title type="html">Reducing Windows 10, version 22H2 monthly LCU package size</title><updated>2024-04-24T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The security and quality update packages that Windows 10 receives every month are becoming smaller and more efficient. This means that systems operating on Windows 10 can enjoy the low demands on network bandwidth previously only available to Windows 11.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Changes are effective as of the April 23, 2024 preview release. Get more information, including steps you can take to make sure you’re ready for these changes, at &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://aka.ms/Win10UpdateSize" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;Reducing Windows 10, version 22H2 Monthly LCU package size&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://aka.ms/Win10UpdateSize" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3285</id><title type="html">The April 2024 Windows non-security preview update is now available</title><updated>2024-04-23T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The April&amp;nbsp;2024 non-security preview update is now available for Windows 11 and all supported versions of Windows 10. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article. Information about the contents of this update is available from the release notes, which are accessible from the &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5036980" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt; and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5036979" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;update history pages. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://aka.ms/Windows/MonthlyUpdates" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows monthly updates explained&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on X &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://x.com/windowsupdate" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11, versions 22H2 and 23H2 update:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;REMINDER&lt;/strong&gt; The June 2024 security update is the last security release for &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-enterprise-and-education"&gt;Enterprise&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-enterprise-and-education" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Education&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-iot-enterprise"&gt;IoT Enterprise&lt;/a&gt; editions of &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-enterprise-and-education"&gt;Windows 10, version 21H2&lt;/a&gt;. Windows 10, version 22H2, will be the final version of Windows 10, and all editions will remain in support with monthly security updates through &lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/lifecycle/announcements/windows-10-22h2-end-of-support-update" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;October 14, 2025&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;Enterprise and IoT Enterprise &lt;a href="/en-us/windows/release-health/release-information" data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;LTSB/LTSC editions&lt;/a&gt; will continue to have mainstream support until January 12, 2027.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5036980" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3284</id><title type="html">Register for the Graph API webinar on April 23</title><updated>2024-04-17T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Learn how you can use Graph API to access information on Windows known issues and product lifecycle. Microsoft has heard your feedback and now gives you faster, programmatic access to Windows update data. Phase one of these changes has already started on April 4, 2024, with further developments planned for the coming months.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;To keep you up to date, we invite you to join us for a &lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-events/windows-known-issues-and-product-lifecycle-in-the-graph-api/ec-p/4105824" data-linktype="external"&gt;Graph API webinar on April 23&lt;/a&gt;. You’ll hear common use scenarios, receive important product announcements, and see live demonstrations of how this new functionality can work for you and your organization. &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://forms.office.com/Pages/ResponsePage.aspx?id=v4j5cvGGr0GRqy180BHbR6Y3c5FtvxlLgwJNBAvsrFZUOFYwSENIMDJBNERHR0xYVVY1VEw1S1kyNS4u" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Register now&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-events/windows-known-issues-and-product-lifecycle-in-the-graph-api/ec-p/4105824" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3282</id><title type="html">New steps have been released to mitigate Kerberos signature validation vulnerabilities</title><updated>2024-04-12T20:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The April 2024 security update released on April 9, 2024 addresses a security vulnerability in the &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/openspecs/windows_protocols/ms-apds/82b7b7c6-413d-4d66-b6b7-4a9224549782"&gt;Kerberos PAC Validation Protocol&lt;/a&gt;. New &lt;strong&gt;Take Action&lt;/strong&gt; steps have been released as part of &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5037754" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;KB5037754&lt;/a&gt; to prevent bypassing PAC signature validation security checks added in&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5020805" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;KB5020805: How to manage Kerberos protocol changes related to CVE-2022-37967&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;To help protect your environment and prevent outages, see &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5037754" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;KB5037754: How to manage PAC Validation changes related to CVE-2024-26248 and CVE-2024-29056&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5037754" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3262</id><title type="html">Windows Office Hours: April 18th, 2024</title><updated>2024-04-11T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you are an IT admin with questions about managing and updating Windows, we want to help. Every third Thursday of the month, we host a live chat-based event on the Tech Community called Windows Office Hours. Members of the Windows, Intune, Windows Autopilot, Windows Autopatch, and Windows 365 engineering teams will be standing by to answer your questions. We also have experts from FastTrack, the Customer Acceleration Team, and Microsoft public sector teams.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Want to attend the&amp;nbsp;April 18th&amp;nbsp;session of Office Hours?&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/gxcuf89792/downloadCalendar?message.id=4020746" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Click here to add it to your calendar&lt;/a&gt;. There is no video or live meeting component. Simply visit the event page, log in to the Tech Community, and leave your questions in the Comments section. You can also bookmark&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://aka.ms/Windows/OfficeHours"&gt;https://aka.ms/Windows/OfficeHours&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;for upcoming dates (and the ability to add this event to your calendar). We look forward to helping you.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-events/windows-office-hours-april-18-2024/ec-p/4020746" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3276</id><title type="html">The April 2024 security update is now available</title><updated>2024-04-09T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The April 2024 security update is now available for Windows 11 and all supported versions of Windows 10. We recommend that you install these updates promptly. For more information about the contents of this update, see the release notes, which are easily accessible from the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5036893"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5036892" data-linktype="external" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;update history pages. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article.&amp;nbsp;To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://aka.ms/Windows/MonthlyUpdates"&gt;Windows monthly updates explained&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on X &lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://x.com/windowsupdate" data-linktype="external"&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11, versions 23H2 and 22H2 update:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Short on time? Watch our &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=e_uh1pc5Vtc" data-linktype="external" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 11 release notes video&lt;/a&gt; for this month's tips.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;REMINDER&lt;/strong&gt; The June 2024 security update is the last security release for &lt;a target="_blank" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-enterprise-and-education" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Enterprise&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-enterprise-and-education" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Education&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-iot-enterprise" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;IoT Enterprise&lt;/a&gt; editions of &lt;a href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-enterprise-and-education" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 10, version 21H2&lt;/a&gt;. Windows 10, version 22H2, will be the final version of Windows 10, and all editions will remain in support with monthly security updates through &lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="/en-us/lifecycle/announcements/windows-10-22h2-end-of-support-update"&gt;October 14, 2025&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;Enterprise and IoT Enterprise &lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/release-information" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;LTSB/LTSC editions&lt;/a&gt; of version 21H2 will continue to have mainstream support until January 12, 2027.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5036893" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3277</id><title type="html">Windows known issues and product lifecycle in Graph API</title><updated>2024-04-04T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The Windows updates API in Microsoft Graph now offers faster and more comprehensive data access for building applications and reports. As part of the first phase of this release, you can now access data on Windows known issues and product lifecycle in one place. Before this, you’d have to search for this data via the Microsoft Lifecycle Policy site, known issues, and the Windows release information pages. Further updates are planned for later this year. Learn more and see a few examples in &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-known-issues-and-product-lifecycle-in-graph-api/ba-p/4105047"&gt;Windows known issues and product lifecycle in Graph API&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-known-issues-and-product-lifecycle-in-graph-api/ba-p/4105047" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3267</id><title type="html">When to use Windows 10 Extended Security Updates</title><updated>2024-04-02T16:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Learn how to prepare for Windows 10 End of Support and take advantage of a new offer for those using cloud-based management. If you need temporary help to make the transition to Windows 11, you can enroll in the Windows 10 Extended Security Updates (ESU) program. You have three options to do so: the traditional 5-by-5 activation, through Windows 365, or using a cloud management solution. A new article announces a ~25% discount in the latter case. Read complete information at &lt;a href="https://aka.ms/Windows/CloudBasedUpdates" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;When to use Windows 10 Extended Security Updates&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://aka.ms/Windows/CloudBasedUpdates" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3275</id><title type="html">Time zone updates for Kazakhstan, Samoa, and Palestinian Authority</title><updated>2024-04-01T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Three time zone changes have been put into effect as part of the March 2024 non-security preview update and the April 2024 security update. Samoa has abolished the use of DST. Kazakhstan has switched to a single time zone throughout the entire country. The Palestinian Authority has delayed the beginning of DST for 2024 and 2025. Microsoft recommends temporary workarounds for users affected by these changes. Read individual articles on the &lt;a href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/daylight-saving-time-time-zone/bg-p/DSTBlog" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Daylight Saving Time &amp;amp; Time Zone Blog&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/daylight-saving-time-time-zone/bg-p/DSTBlog" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3251</id><title type="html">Configuring "Weather and more" on Windows lock screen</title><updated>2024-03-29T23:30:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;In the coming weeks, we’re enhancing the lock screen experience on Windows devices, starting with dynamic, interactive weather updates. Organizations with devices running Windows 11, version 23H2 and Windows 10, version 22H2 that have installed the April 2024 monthly security update or later updates will be included in a phased rollout of this new experience. Home devices with the March 2024 preview optional update are also part of this rollout. As the rollout progresses, there will be an option to see more dynamic updates related to finance, sports, traffic, and more.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Windows Home users can &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/personalize-your-lock-screen-81dab9b0-35cf-887c-84a0-6de8ef72bea0" data-linktype="external"&gt;personalize their own lock screen experience&lt;/a&gt; on their devices through Settings on the Start menu. IT administrators can manage this experience for their organization’s devices through Mobile Devie Management (MDM) and Group Policies. For more information, see &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/configuring-weather-and-more-on-the-lock-screen-in-windows/ba-p/4101024"&gt;Configuring weather and more on the lock screen in Windows&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/configuring-weather-and-more-on-the-lock-screen-in-windows/ba-p/4101024" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3273</id><title type="html">March skilling snacks: Bite-sized learning for IT pros</title><updated>2024-03-29T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Visit our updated learning series on all things Windows. This month, we’ve published the following learning bites:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Our growing topics library for personalized learning now contains 35 learning journeys: &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-skilling-snacks-bite-sized-learning-for-it-pros/ba-p/3725923"&gt;Windows skilling snacks: bite-sized learning for IT pros&lt;/a&gt;. This is where we package available resources on different topics in a way that is easy to consume in under two hours each. This professional development opportunity is appropriate for all skill levels and is updated every other week.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-skilling-snacks-bite-sized-learning-for-it-pros/ba-p/3725923" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3263</id><title type="html">Reminder: Windows 11, version 22H2 (Home &amp; Pro Editions) will receive non-security preview updates until June 26, 2024</title><updated>2024-03-27T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Home, Pro, Pro Education, and Pro for Workstations editions of Windows 11, version 22H2 will receive non-security preview updates until June 26, 2024. Previously, we communicated that the last optional non-security preview update for version 22H2 would be released on February 27, 2024. Based on user feedback, this date has been changed so more customers can take advantage of our&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/delivering-continuous-innovation-in-windows-11-b0aa0a27-ea9a-4365-9224-cb155e517f12"&gt;continuous innovation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;quickly.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;These devices will continue to receive cumulative monthly security updates until the end of servicing for Windows 11, version 22H2 in accordance with the Windows lifecycle policies. There are no changes to the end of servicing dates for Windows 11, version 22H2.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As always, we recommend that you update&amp;nbsp;your&amp;nbsp;devices to the latest version of&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="external" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://aka.ms/W11/how-to-get-23H2"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;For information about servicing timelines and lifecycle, see&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/windows11-release-information" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 11 release information&lt;/a&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="/en-us/lifecycle/faq/windows"&gt;Lifecycle FAQ - Windows&lt;/a&gt;, and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/?terms=windows"&gt;Microsoft Lifecycle Policy search tool&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://yumetodo.github.io/unofficial-windows-message-center-rss/feed/atom10.xml" rel="self" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3269</id><title type="html">The March 2024 Windows non-security preview update is now available</title><updated>2024-03-26T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The March 2024 non-security preview update is now available for Windows 11 and all supported versions of Windows 10. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article. Information about the contents of this update is available from the release notes, which are accessible from the &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5035942"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt; and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5035941" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;update history pages. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" href="https://aka.ms/Windows/MonthlyUpdates" target="_blank"&gt;Windows monthly updates explained&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on X &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://x.com/windowsupdate" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11, versions 22H2 and 23H2 update:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;REMINDER&lt;/strong&gt; The June 2024 security update is the last security release for &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-enterprise-and-education"&gt;Enterprise&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-enterprise-and-education" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Education&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a target="_blank" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-iot-enterprise" data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;IoT Enterprise&lt;/a&gt; editions of &lt;a href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-enterprise-and-education" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Windows 10, version 21H2&lt;/a&gt;. Windows 10, version 22H2, will be the final version of Windows 10, and all editions will remain in support with monthly security updates through &lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank" href="/en-us/lifecycle/announcements/windows-10-22h2-end-of-support-update" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;October 14, 2025&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;Enterprise and IoT Enterprise &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/release-information"&gt;LTSB/LTSC editions&lt;/a&gt; will continue to have mainstream support until January 12, 2027.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5035942" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3268</id><title type="html">Expedite non-security updates in Windows 11</title><updated>2024-03-26T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you use Microsoft Intune or Microsoft Graph, you can now expedite non-security updates in Windows 11. Previously, you’ve been able to expedite security updates. Now, you can improve the stability, performance, and functionality of devices by addressing quality issues before the next security update. Check the prerequisites and read about how it works in a new article: &lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/expedite-non-security-updates-in-windows-11/ba-p/4093249"&gt;Expedite non-security updates in Windows 11&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/expedite-non-security-updates-in-windows-11/ba-p/4093249" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3143</id><title type="html">Out-of-band updates to address a Windows Server domain controller issue</title><updated>2024-03-22T22:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;Updated March 25, 2024&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Microsoft has identified an &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/status-windows-server-2022#3271msgdesc"&gt;issue that affects Windows Server domain controllers (DCs)&lt;/a&gt;, and has expedited a resolution that can be applied to affected devices. Out-of-band (OOB) updates have been released for some versions of Windows today, March 22, 2024, to addresses this issue related to a memory leak in the Local Security Authority Subsystem Service (LSASS). This occurs when on-premises and cloud-based Active Directory domain controllers service Kerberos authentication requests.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;This issue is not expected to impact Home users, as it is only observed in some versions of Windows Server. Domain controllers are not commonly used in personal and home devices.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Updates are available on the &lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://www.catalog.update.microsoft.com/home.aspx" data-linktype="external"&gt;Microsoft Update Catalog&lt;/a&gt; only. These are cumulative updates, so you do not need to apply any previous update before installing them, and they supersede all previous updates for affected versions. If your organization uses the affected server platforms as DCs and you haven’t deployed the March 2024 security updated yet, we recommend you apply this OOB update instead.&amp;nbsp;For more information and instructions on how to install this update on your device, consult the below resources for your version of Windows:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As of March 25, 2024, all affected versions have been addressed via the updates above.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/status-windows-server-2022#3271msgdesc" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3270</id><title type="html">Microsoft Copilot in Windows starts to roll out to more Windows 11 and 10 devices</title><updated>2024-03-21T22:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Starting today, Copilot in Windows (in preview)* begins to roll out to more Windows 11 and Windows 10 devices. In addition, starting this week, you can access up to 10 Copilot requests before signing in with a &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://support.microsoft.com/account-billing/what-s-the-difference-between-a-microsoft-account-and-a-work-or-school-account-72f10e1e-cab8-4950-a8da-7c45339575b0" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Microsoft account or Microsoft Entra ID&lt;/a&gt;. After reaching this limit, signing in is necessary to continue using Copilot. We recommend signing in with a Microsoft account or Entra ID to access the full capabilities of Copilot.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;This new wave of &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/welcome-to-copilot-in-windows-675708af-8c16-4675-afeb-85a5a476ccb0" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Copilot in Windows&lt;/a&gt; availability and sign-in options will start to reach devices running supported editions of Windows 11 today. IT admins should note that Copilot is enabled by default in Windows 11, version 23H2, and disabled by default in Windows 11, version 22H2. If your organization has configured policy settings to manage Copilot in Windows, those policies will be respected during this rollout.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Eligible devices running Home and Pro editions of Windows 10, version 22H2, and that are not managed by an organization, will start to receive Copilot in Windows later this month. This continues the rollout of &lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/topic/how-to-get-copilot-in-windows-in-preview-on-windows-10-570514d1-add9-4bc4-9add-c75ea4496949" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Copilot in Windows 10&lt;/a&gt; that began in November of 2023. This current rollout phase will reach most of its targeted Windows 11 and 10 devices by the end of May.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;When your device receives Copilot in Windows, you will see the Copilot (preview) icon&amp;nbsp;in the system tray on the taskbar after a reboot. To show or hide this icon on your taskbar, go to &lt;strong&gt;Settings&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;gt; &lt;strong&gt;Personalization&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;gt; &lt;strong&gt;Taskbar&lt;/strong&gt;. You can also right-click the taskbar and select &lt;strong&gt;Taskbar&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;settings&lt;/strong&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;To learn more, see &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/welcome-to-copilot-in-windows-675708af-8c16-4675-afeb-85a5a476ccb0"&gt;Welcome to Copilot in Windows&lt;/a&gt;. If you are an IT administrator and want to learn how to configure and manage policy settings for this experience, check out &lt;a href="/en-us/windows/client-management/manage-windows-copilot" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Manage Copilot in Windows&lt;/a&gt;. Copilot in Windows is currently in preview; see the &lt;a href="/en-us/windows/privacy/copilot-supplemental-terms" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;terms of use&lt;/a&gt; for additional information.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;* Copilot in Windows (in preview) is available in select global markets and will be rolled out to additional markets over time. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://www.microsoft.com/windows/copilot-ai-features/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Learn more&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://yumetodo.github.io/unofficial-windows-message-center-rss/feed/atom10.xml" rel="self" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3256</id><title type="html">Windows Office Hours: March 21st, 2024</title><updated>2024-03-14T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you are an IT admin with questions about managing and updating Windows, we want to help. Every third Thursday of the month, we host a live chat-based event on the Tech Community called Windows Office Hours. Members of the Windows, Intune, Windows Autopilot, Windows Autopatch, and Windows 365 engineering teams will be standing by to answer your questions. We also have experts from FastTrack, the Customer Acceleration Team, and Microsoft public sector teams.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Want to attend the&amp;nbsp;March 21st&amp;nbsp;session of Office Hours?&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/gxcuf89792/downloadCalendar?message.id=4020741" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;Click here to add it to your calendar&lt;/a&gt;. There is no video or live meeting component. Simply visit the event page, log in to the Tech Community, and leave your questions in the Comments section. You can also bookmark&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://aka.ms/Windows/OfficeHours" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;https://aka.ms/Windows/OfficeHours&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;for upcoming dates (and the ability to add this event to your calendar). We look forward to helping you.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-events/windows-office-hours-march-21-2024/ev-p/4020741" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3250</id><title type="html">90-Day Reminder:  Windows 10, version 21H2 end of servicing (Enterprise &amp; Education)</title><updated>2024-03-13T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;On June 11, 2024,&amp;nbsp;Enterprise, Education, and IoT Enterprise editions of&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-enterprise-and-education" data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 10, version 21H2&lt;/a&gt; will reach end of servicing. The upcoming June 2024 security update, to be released on June 11, 2024, will be the last update available for this version. After this date, devices running this version will no longer receive monthly security and preview updates containing protections from the latest security threats.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;To help keep you protected and productive, Windows Update will automatically initiate a feature update for Windows 10 business devices not managed by IT departments when these are nearing end of servicing. Moving to Windows 10, version 22H2 keeps your device supported and receiving monthly updates that are critical to security and ecosystem health.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As always, we recommend that you upgrade eligible devices to&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://aka.ms/W11/how-to-get-23H2" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt;. For detailed information, see the &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-enterprise-and-education"&gt;Windows 10 Enterprise and Education&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-iot-enterprise" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Windows 10 IoT Enterprise&lt;/a&gt; lifecycle pages. For information about servicing timelines and lifecycle, see&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/release-information"&gt;Windows 10 release information&lt;/a&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="/en-us/windows/release-health/windows11-release-information" data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 11 release information&lt;/a&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/lifecycle/faq/windows"&gt;Lifecycle FAQ - Windows&lt;/a&gt;, and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/?terms=windows"&gt;Microsoft Lifecycle Policy search tool&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-enterprise-and-education" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3258</id><title type="html">Take action: March 2024 security update is now available</title><updated>2024-03-12T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The March 2024 security update is now available for Windows 11 and all supported versions of Windows 10. We recommend that you install these updates promptly. For more information about the contents of this update, see the release notes, which are easily accessible from the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5035853" data-linktype="external" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5035845" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;update history pages. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://aka.ms/Windows/MonthlyUpdates"&gt;Windows monthly updates explained&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on X &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://x.com/windowsupdate" data-linktype="external"&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11, versions 23H2 and 22H2 update:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Short on time? Watch our &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://youtu.be/ea5eMCTzNOI" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 11 release notes video&lt;/a&gt; for this month's tips.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;REMINDER&lt;/strong&gt; The June 2024 security update is the last security release for &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-enterprise-and-education" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Enterprise&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a target="_blank" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-enterprise-and-education" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Education&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-iot-enterprise" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank"&gt;IoT Enterprise&lt;/a&gt; editions of &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-10-enterprise-and-education"&gt;Windows 10, version 21H2&lt;/a&gt;. Windows 10, version 22H2, will be the final version of Windows 10, and all editions will remain in support with monthly security updates through &lt;a target="_blank" href="/en-us/lifecycle/announcements/windows-10-22h2-end-of-support-update" data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;October 14, 2025&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;Enterprise and IoT Enterprise &lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/release-information" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;LTSB/LTSC editions&lt;/a&gt; will continue to have mainstream support until January 12, 2027.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5035853" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3254</id><title type="html">New innovations in Windows 11 make it easier to create and get things done</title><updated>2024-02-29T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Explore the new experiences that are beginning to roll out&amp;nbsp;to Windows 11 devices today. Simplify tasks with new plug-ins and skills for Copilot in Windows. Work and create with greater ease thanks to enhancements for Photos, Clipchamp, Windows Ink, Snap, Widgets, and accessibility. For more details and instructions on how to take advantage of all the new and improved features, read &lt;a data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://blogs.windows.com/windowsexperience/?p=178717" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;today’s announcement in the Windows Blog.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://blogs.windows.com/windowsexperience/?p=178717" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3249</id><title type="html">The February 2024 Windows non-security preview update is now available</title><updated>2024-02-29T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The February&amp;nbsp;2024 non-security preview update is now available for Windows 11 and all supported versions of Windows 10. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article. Information about the contents of this update is available from the release notes, which are accessible from the &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5034848" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt; and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5034843" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;update history pages. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see &lt;a href="https://aka.ms/Windows/MonthlyUpdates" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows monthly updates explained&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on X &lt;a href="https://x.com/windowsupdate" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" target="_blank"&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11, versions 22H2 and 23H2 update:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IMPORTANT &lt;/strong&gt;New dates have been announced for the end of non-security preview updates for Windows 11, version 22H2. June 24, 2025, will be the date of the last preview updates for all Enterprise editions of Windows 11, version 22H2. June 26, 2024 will be date of the last preview updates for Home and all Pro editions of Windows 11, version 22H2.&amp;nbsp;After these dates, only cumulative monthly security updates will continue for this version of Windows. We previously communicated that the last preview update for 22H2 would be released on February 2024, and this extension allows more customers to experience the &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/delivering-continuous-innovation-in-windows-11-b0aa0a27-ea9a-4365-9224-cb155e517f12" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;continuous innovation in Windows 11&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5034848" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3238</id><title type="html">(Updated) Expanding invitations to move to Windows 11 to more people</title><updated>2024-02-28T20:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;Updated April 3, 2024&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;If your organization relies on Microsoft to manage Windows updates, you’ll start seeing a new user interface on eligible Windows 10 devices in the coming months. A new message will appear after signing in and usually following a reboot. It will invite users to “Upgrade for free to the latest Windows 11” on business devices with the following characteristics:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note&lt;/strong&gt;: These invitations were originally programmed to start with the April 2024 security update, but this initiative was postponed. We will share a new timeline in the coming months.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;For more details, read &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/expanding-invitations-to-move-to-windows-11-to-more-people/ba-p/4069463"&gt;Expanding invitations to move to Windows 11 to more people&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/expanding-invitations-to-move-to-windows-11-to-more-people/ba-p/4069463" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3255</id><title type="html">Non-security preview updates will continue to be released for Windows 11, version 22H2</title><updated>2024-02-28T00:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you use or manage Windows 11, version 22H2 devices, your opportunity to receive non-security preview updates has been extended. These updates bring optional fixes and productivity improvements that you can get every fourth week of the month&amp;nbsp;as a preview of what will be available in the next month’s security update .&amp;nbsp;Previously, we communicated that the last optional non-security preview update for version 22H2 would be released on February 27, 2024. Based on user feedback, this date has been changed so more customers can take advantage of our&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/delivering-continuous-innovation-in-windows-11-b0aa0a27-ea9a-4365-9224-cb155e517f12" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;continuous innovation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;quickly.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The new end date is June 24, 2025 for Windows 11, version 22H2&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Enterprise, Education, IoT Enterprise, and Enterprise multi-session editions. Home, Pro, Pro Education, and Pro for Workstations editions of version 22H2 will receive non-security preview updates until&amp;nbsp;June 26, 2024.&amp;nbsp;This extension will allow IT administrators to test improvements and fixes ahead of the upcoming security update on more devices.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;These devices will continue to receive security updates (known as “B” releases) until the end of servicing for version 22H2 in accordance with the Windows lifecycle policies. There are no changes on the end of servicing dates for Windows 11, version 22H2. For more information on end of servicing dates for all Windows 11 versions and editions, see&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="/en-us/windows/release-health/windows11-release-information" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 11 - release information.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://yumetodo.github.io/unofficial-windows-message-center-rss/feed/atom10.xml" rel="self" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3248</id><title type="html">February skilling snacks: Bite-sized learning for IT pros</title><updated>2024-02-22T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Visit our updated learning series on all things Windows. Between January and February, we’ve published the following learning bites with a special focus on security:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Our growing topics library for personalized learning now contains 33 learning journeys: &lt;a href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-skilling-snacks-bite-sized-learning-for-it-pros/ba-p/3725923" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows skilling snacks: bite-sized learning for IT pros&lt;/a&gt;. This is where we package available resources on different topics in a way that is easy to consume in under two hours each. This professional development opportunity is appropriate for all skill levels and is updated every other week.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-skilling-snacks-bite-sized-learning-for-it-pros/ba-p/3725923" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3244</id><title type="html">Subscribe to the Windows Community YouTube channel</title><updated>2024-02-14T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Looking for short how-to videos to help you get the most out of Windows 11? Need an easy way to see what's new in the latest Windows 11 security update? Subscribe to the &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCTveKU9IdMSTGf7eK6660eg" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Windows community on YouTube&lt;/a&gt;! In addition to short, &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLs_2OKVJH7eOAqCwuvUnj9gDpuXmCZ0l9"&gt;video summaries of our monthly updates&lt;/a&gt;, you’ll find &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLs_2OKVJH7eMAck1Xwp48Au7_Tv0VkvyM"&gt;quick tips&lt;/a&gt; that will make the things you do every day easier. When it’s time to update to a new version of Windows, find a step-by-step video explaining &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=T60vd9m8fUA&amp;amp;list=PLs_2OKVJH7eN6aN6vgWtg5l6imEv46dXS&amp;amp;pp=gAQBiAQB" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;how to get the latest update&lt;/a&gt;. Subscribe, turn on notifications, and explore the &lt;a data-linktype="external" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCTveKU9IdMSTGf7eK6660eg/"&gt;Windows community&lt;/a&gt; today.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCTveKU9IdMSTGf7eK6660eg" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3242</id><title type="html">Take action: February 2024 security update is now available</title><updated>2024-02-13T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The February 2024 security update is now available for Windows 11 and all supported versions of Windows 10. We recommend that you install these updates promptly. For more information about the contents of this update, see the release notes, which are easily accessible from the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5034765" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5034763" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;update history pages. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" data-linktype="external" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see &lt;a href="https://aka.ms/Windows/MonthlyUpdates" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows monthly updates explained&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on X &lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://x.com/windowsupdate" target="_blank"&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11, versions 23H2 and 22H2 update:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Short on time? Watch our &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://youtu.be/cXHIXqPTApA" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 11 release notes video&lt;/a&gt; for this month's tips.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IMPORTANT &lt;/strong&gt;After February 2024, there are no more optional, non-security preview releases for Windows 11, version 22H2. Only cumulative monthly security updates (known as the "B" or Update Tuesday release) will continue for this version. Windows 11, version 23H2 and Windows 10, version 22H2 will continue to receive security and optional releases.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5034765" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3246</id><title type="html">Interim DST guidance for Kazakhstan, Samoa, and Palestinian Authority</title><updated>2024-02-12T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Three Daylight Saving Time (DST) changes will be released as part of the March 2024 non-security preview update and the April 2024 security update. Samoa has abolished DST. Kazakhstan has switched to a single time zone. The Palestinian Authority has announced a delay in DST dates for 2024 and 2025. Microsoft recommends temporary workarounds for users affected by these changes. Read individual articles on the &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/daylight-saving-time-time-zone/bg-p/DSTBlog" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Daylight Saving Time &amp;amp; Time Zone Blog&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/daylight-saving-time-time-zone/bg-p/DSTBlog" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3243</id><title type="html">Reminder: Changes coming to Windows Boot Manager revocations for Secure Boot, April 9, 2024</title><updated>2024-02-09T19:30:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Administrators should observe mitigations and security enforcement requirements coming into effect with Windows updates released on and after &lt;strong&gt;April 9, 2024&lt;/strong&gt;. Devices running Windows updates released July 11, 2023 or later include security measures designed to protect vulnerable boot managers against a Secure Boot bypass vulnerability disclosed in &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2023-24932" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;CVE-2023-24932&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="/en-us/windows/security/operating-system-security/system-security/trusted-boot"&gt;Secure Boot&lt;/a&gt; is a Windows security feature designed to protect devices from bootkit malware.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;In addition to the changes coming with Windows updates to be released April 9, 2024, additional changes are coming with Windows updates to be released &lt;strong&gt;October 8, 2024&lt;/strong&gt;. These further changes enforce Code Integrity Boot policy and Secure Boot disallow list revocations related to this hardening. There will be no option to disable enforcement after this update.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;To enable protections manually, it's necessary to ensure all devices and bootable media are updated and ready for this security hardening change.&amp;nbsp;Users should determine whether it's important to enable protections now, or wait for a future update from Microsoft. To better assess this, in addition to understanding the options available for configuring these security requirements, see &lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5025885" data-linktype="external"&gt;KB5025885: How to manage the Windows Boot Manager revocations for Secure Boot changes associated with CVE-2023-24932&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5025885" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3245</id><title type="html">Copilot in Windows: enhanced design rolling out this week</title><updated>2024-02-09T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;We’re bringing great enhancements to Copilot in Windows (in preview)&amp;nbsp;this week. The pane launches in an expanded window size to give you even more space to chat. You can also resize it to adjust to your needs. You can easily switch back to a thinner side-by-side window, so that Copilot in Windows works alongside all of your other windows.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;If you want a more immersive experience, continue your conversation on &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://copilot.microsoft.com/" data-linktype="external" target="_blank"&gt;copilot.microsoft.com&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;by using the &lt;strong&gt;Open in Microsoft Edge&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;button at the top of Copilot.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;When you launch Copilot in Windows, you will see a more streamlined look and feel designed to help you bring your ideas to life. We’ve introduced a cleaner, sleeker experience for answers and a fun new carousel of suggested prompts that showcase the power of Copilot in Windows. Please note that some styling might only be available for users with a Microsoft account.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;These updates are rolling out over time, so &lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/topic/microsoft-edge-update-settings-af8aaca2-1b69-4870-94fe-18822dbb7ef1" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" target="_blank"&gt;check Edge&amp;nbsp;for the latest update&lt;/a&gt; if you’re eager to see what’s new in Copilot in Windows. To learn more about this feature, see &lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/welcome-to-copilot-in-windows-675708af-8c16-4675-afeb-85a5a476ccb0" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;Welcome to Copilot in Windows.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Copilot in Windows (in preview) is available in select global markets and will be rolled out to additional markets over time.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://www.microsoft.com/windows/copilot-ai-features#faq"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Learn more.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;Copilot in Windows 10 functionality is limited and has specific&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://www.microsoft.com/windows/windows-10-specifications" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;system requirements&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/welcome-to-copilot-in-windows-675708af-8c16-4675-afeb-85a5a476ccb0" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3241</id><title type="html">Windows Office Hours: February 15th, 2024</title><updated>2024-02-08T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you are an IT admin with questions about managing and updating Windows, we want to help. Every third Thursday of the month, we host a live chat-based event on the Tech Community called Windows Office Hours. Members of the Windows, Intune, Windows Autopilot, Windows Autopatch, and Windows 365 engineering teams will be standing by to answer your questions. We also have experts from FastTrack, the Customer Acceleration Team, and Microsoft public sector teams.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Want to attend the&amp;nbsp;February 15th&amp;nbsp;session of Office Hours?&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/gxcuf89792/downloadCalendar?message.id=4020731" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Click here to add it to your calendar&lt;/a&gt;. There is no video or live meeting component. Simply visit the event page, log in to the Tech Community, and leave your questions in the Comments section. You can also bookmark&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://aka.ms/Windows/OfficeHours"&gt;https://aka.ms/Windows/OfficeHours&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;for upcoming dates (and the ability to add this event to your calendar). We look forward to helping you.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-events/windows-office-hours-february-15-2024/ec-p/4020731" rel="alternate" /></entry></feed>