<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/yumetodo/unofficial-windows-message-center-rss</id><title>Windows message center - Recent announcements</title><updated>2023-12-25T00:29:46Z</updated><author><name>direek</name></author><author><name>Microsoft</name></author><link href="https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center" type="text/html" /><link href="https://yumetodo.github.io/unofficial-windows-message-center-rss/feed/atom10.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3226</id><title type="html">Upgrade your Windows servicing skills to wrap up 2023</title><updated>2023-12-19T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Review and bookmark our learning resources called Windows skilling snacks. We’ve updated our library of personalized learning and put together a cheat sheet of all the Windows servicing topics we covered in 2023. Each topic packages available resources in a way that is easy to consume in under two hours. This professional development opportunity is appropriate for all skill levels.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-servicing/wrap-up-2023-by-upgrading-your-windows-servicing-skills/m-p/4012479" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3225</id><title type="html">Upcoming changes to Windows Single Sign-On</title><updated>2023-12-14T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Prepare for changes if you use Windows 10 or Windows 11 devices in the European Economic Area (EEA). In January 2024, users will start seeing a new SSO notice allowing them to choose how to sign in to apps. The notice will be fully rolled out by March 2024 to both consumers and IT users. This solution helps comply with the Digital Markets Act (DMA). Find details about what you and your users can expect at &lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/upcoming-changes-to-windows-single-sign-on/ba-p/4008151"&gt;Upcoming changes to Windows Single Sign-On&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/upcoming-changes-to-windows-single-sign-on/ba-p/4008151" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3222</id><title type="html">Windows Office Hours: December 21st, 2023</title><updated>2023-12-14T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you are an IT admin with questions about managing and updating Windows, we want to help. Every third Thursday of the month, we host a live chat-based event on the Tech Community called Windows Office Hours. Members of the Windows, Intune, Windows Autopilot, Windows Autopatch, and Windows 365 engineering teams will be standing by to answer your questions. We also have experts from FastTrack, the Customer Acceleration Team, and Microsoft public sector teams.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Want to attend the&amp;nbsp;December 21st&amp;nbsp;session of Office Hours?&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/gxcuf89792/downloadCalendar?message.id=3871726" target="_blank"&gt;Click here to add it to your calendar&lt;/a&gt;. There is no video or live meeting component. Simply visit the event page, log in to the Tech Community, and leave your questions in the Comments section. You can also bookmark&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://aka.ms/Windows/OfficeHours" data-linktype="external"&gt;https://aka.ms/Windows/OfficeHours&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;for upcoming dates (and the ability to add this event to your calendar). We look forward to helping you.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-events/windows-office-hours-december-21-2023/ev-p/3871726" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3223</id><title type="html">Take action: December 2023 security update is now available</title><updated>2023-12-12T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The December 2023 security update release is now available for Windows 11 and all supported versions of Windows 10. We recommend that you install these updates promptly. For more information about the contents of this update, see the release notes, which are easily accessible from the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5033375"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5033372" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;update history pages. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see &lt;a data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://aka.ms/Windows/MonthlyUpdates" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows monthly updates explained&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on X &lt;a href="https://x.com/windowsupdate" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11, versions 23H2 and 22H2 update:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Short on time? Watch our short &lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://youtu.be/tDkpxod-24w"&gt;Windows 11 update&lt;/a&gt; release notes video for this month's tips.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IMPORTANT &lt;/strong&gt;After February 2024, there are no more optional, non-security preview releases for Windows 11, version 22H2. Only cumulative monthly security updates (known as the "B" or Update Tuesday release) will continue for this version. Windows 11, version 23H2 and Windows 10, version 22H2 will continue to receive security and optional releases.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IMPORTANT&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Because of reduced operations during the Western holidays and the upcoming new year, there won’t be a non-security preview release for the month of December 2023. Non-security preview releases will resume in January 2024.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5033375" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3224</id><title type="html">Windows update management at Microsoft Technical Takeoff</title><updated>2023-12-07T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Find demos and see what’s new and coming in Windows update management from Microsoft Technical Takeoff for Windows and Intune. Here are a couple of sessions to get you started:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Also, get answers to common questions and insightful tips to support your move to Windows 11. Check out the full link list at &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-servicing/catch-up-on-the-latest-in-windows-update-management-at-microsoft/m-p/3994957" data-linktype="external" target="_blank"&gt;Catch up on the latest in Windows update management at Microsoft Technical&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-servicing/catch-up-on-the-latest-in-windows-update-management-at-microsoft/m-p/3994957" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3220</id><title type="html">Plan for Windows 10 EOS with Windows 11, Windows 365, and ESU</title><updated>2023-12-05T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Windows 10 is nearing end of support (EOS) on October 14, 2025. At that time, Microsoft will no longer provide bug fixes for issues, security fixes for vulnerabilities, time zone updates, or technical support for problems that might occur. If you’re a home user, learn more at &lt;a href="/en-us/lifecycle/faq/windows" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank"&gt;Lifecycle FAQ&lt;/a&gt; for Windows. If you’re an IT admin, start modernizing your infrastructure now. You can upgrade eligible PCs to Windows 11, purchase new Windows 11 Pro PCs, or make Windows 11 available in the cloud through a Windows 365 subscription. Read about all your options, including the Extended Security Update (ESU) program for Windows 10 in &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://aka.ms/PrepareForWindows10EOS" data-linktype="external" target="_blank"&gt;Plan for Windows 10 EOS with Windows 11, Windows 365, and ESU&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://aka.ms/PrepareForWindows10EOS" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3216</id><title type="html">The November 2023 Windows non-security preview update is now available for Windows 11, versions 22H2 and 23H2</title><updated>2023-12-04T22:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The November 2023 non-security preview update is now available&amp;nbsp;for Windows 11, versions 22H2 and 23H2. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" data-linktype="external" target="_blank"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article. Information about the contents of this update is available from the release notes, which are accessible from the &lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5032288"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt; update history page. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see &lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://aka.ms/Windows/MonthlyUpdates" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows monthly updates explained&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on X &lt;a href="https://x.com/windowsupdate" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11, versions 22H2 and 23H2 update:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IMPORTANT&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;After&amp;nbsp;​February 2024, there are no more optional, non-security preview releases for Windows 11, version 22H2. Only cumulative monthly security updates (known as the "B" or Update Tuesday release) will continue for this version. Windows 11, version 23H2 and Windows 10, version 22H2 will continue to receive security and optional releases.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IMPORTANT&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Because of reduced operations during the Western holidays and the upcoming&amp;nbsp;new year, there won’t be a non-security preview release&amp;nbsp;for the month of December 2023. There will be a monthly security release for December 2023. Normal monthly servicing for both security and non-security preview releases will resume in January 2024.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5032288" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3219</id><title type="html">Survey: WSUS driver synchronization deprecation</title><updated>2023-12-04T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you manage driver updates with Windows Server Update Services (WSUS), please help us understand your needs around an upcoming change. We plan to end the synchronization of driver updates via WSUS by December 2024. With cloud-based and manual solutions available today, we want to help ensure a smooth transition for your organization. Please share your thoughts on current usage, the implications of this change for your IT infrastructure, and your transition needs. Take the &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://forms.office.com/r/Y44DW8XRpW"&gt;WSUS Driver Sync Deprecation&lt;/a&gt; survey.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://forms.office.com/r/Y44DW8XRpW" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3215</id><title type="html">November skilling snacks: Bite-sized learning for IT pros</title><updated>2023-12-01T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Visit our updated learning series on all things Windows. This month, we’ve published the following learning bites:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Bookmark our growing topics library for personalized learning and check back every other week: &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-skilling-snacks-bite-sized-learning-for-it-pros/ba-p/3725923" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Windows skilling snacks: bite-sized learning for IT pros&lt;/a&gt;. This is where we package available resources on different topics in a way that is easy to consume in under two hours each. This professional development opportunity is appropriate for all skill levels.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-skilling-snacks-bite-sized-learning-for-it-pros/ba-p/3725923" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3181</id><title type="html">Copilot is available for eligible Windows 10 devices</title><updated>2023-11-30T22:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Today we start to roll out Copilot in Windows (in preview) to eligible, non-managed Windows 10 devices running the Home or Pro editions of Windows 10, version 22H2. Devices on version 22H2 of Windows 10 Enterprise or Education, or Pro devices managed by organizations, will be included in a later rollout phase.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;If you are interested in experiencing Copilot in Windows as soon as possible, you can do so by going to &lt;strong&gt;Settings&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;gt; &lt;strong&gt;Update &amp;amp; Security&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;gt; &lt;strong&gt;Windows Update.&lt;/strong&gt; Turn on "&lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?linkid=2249590" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Get the latest updates as soon as they’re available&lt;/a&gt;" and &lt;strong&gt;Check for updates&lt;/strong&gt;. Note that the device may need to reboot to enable new features. If you are an IT administrator, read &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/copilot-coming-to-windows-10/ba-p/3984070" target="_blank"&gt;Copilot coming to Windows 10&lt;/a&gt; to learn more.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note 1: Copilot in Windows is currently available in preview in select global markets. It is our intention to add additional markets over time.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note 2: Devices require &amp;gt; 4GB RAM and Display adapter that supports +720p resolution. If we detect that devices may have an issue, such as an application incompatibility, we may put a safeguard hold in place and not offer Copilot in Windows until that issue is resolved.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5033809" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3214</id><title type="html">The November 2023 Windows non-security preview update is now available for Windows 10, version 22H2</title><updated>2023-11-30T22:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The November 2023 non-security preview update is now available for Windows 10, version 22H2. The preview update for Windows 11, versions 22H2 and 23H2 will be available in the near term. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article. Information about the contents of this update is available from the release notes, which are accessible from the &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5032278" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt; update history page. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see &lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://aka.ms/Windows/MonthlyUpdates" target="_blank"&gt;Windows monthly updates explained&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on X &lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://x.com/windowsupdate" data-linktype="external"&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 10, version 22H2 update:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IMPORTANT&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Because of reduced operations during the Western holidays and the upcoming&amp;nbsp;new year, there won’t be a non-security preview release&amp;nbsp;for the month of December 2023. There will be a monthly security release for December 2023. Normal monthly servicing for both security and non-security preview releases will resume in January 2024.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5032278" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3213</id><title type="html">Planning for Copilot in Windows 10</title><updated>2023-11-20T22:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Today we start to roll out Copilot in Windows (in preview) to eligible Windows 10 devices. Copilot in Windows is available for Windows Insiders in the Release Preview Channel for Windows 10, version 22H2. The experience will be rolled out more broadly in the coming weeks to eligible non-managed devices running the Home and Pro editions of Windows 10, version 22H2.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Devices on version 22H2 of Windows 10 Enterprise or Education, or Pro devices managed by organizations, will be included in a later rollout phase. If you are an IT administrator, read today’s post on &lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/copilot-coming-to-windows-10/ba-p/3984070"&gt;Copilot coming to Windows 10&lt;/a&gt; and see why your organization should try Copilot in Windows. Also check this article to learn &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/topic/how-we-are-maximizing-value-in-windows-10-7dca25fa-be2f-492d-b99c-bf3342be7037" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;How we are maximizing value in Windows 10.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: Copilot in Windows is currently available in preview in select global markets. It is our intention to add additional markets over time.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://blogs.windows.com/windows-insider/2023/11/20/releasing-windows-10-build-19045-3757-to-release-preview-channel/" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3211</id><title type="html">Copilot coming to Windows 10</title><updated>2023-11-16T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Today we announced that Copilot in Windows (in preview) is coming to Windows 10. We are revisiting our approach to Windows 10 and will be making additional investments to make sure everyone can get the &lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5033467" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;maximum value from their Windows PC&lt;/a&gt; including Copilot in Windows.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Copilot in Windows will be available soon for Windows Insiders in the Release Preview Channel for eligible devices running Windows 10, version 22H2. The experience will be rolled out more broadly to non-managed devices running the Home and Pro editions of Windows 10, version 22H2 in the coming weeks. To learn more, see &lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://blogs.windows.com/windows-insider/?p=176682" target="_blank"&gt;Releasing Windows 10 Build 19045.3754 to Release Preview Channel&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;If you are an IT administrator, consult our documentation on how to &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/windows/client-management/manage-windows-copilot"&gt;manage Copilot in Windows&lt;/a&gt; to learn how to manage the Copilot experience for the devices in your organization.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: Copilot in Windows is currently available in preview in select global markets. It is our intention to add additional markets over time.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://blogs.windows.com/windows-insider/?p=176682" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3210</id><title type="html">Enable optional updates for Windows 10 devices</title><updated>2023-11-16T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;A new policy will be available to IT pros managing Windows 10 devices with Windows Update for Business. With the upcoming November 2023 optional update, you will be able to automatically deploy optional Windows updates or enable users in your organization to get them just like on Windows 11. Configure this policy as a Group Policy Object (GPO) or as a Configuration Service Provider (CSP) policy and choose the types of optional updates that suit your organizational goals. Find out more at &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/enable-optional-updates-for-windows-10-devices/ba-p/3983927" data-linktype="external"&gt;Enable optional updates for Windows 10 devices&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/enable-optional-updates-for-windows-10-devices/ba-p/3983927" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3192</id><title type="html">Reflecting on 20 years of Windows Patch Tuesday </title><updated>2023-11-15T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Learn about interesting facts and milestones of the 20-year history of Windows Patch Tuesday. The historical context adds special importance to the recently announced Microsoft’s Secure Future Initiative. This new article focuses on the forward-looking present of Windows servicing through four basic principles: predictability, simplicity, agility, and transparency. Some of these efforts are embodied in new hotpatching technologies, artificial intelligence, and cross-team partnerships. Get a quick idea of the past, present, and future of Windows updates, quick detection of issues, rapid mitigations, clear and prescriptive communications, and continued learning and improvements. Find out more at &lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://blogs.windows.com/windowsexperience/?p=178558"&gt;Reflecting on 20 years of Windows Patch Tuesday&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://blogs.windows.com/windowsexperience/?p=178558" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3204</id><title type="html">Take action: November 2023 security update is now available</title><updated>2023-11-14T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The November 2023 security update release is now available for Windows 11 and all supported versions of Windows 10. We recommend that you install these updates promptly. For more information about the contents of this update, see the release notes, which are easily accessible from the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5032190" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5032189" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;update history pages. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see &lt;a href="https://aka.ms/Windows/MonthlyUpdates" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows monthly updates explained&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on X (formerly Twitter) &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://x.com/windowsupdate" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;&lt;u&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11, versions 23H2 and 22H2 update:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Short on time? Watch our short &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://youtu.be/IyMReJq-BQM"&gt;Windows 11 update&lt;/a&gt; release notes video for this month's tips.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5032190" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3209</id><title type="html">Tailor Windows Update for Business reports with Power BI</title><updated>2023-11-13T22:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you’re an IT pro using Windows Update for Business reports, check out comprehensive guidance on how to customize them. Power BI simplifies your device monitoring and management with an array of visualizations, filtering, drilling down, and data slicing options. Learn from a few practical scenarios and start building unique reports that meet your organizational needs. See how it works in &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/tailor-windows-update-for-business-reports-with-power-bi/ba-p/3978975" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Tailor Windows Update for Business reports with Power BI&lt;/a&gt;. Then replicate the steps with a starter template and guide in &lt;a href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-servicing/build-custom-windows-update-for-business-reports-using-power-bi/m-p/3980535#M1843" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Build custom Windows Update for Business reports using Power BI&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/tailor-windows-update-for-business-reports-with-power-bi/ba-p/3978975" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3208</id><title type="html">Windows Office Hours: November 16th, 2023</title><updated>2023-11-13T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you are an IT admin with questions about managing and updating Windows, we want to help. Every third Thursday of the month, we host a live chat-based event on the Tech Community called Windows Office Hours. Members of the Windows, Intune, Windows Autopilot, Windows Autopatch, and Windows 365 engineering teams will be standing by to answer your questions. We also have experts from FastTrack, the Customer Acceleration Team, and Microsoft public sector teams.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Want to attend the&amp;nbsp;November 16th&amp;nbsp;session of Office Hours?&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/gxcuf89792/downloadCalendar?message.id=3871722" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Click here to add it to your calendar&lt;/a&gt;. There is no video or live meeting component. Simply visit the event page, log in to the Tech Community, and leave your questions in the Comments section. You can also bookmark&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://aka.ms/Windows/OfficeHours" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;https://aka.ms/Windows/OfficeHours&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;for upcoming dates (and the ability to add this event to your calendar). We look forward to helping you.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-events/windows-office-hours-november-16-2023/ev-p/3871722" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3207</id><title type="html">Your guide to Windows at Microsoft Ignite 2023</title><updated>2023-11-10T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Learn about the latest AI innovations directly from experts and sharpen your skills through live breakouts and interactive workshops around Windows at Microsoft Ignite. The event is online and in-person next week, November 14-17, 2023. A number of sessions focus on Windows 11, Windows 365, Microsoft Copilot, Azure Virtual Desktop, Microsoft Intune, Microsoft 365 admin center, among others. Browse and bookmark &lt;a href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/your-guide-to-windows-at-microsoft-ignite-2023/ba-p/3974552" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Your guide to Windows at Microsoft Ignite 2023&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/your-guide-to-windows-at-microsoft-ignite-2023/ba-p/3974552" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3206</id><title type="html">Windows Server 2012/R2: Extended Security Updates</title><updated>2023-11-09T22:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;You can now get three additional years of Extended Security Updates (ESUs) if you need more time to upgrade and modernize your Windows Server 2012, Windows Server R2, or Windows Embedded Server 2012 R2 on Azure. This also applies to Azure Stack HCI, Azure Stach Hub, and other Azure products. A new article provides details and step-by-step instructions to extending limited protection for up to three consecutive 12-month increments. Read it at &lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-server-2012-r2-extended-security-updates/ba-p/3976610" target="_blank"&gt;Windows Server 2012/R2: Extended Security Updates&lt;/a&gt;. ESU online and proxy activation scenarios are covered in &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/extended-security-updates-esus-online-or-proxy-activation/ba-p/3976649"&gt;Extended Security Updates (ESUs): Online or proxy activation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-server-2012-r2-extended-security-updates/ba-p/3976610" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3205</id><title type="html">Simplify your Windows 11 upgrade experience with Intune</title><updated>2023-11-08T22:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;A new capability is available for users of the Windows Update for Business deployment service. IT pros no longer need to worry about creating and maintaining eligibility groups for devices not ready for Windows 11. Now, you can use Microsoft Intune or the Microsoft Graph API to deploy Windows 11 upgrades with assurance that any ineligible devices would be automatically updated to the latest available version of Windows 10. For guidance on how to do this, read &lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/simplify-your-windows-11-upgrade-experience-with-intune/ba-p/3974500" target="_blank"&gt;Simplify your Windows 11 upgrade experience with Intune&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/simplify-your-windows-11-upgrade-experience-with-intune/ba-p/3974500" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3203</id><title type="html">Windows 11 2023 Update available</title><updated>2023-10-31T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Today, we are announcing the availability of the &lt;a href="https://aka.ms/W11/how-to-get-23H2" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 11 2023 Update&lt;/a&gt; (also known as Windows 11, version 23H2). We are providing a limited scope of new features and functionality including the ones announced in September as part of continuous innovation. This update brings enhancements to the Start menu, taskbar, and chat experience, which is now &lt;a href="https://www.microsoft.com/microsoft-teams/teams-for-home" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Microsoft Teams (free)&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;If you have an eligible device and are interested in experiencing these new enhancements when they are available, open the Windows Update settings page, turn on “Get the latest updates as soon as they’re available,” and select &lt;strong&gt;Check for updates&lt;/strong&gt;. This update will be delivered using servicing technology (like that used for monthly updates) so if you are already running Windows 11, version 22H2, installation will be fast and easy. For more information on ways to get the update, watch this &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://aka.ms/video/W11/how-to-get-23H2" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;video&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Note: If we detect that your device may have an issue, such as application incompatibility, we may put a safeguard hold in place and not offer the update until that issue is resolved.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;If you are an IT administrator, see &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://aka.ms/new-in-23H2" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;What's new for IT pros in Windows 11, version 23H2&lt;/a&gt; for information on commercial release channels, deployment tools, and enhancements for commercial organizations.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://aka.ms/Windows11/2023Update" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3201</id><title type="html">October skilling snacks: Bite-sized learning for IT pros</title><updated>2023-10-30T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Visit our updated learning series on all things Windows. Every two weeks, we package available resources on a different topic in a way that is easy to consume in under two hours each. This professional development opportunity is appropriate for all skill levels, from entry-level to senior and seasoned. Take advantage of the following learning bites published in the month of October:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Our growing topics library now contains 27 learning journeys! Bookmark it for personalized learning and check back every other week: &lt;a href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-skilling-snacks-bite-sized-learning-for-it-pros/ba-p/3725923" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows skilling snacks: bite-sized learning for IT pros&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-skilling-snacks-bite-sized-learning-for-it-pros/ba-p/3725923" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3190</id><title type="html">Syria 2022 time zone update now available</title><updated>2023-10-27T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;On October 5, 2022, the Syrian government made an official announcement about a Daylight Saving Time (DST) time zone change. Since then, the official time has not advanced by an hour and has permanently shifted to the UTC+3 time zone. Microsoft is releasing updates to support this change. The October 2023 non-security preview release includes the update for Windows 11 and Windows 10, version 22H2. All other supported versions of Windows will receive this time adjustment in the November 14, 2023 monthly quality release. Read &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/daylight-saving-time-time-zone/syria-2022-time-zone-update-now-available/ba-p/3966066" target="_blank"&gt;Syria 2022 time zone update now available&lt;/a&gt; for more details.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/daylight-saving-time-time-zone/syria-2022-time-zone-update-now-available/ba-p/3966066" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3191</id><title type="html">The October 2023 Windows non-security preview update is now available</title><updated>2023-10-26T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The October 2023 non-security preview update is now available. These optional non-security previews are released only for Windows 10, version 22H2 and Windows 11, version 22H2. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" data-linktype="external" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article. Information about the contents of this update is available from the release notes, which are accessible from the &lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5031455" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt; and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5031445" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt; update history pages. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://aka.ms/Windows/MonthlyUpdates"&gt;Windows monthly updates explained&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on X (formerly Twitter) &lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://x.com/windowsupdate" data-linktype="external"&gt;&lt;u&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11, version 22H2 update:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5031455" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3189</id><title type="html">What’s new in Test Base for Microsoft 365: September 2023</title><updated>2023-10-16T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Test Base for Microsoft 365 is a service that allows you to test your applications against Windows feature and quality updates in a Microsoft-managed environment. Starting September 26, 2023, you can test your applications on Windows 11, version 23H2 and you can do so using Custom Image. Join the Test Base Community and express your interest in the private preview of two new features: Test Base Chat and testing apps for Windows on Arm. Get further details from &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/what-s-new-in-test-base-for-microsoft-365-september-2023/ba-p/3937583" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;What’s new in Test Base for Microsoft 365: September 2023&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/what-s-new-in-test-base-for-microsoft-365-september-2023/ba-p/3937583" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3188</id><title type="html">Day 1 with Windows 11: a quick tour</title><updated>2023-10-13T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;A new blog article is here to help IT pros prepare users for Windows 11. It includes a video walkthrough of the user experience on the first day of using Windows 11. This quick tour covers the basics of navigation, collaboration, multitasking, and the overall experience in comparison with Windows 10. Besides the visual tutorial, the recommendations of the Windows 11 onboarding kit and Windows 11 tips videos complement anyone’s Windows 11 adoption toolbox.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/day-1-with-windows-11-a-quick-tour/ba-p/3939968" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3185</id><title type="html">Windows Office Hours: October 19th, 2023</title><updated>2023-10-12T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you are an IT admin with questions about managing and updating Windows, we want to help. Every third Thursday of the month, we host a live chat-based event on the Tech Community called Windows Office Hours. Members of the Windows, Intune, Windows Autopilot, Windows Autopatch, and Windows 365 engineering teams stand by to answer your questions. We also have experts from FastTrack, the Customer Acceleration Team, and Microsoft public sector teams.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Want to attend the&amp;nbsp;October 19th&amp;nbsp;session of Office Hours?&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/gxcuf89792/downloadCalendar?message.id=3871718" data-linktype="external"&gt;Click here to add it to your calendar&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and log in to the Tech Community to post your questions early! You can also bookmark&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://aka.ms/Windows/OfficeHours"&gt;https://aka.ms/Windows/OfficeHours&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;for upcoming dates (and the ability to add this event to your calendar). We look forward to helping you.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-events/windows-office-hours-october-19-2023/ev-p/3871718" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2885</id><title type="html">Windows Autopatch availability within Microsoft Intune admin center</title><updated>2023-10-12T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you use Microsoft Managed Desktop, Windows Autopatch is now available as an additional option in Microsoft Intune admin center. Windows Autopatch is a service that automates Windows, Microsoft 365 Apps for enterprise, Microsoft Edge, and Microsoft Teams updates, while offering security and productivity solutions.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Beginning October 5, 2023, devices not currently under management by Windows Autopatch can be enrolled using Microsoft Managed Desktop (is this an application?). As always, Windows Autopatch is included under Window 10 and Windows 11 Enterprise E3 licensing agreements, or higher. To learn more about this new enrollment process, see &lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/managed-desktop/operate/maintain-environment#microsoft-managed-desktop-tenant-actions" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Maintain the Microsoft Managed Desktop environment&lt;/a&gt;. To learn about Windows Autopatch, see &lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/windows/deployment/windows-autopatch/overview/windows-autopatch-overview"&gt;Windows Autopatch overview&lt;/a&gt; and visit the &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://aka.ms/community/windowsautopatch" data-linktype="external" target="_blank"&gt;Windows Autopatch Tech Community&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/managed-desktop/operate/maintain-environment#microsoft-managed-desktop-tenant-actions" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3184</id><title type="html">New security capabilities of Event Tracing for Windows</title><updated>2023-10-11T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Whether you’re in cybersecurity, IT, performance, or software development, improved resources can help you diagnose cybersecurity threats. While you could previously use Event Tracing for Windows for limited audit functions, nine events have recently been improved for better insight. Specifically, several security-related events now show Process ID and Process Start Key in the event schema, allowing you to confirm the causal process of these events. We've also increased the event version as events are updated over time, following the application compatibility policy. Read &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/new-security-capabilities-of-event-tracing-for-windows/ba-p/3949941" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;New security capabilities of Event Tracing for Windows&lt;/a&gt; for step-by-step instructions, screenshots, and examples of these improvements.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/new-security-capabilities-of-event-tracing-for-windows/ba-p/3949941" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3187</id><title type="html">Windows Server 2012 R2 has reached end of support</title><updated>2023-10-10T23:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Windows Server 2012 R2&amp;nbsp;has reached end of support today, October 10, 2023. The&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5031419" data-linktype="external" target="_blank"&gt;October 2023 security update&lt;/a&gt; is the last update available for this version. After this date, devices running this version of Windows Server will no longer receive monthly security and preview updates containing protections from the latest security threats.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We recommend that you update&amp;nbsp;your&amp;nbsp;devices to &lt;a href="/en-us/windows-server/get-started/whats-new-in-windows-server-2022" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Windows Server 2022&lt;/a&gt;. Learn about upgrading at &lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/windows-server/get-started/upgrade-overview"&gt;Overview of Windows Server upgrades&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Extended Security Updates (ESUs) are available for purchase and will continue for three years, renewable on an annual basis. The final date of this extension is October 13, 2026. For more information, see &lt;a data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5031043" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;KB5031043: Procedure to continue receiving security updates after extended support has ended on October 10, 2023&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Learn more about end of support for Windows Server at &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-server-news-and-best/windows-server-end-of-support-key-dates/ba-p/3074148" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Windows Server End of Support: Key Dates&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-server-2012-r2" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3183</id><title type="html">Take action: October 2023 security update is now available</title><updated>2023-10-10T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The October&amp;nbsp;2023 security update release is now available for Windows 11 and all supported versions of Windows 10. We recommend that you install these updates promptly. For more information about the contents of this update, see the release notes, which are easily accessible from the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5031354"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5031356"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;update history pages. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://aka.ms/Windows/MonthlyUpdates" data-linktype="external" target="_blank"&gt;Windows monthly updates explained&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on X (formerly Twitter) &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://x.com/windowsupdate" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;&lt;u&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11 update:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IMPORTANT&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/en-us/lifecycle/announcements/windows-11-21h2-end-of-servicing" data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;The October 2023 security update is the last security release for some editions of Windows 11, version 21H2&lt;/a&gt;. Windows 11, version 22H2 will continue to receive security and optional releases.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Short on time? Watch our short &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fgFT0p7O_hQ" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 11 update&lt;/a&gt; release notes video for this month's tips.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5031354" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3186</id><title type="html">Home &amp; Pro editions of Windows 11, version 21H2 have reached end of servicing - October 10, 2023</title><updated>2023-10-10T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;As of October 10, 2023,&amp;nbsp;Home, Pro, Pro for Workstations, and Pro Education editions of&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/lifecycle/announcements/windows-11-21h2-end-of-servicing" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 11, version 21H2&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;have reached end of servicing. The &lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5031358" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;October 2023 security update&lt;/a&gt;, released on October 10, 2023, is the last update available for these editions. After this date, devices running these editions will no longer receive monthly security and preview updates containing protections from the latest security threats. Enterprise, Education, IoT Enterprise, and Enterprise multi-session editions for this version will reach end of servicing on October 8, 2024 and will receive security updates until then.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;To help keep you protected and productive, Windows Update will automatically initiate a feature update for Windows 11 consumer devices and non-managed business devices that are at, or within several months of reaching, end of servicing. This keeps your device supported and receiving monthly updates that are critical to security and ecosystem health. For these devices, you will be able to&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/get-updates-when-you-re-away-from-your-pc-with-active-hours-in-windows-09b5376c-7647-4361-1423-c29aa692a8c4#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;choose a convenient time&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;for your device to restart and complete the update.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As always, we recommend that you update&amp;nbsp;your&amp;nbsp;devices to the latest version of&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://aka.ms/W11/how-to-get-22H2" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt;. For detailed information, see the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="/en-us/lifecycle/announcements/windows-11-21h2-end-of-servicing" data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 11, version 21H2 end of servicing (Home &amp;amp; Pro)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;lifecycle page. For information about servicing timelines and lifecycle, see&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/windows11-release-information"&gt;Windows 11 release information&lt;/a&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/lifecycle/faq/windows" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Lifecycle FAQ - Windows&lt;/a&gt;, and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/?terms=windows"&gt;Microsoft Lifecycle Policy search tool&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/lifecycle/announcements/windows-11-21h2-end-of-servicing" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3068</id><title type="html">Security hardening changes for Kerberos effective with the October 10, 2023 Windows Update</title><updated>2023-10-10T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;As previously announced, Windows updates released today, October 10, 2023, conclude the rollout of security enforcement to protect Windows Server domain controllers (DC) against a Kerberos security bypass vulnerability. This vulnerability also involves an elevation of privilege scenario and alteration of Privilege Attribute Certificate (PAC) signatures. These changes have been gradually enforced through a series of phases, beginning with Windows updates released November 8, 2022. Administrators should observe changes which affect Kerberos protocol requirements, and are coming into effect with the Windows updates released on and after October 10, 2023.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;October 10, 2023 - Full Enforcement phase&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Windows updates released on and after this date will have the following effect:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;This is the final phase of the rollout for these security hardening measures.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;All domain-joined, machine accounts are affected by these vulnerabilities. To understand the options available for configuring these security requirements in your environment, see &lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/topic/kb5020805-how-to-manage-kerberos-protocol-changes-related-to-cve-2022-37967-997e9acc-67c5-48e1-8d0d-190269bf4efb" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;KB5020805: How to manage Kerberos protocol changes related to CVE-2022-37967&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5020805" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3182</id><title type="html">Overview of Windows Backup as installed in Windows 10 and Windows 11</title><updated>2023-10-04T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Windows Backup enables you to back up files and folders, settings, credentials, and apps to the cloud through a single solution. In addition to restoring data, you can import data when switching to a new Windows device. This component is installed on devices as part of Windows updates released on and after August 22, 2023.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Currently, the Windows Backup app can be used for consumer devices - for example, devices that can be used by signing in to a personal Microsoft account (MSA). It's not presently available for Microsoft Entra ID (formerly Azure AD) or Active Directory (AD) users. Because Windows Backup is a system component, it cannot be removed. A future Windows Update will provide an option to prevent Windows Backup from appearing on certain user interface screens for Entra ID and AD users that run certain Windows editions.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;For answers to frequently asked questions related to this component, see &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5032038" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;KB5032038: Overview of Windows Backup as installed in Windows 10 and Windows 11&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5032038" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3178</id><title type="html">September skilling snacks: Bite-sized learning for IT pros</title><updated>2023-09-29T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;See what’s new in our special learning series on all things Windows. These public resources are packaged in a way that is easy to consume in under two hours each. This professional development opportunity is meant as a refresher or mentoring material for all IT skill levels. Take advantage of the following learning bites published in the month of September:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Bookmark our growing topics library for personalized learning: &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-skilling-snacks-bite-sized-learning-for-it-pros/ba-p/3725923" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows skilling snacks: bite-sized learning for IT pros&lt;/a&gt;. It now contains 25 learning journeys, and new topics are published every other week.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-skilling-snacks-bite-sized-learning-for-it-pros/ba-p/3725923" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3174</id><title type="html">Greenland DST changes 2023 update now available</title><updated>2023-09-27T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Updates are now available to reflect the new 2023 DST changes in Greenland. As previously announced, Greenland’s standard time will permanently shift to UTC-2, which is the same time that has been observed since March 25, 2023. In 2024, Greenland will resume annual Daylight Saving Time between March and October by temporarily shifting from UTC-2 to UTC-1. In support of this decision, Microsoft has released Windows updates to the latest versions of Windows 11 and Windows 10 on September 26. All other supported versions of Windows will receive the update as part of the October 2023 monthly quality release. A few users might notice a minor time discrepancy in the historical message string data in the “Date and Time” app. Please visit &lt;a href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/daylight-saving-time-time-zone/greenland-2023-time-zone-update-now-available/ba-p/3937743" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Greenland DST changes 2023 update now available&lt;/a&gt; for further details.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/daylight-saving-time-time-zone/greenland-2023-time-zone-update-now-available/ba-p/3937743" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3176</id><title type="html">The most personal Windows 11 experience begins to rollout today</title><updated>2023-09-26T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Last week we announced a new wave of capabilities that enhance accessibility, security, and the overall Windows 11 experience. Starting today, &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" href="https://blogs.windows.com/windowsexperience/?p=178423" target="_blank"&gt;more innovation is available&lt;/a&gt; for devices running the latest update of Windows 11, version 22H2. Windows Backup makes it easier to back up and transfer files and settings to a new PC. Voice access now works right when you start your PC. You can utilize passkeys instead of passwords when you sign into a website or application that supports them.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We’re also bringing the power of AI to your PC. Copilot in Windows (now in preview) helps you find answers and complete tasks quickly. Cocreator (also in preview) brings the power of generative AI to the Paint app. Photos offers new features, such as background blur, that make editing photos easy.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Some of these features are available today. Others will roll out gradually so you may not see them right away. If you have an eligible device that is running Windows 11, version 22H2, and want to experience these innovations, you can navigate to the &lt;strong&gt;Windows Update&lt;/strong&gt; settings page and turn on &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/get-windows-updates-as-soon-as-they-re-available-for-your-device-cad7b32b-001e-435b-9110-f18309b54168"&gt;Get the latest updates as soon as they’re available&lt;/a&gt;. (Note: For more detail on availability, see &lt;a href="https://blogs.windows.com/windowsexperience/?p=178424" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" target="_blank"&gt;How to get the latest Windows 11 innovations&lt;/a&gt;.)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://blogs.windows.com/windowsexperience/?p=178423" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3160</id><title type="html">The September 2023 Windows non-security preview update is now available</title><updated>2023-09-26T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The September 2023 non-security preview update is now available. These optional non-security previews are released only for Windows 10, version 22H2 and Windows 11, versions 21H2 and 22H2. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article. Information about the contents of this update is available from the release notes, which are accessible from the &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5030310" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt; and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5030300" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt; update history pages. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" href="https://aka.ms/Windows/MonthlyUpdates" target="_blank"&gt;Windows monthly updates explained&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on X (formerly Twitter) &lt;a data-linktype="external" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://x.com/windowsupdate"&gt;&lt;u&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11, version 22H2 update:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IMPORTANT&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;The September 2023 non-security preview update will be the last optional release for Windows 11, version 21H2. &lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/lifecycle/announcements/windows-11-21h2-end-of-servicing" target="_blank"&gt;The October 2023 security update will be the last security release for some editions of Windows 11, version 21H2&lt;/a&gt;. Windows 11, version 22H2 will continue to receive security and optional releases.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5030310" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3168</id><title type="html">Where organizations can find trusted information on Windows</title><updated>2023-09-25T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Take a quick tour of Windows technical documentation on Microsoft Learn, Windows release health, and other resources that offer the information you and your organization need to better manage your Windows estate. We'll delve into how documentation is created--and how you can contribute to better docs! Ready to learn? See &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rqdUb2sgLcg" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Tackling Tech: Behind the scenes with Windows docs and trusted information&lt;/a&gt;. And, for links to the resources discussed in this episode, see our &lt;a href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/skilling-snack-windows-information-and-resources-for-it-pros/ba-p/3885111" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;skilling snack on Windows information and resources for IT pros&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rqdUb2sgLcg" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3167</id><title type="html">Tackling Tech: Windows LAPS  </title><updated>2023-09-22T20:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If your organization needs to store local admin account passwords safely, &lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/by-popular-demand-windows-laps-available-now/ba-p/3788747" target="_blank"&gt;Windows Local Administrator Password Solution (LAPS)&lt;/a&gt; can help! Dive into what Windows LAPS is, how it works, and why it’s useful to you! Check out the conversation at &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bcs1gPB4dOQ"&gt;Keeping passwords secure with Windows LAPS&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bcs1gPB4dOQ" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3169</id><title type="html">Windows Office Hours: September 28th, 2023</title><updated>2023-09-22T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you are an IT admin with questions about managing and updating Windows, we want to help. Every third Thursday of the month, we host a live chat-based event on the Tech Community called Windows Office Hours. Members of the Windows, Intune, Windows Autopilot, Windows Autopatch, and Windows 365 engineering teams stand by to answer your questions. We also have experts from FastTrack, the Customer Acceleration Team, and Microsoft public sector teams.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Want to attend the&amp;nbsp;September 28th&amp;nbsp;session of Office Hours?&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/gxcuf89792/downloadCalendar?message.id=3871716" data-linktype="external"&gt;Click here to add it to your calendar&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and log in to the Tech Community to post your questions early! You can also bookmark&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://aka.ms/Windows/OfficeHours" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;https://aka.ms/Windows/OfficeHours&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;for upcoming dates (and the ability to add this event to your calendar). We look forward to helping you.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-events/windows-office-hours-september-28-2023/ev-p/3871716" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3161</id><title type="html">Expanding our AI capabilities to meet the everyday needs of people and business</title><updated>2023-09-21T15:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Today, Microsoft took the first step to unify our AI capabilities as Microsoft Copilot, providing a consistent look and feel across our products. Available as a side pane in Microsoft applications like Microsoft 365 and Edge, and on your Windows taskbar, the Copilot icon will be a consistent experience and entry point. To learn more about the new Copilot experience, and the updates we are bringing to Windows 11, Microsoft 365, Bing, Microsoft Edge, and Surface, read today’s announcement on&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://aka.ms/AAlwlsw"&gt;Ushering in a new era of AI with Copilot from Microsoft designed to empower people across work and life&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://aka.ms/AAlwlsw" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3156</id><title type="html">Take action: September 2023 security update is now available</title><updated>2023-09-12T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The September 2023 security update release is now available for Windows 11 and all supported versions of Windows 10. We recommend that you install these updates promptly. For more information about the contents of this update, see the release notes, which are easily accessible from the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5030219" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5030211" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;update history pages. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" target="_blank"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see &lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://aka.ms/Windows/MonthlyUpdates" target="_blank"&gt;Windows monthly updates explained&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on X (formerly Twitter) &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://x.com/windowsupdate" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;&lt;u&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11 update:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IMPORTANT&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;The September 2023 non-security preview update will be the last optional release for Windows 11, version 21H2. &lt;a href="/en-us/lifecycle/announcements/windows-11-21h2-end-of-servicing" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;The October 2023 security update will be the last security release for some editions of Windows 11, version 21H2&lt;/a&gt;. Windows 11, version 22H2 will continue to receive security and optional releases.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Short on time? Watch our short &lt;a href="https://youtu.be/Aa6FViB5bPM" data-linktype="external" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 11 update&lt;/a&gt; release notes video for this month's tips.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5030219" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3158</id><title type="html">Reminder: Security hardening changes for Netlogon and Kerberos effective October 10, 2023</title><updated>2023-09-11T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Windows updates release November 8, 2022 and later include changes that address security vulnerabilities affecting Windows Server domain controllers (DC). Among the addressed vulnerabilities is a Kerberos security bypass and elevation of privilege scenario involving alteration of Privilege Attribute Certificate (PAC) signatures. Changes to address this issue have been released following a series of phases throughout 2023, and are reaching the final stage of enforcement in October.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Administrators should observe changes which affect Kerberos protocol requirements and are coming into effect with the Windows updates released on and after October 10, 2023.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;October 10, 2023 - Full Enforcement phase&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Windows updates released on and after this date will have the following effect:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The phase described above is the final phase of these security hardening measures.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;All domain-joined, machine accounts are affected by these vulnerabilities. To understand the options available for configuring these security requirements in your environment, see &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/topic/kb5020805-how-to-manage-kerberos-protocol-changes-related-to-cve-2022-37967-997e9acc-67c5-48e1-8d0d-190269bf4efb"&gt;KB5020805: How to manage Kerberos protocol changes related to CVE-2022-37967&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/topic/kb5020805-how-to-manage-kerberos-protocol-changes-related-to-cve-2022-37967-997e9acc-67c5-48e1-8d0d-190269bf4efb" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3157</id><title type="html">The Windows release health experience is now available for GCC tenants</title><updated>2023-09-07T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Now, eligible Government Community Cloud tenants can access essential information about Windows update known issues and announcements on the Microsoft 365 admin center. IT admins in the public sector can check prerequisites for access, learn about the available types of content and notifications, and follow steps to configure these preferences to stay informed. A new article shares details, instructions, links for further help, and guidance to provide feedback. Read it at &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/public-sector-blog/the-windows-release-health-experience-is-now-available-for-gcc/ba-p/3920457"&gt;Check Windows issues information in the admin center&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/public-sector-blog/the-windows-release-health-experience-is-now-available-for-gcc/ba-p/3920457" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3150</id><title type="html">Interim guidance for Greenland DST changes 2023</title><updated>2023-09-06T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;According to the new law by the government of Greenland, this year, the country will not switch to Daylight Saving Time. Instead, Greenland’s standard time will permanently shift to UTC-2, which is the same time that has been observed since March 25, 2023. In 2024, Greenland will resume annual Daylight Saving Time between March and October by temporarily shifting from UTC-2 to UTC-1. In support of this decision, Microsoft will release Windows updates in late September, 2023 to the latest versions of Windows 11 and Windows 10. All other supported versions of Windows will receive the update as part of the October 2023 monthly quality release. Please visit &lt;a href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/daylight-saving-time-time-zone/interim-guidance-for-greenland-dst-changes-2023/ba-p/3910830" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Interim guidance for Greenland DST changes 2023&lt;/a&gt; for further details.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/daylight-saving-time-time-zone/interim-guidance-for-greenland-dst-changes-2023/ba-p/3910830" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3155</id><title type="html">Interim guidance for Syria DST changes 2023</title><updated>2023-09-06T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;On October 5, 2022, the Syrian government made an official announcement about a Daylight Saving Time (DST) time zone change. Since then, the official time has not advanced by an hour and has permanently shifted to the UTC+3 time zone. Microsoft is releasing updates to support this change. The October 22, 2023 non-security preview release includes the update for Windows 11 and Windows 10, version 22H2. All other supported versions of Windows will receive this time adjustment in the November 14, 2023 monthly quality release. Read &lt;a href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/daylight-saving-time-time-zone/interim-guidance-for-syria-dst-changes-2022/ba-p/3911223" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Interim guidance for Syria DST changes 2022&lt;/a&gt; for more details.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/daylight-saving-time-time-zone/interim-guidance-for-syria-dst-changes-2022/ba-p/3911223" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3153</id><title type="html">TLS 1.0 and TLS 1.1 will be disabled in future Windows OSes</title><updated>2023-09-01T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Transport Layer Security (TLS) is the most common internet protocol for setting up an encrypted channel of communication between a client and server.&amp;nbsp;Over the past several years, internet standards and regulatory bodies have&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://www.ietf.org/rfc/rfc8996.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;deprecated&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;or disallowed TLS versions 1.0 and 1.1, due to a variety of security issues. As such, future Windows operating systems will have TLS versions 1.0 and 1.1 disabled by default. This change applies only to future new Windows operating systems, both client and server editions. Windows versions that have already been released will not be affected by this change. Windows 11 Insider Preview builds starting in September 2023 will have TLS versions 1.0 and 1.1 disabled by default. There is an option to re-enable TLS 1.0 or TLS 1.1 for users who need to maintain compatibility.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Home users of Windows are unlikely to experience any issues related to this change. Enterprises will need to test their environment to detect and update or replace any affected apps.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;For information on this change, please see &lt;a data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/tls-1-0-and-tls-1-1-soon-to-be-disabled-in-windows/ba-p/3887947" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;TLS 1.0 and TLS 1.1 soon to be disabled in Windows&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/tls-1-0-and-tls-1-1-soon-to-be-disabled-in-windows/ba-p/3887947" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3147</id><title type="html">Expanded metadata in Windows Update for Business deployment service catalog</title><updated>2023-08-31T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;IT admins can now make better update management decisions with insights from expanded metadata. Windows Update for Business deployment service has expanded its catalog. The main improvements include greater detail about each update and a wider spectrum of update types. Expanded metadata is available for security, non-security, and out-of-band updates. A new article shows how to make Microsoft Graph API calls to retrieve update classification, cadence, naming, vulnerabilities, and revision details. See guidance and examples at &lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/unblocking-the-potential-catalog-metadata-expansion/ba-p/3903474" target="_blank"&gt;Enhance update management decisions with metadata and insights&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/unblocking-the-potential-catalog-metadata-expansion/ba-p/3903474" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3154</id><title type="html">Reminder: Windows 11, version 21H2 end of servicing (Home &amp; Pro)</title><updated>2023-08-31T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;On October 10, 2023,&amp;nbsp;Home and Pro editions of&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/lifecycle/announcements/windows-11-21h2-end-of-servicing" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 11, version 21H2&lt;/a&gt; will reach end of servicing. The upcoming October 2023 security update, to be released on October 10, 2023, will be the last update available for this version. After this date, devices running this version will no longer receive monthly security and preview updates containing protections from the latest security threats.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;To help keep you protected and productive, Windows Update will automatically initiate a feature update for Windows 11 consumer devices and non-managed business devices that are at, or within several months of reaching, end of servicing. This keeps your device supported and receiving monthly updates that are critical to security and ecosystem health. For these devices, you will be able to &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/get-updates-when-you-re-away-from-your-pc-with-active-hours-in-windows-09b5376c-7647-4361-1423-c29aa692a8c4#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" target="_blank"&gt;choose a convenient time&lt;/a&gt; for your device to restart and complete the update.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As always, we recommend that you update&amp;nbsp;your&amp;nbsp;devices to the latest version of&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://aka.ms/W11/how-to-get-22H2" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt;. For detailed information, see the &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/lifecycle/announcements/windows-11-21h2-end-of-servicing" data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 11, version 21H2 end of servicing (Home &amp;amp; Pro)&lt;/a&gt; lifecycle page. For information about servicing timelines and lifecycle, see&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="/en-us/windows/release-health/windows11-release-information" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Windows 11 release information&lt;/a&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank" href="/en-us/lifecycle/faq/windows"&gt;Lifecycle FAQ - Windows&lt;/a&gt;, and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/?terms=windows" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Microsoft Lifecycle Policy search tool&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IMPORTANT&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;The September 2023 non-security preview update will be the last &lt;strong&gt;optional release&lt;/strong&gt; and the October 2023 security update will be the last &lt;strong&gt;security release&lt;/strong&gt; for Windows 11, version 21H2. Windows 11, version 22H2 will continue to receive security and optional releases.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/lifecycle/announcements/windows-11-21h2-end-of-servicing" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3152</id><title type="html">August skilling snacks</title><updated>2023-08-29T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;See what’s new in our special learning series on all things Windows. These selections of already existing, public resources are packaged in a way that is easy to consume in under two hours each. This professional development opportunity is meant for all skill levels: those who are new to IT and those looking for a refresher or mentoring materials. Take advantage of the following learning bites published in the month of August:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Bookmark our growing topics library for personalized learning: &lt;a data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-skilling-snacks-bite-sized-learning-for-it-pros/ba-p/3725923" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows skilli﻿ng snacks: bite-sized learning for IT pros&lt;/a&gt;. It currently contains over 20 learning journeys, and new topics are published every other week. &lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-skilling-snacks-bite-sized-learning-for-it-pros/ba-p/3725923" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3151</id><title type="html">Israel 2024 time zone update now available</title><updated>2023-08-24T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;A new Windows update is available to address a known issue for Israel’s Daylight Saving Time (DST). The issue affects events scheduled for March 2024 and onwards. The fix is available in the non-security preview update released on August 22, 2023 for the 20H2 and newer versions of Windows 10 and Windows 11. All other supported Windows versions will receive the update as part of the September 2023 monthly quality update scheduled for September 12, 2023. Read &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/daylight-saving-time-time-zone/israel-2024-time-zone-update-now-available/ba-p/3908769" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Israel 2024 time zone update now available&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/daylight-saving-time-time-zone/israel-2024-time-zone-update-now-available/ba-p/3908769" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3144</id><title type="html">Reminder: Microsoft Edge for Business is available in Edge version 116</title><updated>2023-08-22T17:15:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Microsoft Edge for Business, the new, dedicated work experience, is now available in Microsoft Edge &lt;strong&gt;stable version 116&lt;/strong&gt;. All users who sign in to Edge using Microsoft Entra ID (formerly Azure Active Directory) will automatically be transitioned to Microsoft Edge for Business as part of the release. Upon first opening Edge after the update, users will see an in-product banner informing them of the change with a link to learn more.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Microsoft Edge for Business includes new visual elements, an adjusted icon, and optional personal browsing window so users with a personal profile can separate their work and personal browsing. &lt;strong&gt;Policies, settings, and configurations previously set by an organization and its Entra ID connected users will be maintained in the transition to Edge for Business. &lt;/strong&gt;There is no impact to users' default browser settings. Additionally, passwords, favorites, and data currently associated with the user’s work profile will be transferred to Edge for Business.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Read the &lt;a href="https://aka.ms/EdgeforBusinessFAQ" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Microsoft Edge for Business FAQ&lt;/a&gt; for more in-depth information.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/deployedge/microsoft-edge-for-business" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3146</id><title type="html">The August 2023 Windows non-security preview update is now available</title><updated>2023-08-22T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The August 2023 non-security preview update is now available. These optional non-security previews are released only for Windows 10, version 22H2 and Windows 11, versions 21H2 and 22H2. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article. Information about the contents of this update is available from the release notes, which are accessible from the &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5029351" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt; and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5029331" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt; update history pages. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see &lt;a href="https://aka.ms/Windows/MonthlyUpdates" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows monthly updates explained&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on Twitter &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/windowsupdate" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;&lt;u&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11, version 22H2 update:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5029351" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3148</id><title type="html">Enable and control optional updates for your organization</title><updated>2023-08-22T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;IT admins can now manage early adoption of new productivity features and fixes for Windows 11 with a new policy. You can set up the policy called “Enable optional updates” to allow users in your organization to receive optional updates with different levels of control.&amp;nbsp;They can either&amp;nbsp;automatically receive optional updates, including or not gradual feature rollouts or CFRs, or manually select what optional updates to receive. Learn more about the details and benefits of this policy, along with tips to support user readiness in &lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/enable-and-control-optional-updates-for-your-organization/ba-p/3905218" target="_blank"&gt;Enable and control optional updates for your organization&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/enable-and-control-optional-updates-for-your-organization/ba-p/3905218" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3142</id><title type="html">Windows Office Hours: August 17th, 2023</title><updated>2023-08-10T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you are an IT admin with questions about managing and updating Windows, we want to help. Every third Thursday of the month, we host a live chat-based event on the Tech Community called Windows Office Hours. Members of the Windows, Intune, Windows Autopilot, Windows Autopatch, and Windows 365 engineering teams stand by to answer your questions. We also have experts from FastTrack, the Customer Acceleration Team, and Microsoft public sector teams.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Want to attend the&amp;nbsp;August 17th&amp;nbsp;session of Office Hours?&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/gxcuf89792/downloadCalendar?message.id=3871709" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Click here to add it to your calendar&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and log in to the Tech Community to post your questions early! You can also bookmark&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://aka.ms/Windows/OfficeHours" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;https://aka.ms/Windows/OfficeHours&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;for upcoming dates (and the ability to add this event to your calendar). We look forward to helping you.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-events/windows-office-hours-august-17-2023/ev-p/3871709" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3140</id><title type="html">Take action: August 2023 security update is now available</title><updated>2023-08-08T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The August 2023 security update release is now available for Windows 11 and all supported versions of Windows 10. We recommend that you install these updates promptly. For more information about the contents of this update, see the release notes, which are easily accessible from the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5029263" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5029244" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;update history pages. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see &lt;a href="https://aka.ms/Windows/MonthlyUpdates" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows monthly updates explained&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on Twitter &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://twitter.com/windowsupdate"&gt;&lt;u&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11 update:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Short on time? Watch our short &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://youtu.be/GJ6PhQzqNjM"&gt;Windows 11 update&lt;/a&gt; release notes video for this month's tips.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5029263" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3139</id><title type="html">Drivers and firmware management on Window Autopatch</title><updated>2023-08-03T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;New capabilities for deploying drivers and firmware are coming to Windows Autopatch-enabled tenants. Using Microsoft Intune's recently released driver management capabilities, you can better manage and report on drivers and firmware updates.&amp;nbsp;With this upcoming feature, Windows Autopatch will configure the deployment of required drivers and firmware available through Windows Update to your Windows Autopatch devices.&amp;nbsp;If you are an existing Windows Autopatch customer, you should see this by August 14. General availability is being released in phases and is planned to conclude by this date.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;See &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="/en-us/windows/deployment/windows-autopatch/operate/windows-autopatch-manage-driver-and-firmware-updates" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Windows Autopatch: Manage Driver and Firmware Updates&lt;/a&gt; for more details.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;If you are not currently using Windows Autopatch and are interested in learning more about this service, consider reading the report commissioned from Forrester: &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://query.prod.cms.rt.microsoft.com/cms/api/am/binary/RW10vlw" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;New Technology: The Projected Total Economic Impact™ Of Windows Autopatch&lt;/a&gt;. You can also read our &lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/windows/deployment/windows-autopatch/overview/windows-autopatch-overview" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows Autopatch overview on Microsoft Learn&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/deployment/windows-autopatch/operate/windows-autopatch-manage-driver-and-firmware-updates" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3137</id><title type="html">July skilling snacks: Bite-sized learning for IT pros</title><updated>2023-07-28T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Our special learning series now includes 6 months’ worth of IT pro topics for continued professional development. These selections of already existing, public resources are packaged in a way that is easy to consume in under two hours each. It’s meant for all skill levels: those who are new to IT and those looking for a refresher or mentoring materials. Take advantage of the following learning bites published in the month of July:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Bookmark our growing topics library for personalized learning: &lt;a data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-skilling-snacks-bite-sized-learning-for-it-pros/ba-p/3725923" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows skilling snacks: bite-sized learning for IT pros&lt;/a&gt;. New topics are published on a biweekly basis.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-skilling-snacks-bite-sized-learning-for-it-pros/ba-p/3725923" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3138</id><title type="html">Help users resume your app seamlessly after a Windows update</title><updated>2023-07-28T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;App developers: you can now find best practices for helping users easily resume a Windows app after a restart. Several native APIs can help you save the user’s state, remember how their previous views were positioned, and relaunch the app following the update. Helpfully, the article includes code examples and useful GitHub links to work with UWP apps, Win32 apps, and .NET apps. Get these details at &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://blogs.windows.com/windowsdeveloper/2023/07/20/help-users-resume-your-app-seamlessly-after-a-windows-update/"&gt;Help users resume your app seamlessly after a Windows update&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://blogs.windows.com/windowsdeveloper/2023/07/20/help-users-resume-your-app-seamlessly-after-a-windows-update/" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3131</id><title type="html">The July 2023 Windows non-security preview update is now available for Windows 11, version 22H2</title><updated>2023-07-26T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The July 2023 non-security preview update is now available for Windows 11, version 22H2. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article. Information about the contents of this update is available from the release notes, which are accessible from the &lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5028254" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt; update history page. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see &lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://aka.ms/Windows/MonthlyUpdates" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows monthly updates explained&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on Twitter &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://twitter.com/windowsupdate" data-linktype="external" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11, version 22H2 update:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5028254" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3136</id><title type="html">Importing updates into WSUS is changing</title><updated>2023-07-26T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you update devices in your organization with Windows Server Update Services (WSUS), the way you import updates has changed. Previously, you imported updates from the Microsoft Update Catalog site using the WSUS admin user interface under &lt;strong&gt;Updates&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;gt; &lt;strong&gt;Actions&lt;/strong&gt;. Starting July 25, 2023, this path takes you to a new PowerShell script instead. To learn how to get and use this script to import updates, please review the updated documentation in &lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/windows-server/administration/windows-server-update-services/manage/wsus-and-the-catalog-site" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;WSUS and the Microsoft Update Catalog&lt;/a&gt; and read the announcement &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/importing-updates-into-wsus-is-changing/ba-p/3882937"&gt;Importing updates into WSUS is changing&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/importing-updates-into-wsus-is-changing/ba-p/3882937" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3135</id><title type="html">The July 2023 Windows non-security preview update is now available for some versions of Windows</title><updated>2023-07-25T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The July 2023 non-security preview update is now available. These optional non-security previews are released only for Windows 11, versions 21H2 and Windows 10, version 22H2. The preview update for Windows 11, version 22H2, will be available in the near term. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article. Information about the contents of this update is available from the release notes, which are accessible from the &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5028245"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt; and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5028244" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;update history pages. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://aka.ms/Windows/MonthlyUpdates"&gt;Windows monthly updates explained&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on Twitter &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/windowsupdate" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;&lt;u&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11, version 21H2 update:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5028245" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3130</id><title type="html">Windows Autopatch celebrates 1 year of managed updates</title><updated>2023-07-20T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Happy 1 year to Windows Autopatch! If you haven't yet explored, catch up on all the latest capabilities. New features include Autopatch groups, custom deployment rings, and policy naming. Organizations can also take advantage of more control over feature updates, the ability to opt out of Microsoft 365 apps or expedited Windows updates, and support for driver and firmware updates. The service also now offers improved reporting with increased visibility into policy health and remediations. Enhancements to Windows Autopatch will continue so, in the meantime, check out &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://aka.ms/AutopatchResource" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;deep dives&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://aka.ms/AutopatchDemo" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;demos&lt;/a&gt;; join the &lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://aka.ms/AutopatchCommunity" target="_blank"&gt;Windows Autopatch Tech Community&lt;/a&gt; for feedback, questions, and to request features; and finally, subscribe to &lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/bg-p/Windows10Blog/label-name/Windows%20Autopatch"&gt;Windows Autopatch blog updates&lt;/a&gt; for the latest on Autopatch!&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-autopatch-celebrates-1-year-of-managed-updates/ba-p/3866140" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3129</id><title type="html">Bing Chat Enterprise rolling out in Preview starting today</title><updated>2023-07-18T15:35:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Starting today, Bing Chat Enterprise will be rolling out to eligible Microsoft 365 tenants in Preview—it will be turned off by default.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Bing Chat Enterprise gives your organization AI-powered chat for work with commercial data protection. With Bing Chat Enterprise, user and business data are protected and will not leak outside the organization. What goes in—and comes out—remains protected. Your organization’s chat data is not saved, Microsoft has no eyes-on access to it, and it is not used to train the models.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Learn more about Bing Chat Enterprise at &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://blogs.microsoft.com/?p=52560989"&gt;Furthering our AI ambitions – Announcing Bing Chat Enterprise and Microsoft 365 Copilot pricing&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://blogs.microsoft.com/?p=52560989" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3126</id><title type="html">Hotpatch is now available on new Windows Server 2022 Azure Edition VMs on Azure with the Desktop Experience</title><updated>2023-07-18T15:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Hotpatch is now available for Windows Server Azure Edition VMs with&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank" href="/en-us/windows-server/administration/server-core/what-is-server-core"&gt;Desktop Experience installation mode&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;using the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://aka.ms/hotpatchondesktopnewimage" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;newly released image&lt;/a&gt;. Hotpatch is a feature that allows you to patch and install OS security updates to Windows Server Azure Edition VMs on Azure without requiring a reboot!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Hotpatching was previously available for the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" href="/en-us/windows-server/administration/server-core/what-is-server-core" data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Server Core&amp;nbsp;installation mode&lt;/a&gt;. Now, Windows Server Azure Edition VMs installed with the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/windows-server/administration/server-core/what-is-server-core" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Desktop Experience installation mode&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;(the Windows Explorer shell, Start Menu, etc.) will no longer reboot every month for security updates. This provides:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Try out Hotpatch today by using&amp;nbsp;the &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://aka.ms/hotpatchondesktopnewimage" data-linktype="external"&gt;new released images &lt;/a&gt;of Windows Server Azure Edition VMs on Azure. Learn more in &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://aka.ms/hotpatchondesktopGAblog" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Hotpatching is now available in preview for Windows Server VMs on Azure with Desktop Experience&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href="https://aka.ms/hotpatchfordesktopdocs" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Hotpatch for new virtual machines&lt;/a&gt; documentation.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://aka.ms/hotpatchondesktopGAblog" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3128</id><title type="html">90-Day Reminder: Windows 11, version 21H2 end of servicing (Home &amp; Pro)</title><updated>2023-07-14T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;On October 10, 2023,&amp;nbsp;Home and Pro editions of&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="/en-us/lifecycle/announcements/windows-11-21h2-end-of-servicing"&gt;Windows 11, version 21H2&lt;/a&gt; will reach end of servicing. The upcoming October 2023 security update, to be released on October 10, 2023, will be the last update available for this version. After this date, devices running this version will no longer receive monthly security and preview updates containing protections from the latest security threats.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;To help keep you protected and productive, Windows Update will automatically initiate a feature update for Windows 11 consumer devices and non-managed business devices that are at, or within several months of, reaching end of servicing. This keeps your device supported and receiving monthly updates that are critical to security and ecosystem health. For these devices, you will be able to &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/get-updates-when-you-re-away-from-your-pc-with-active-hours-in-windows-09b5376c-7647-4361-1423-c29aa692a8c4#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;choose a convenient time&lt;/a&gt; for your device to restart and complete the update.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As always, we recommend that you update&amp;nbsp;your&amp;nbsp;devices to the latest version of&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://aka.ms/W11/how-to-get-22H2" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt;. For detailed information, see the &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank" href="/en-us/lifecycle/announcements/windows-11-21h2-end-of-servicing"&gt;Windows 11, version 21H2 end of servicing (Home &amp;amp; Pro)&lt;/a&gt; lifecycle page. For information about servicing timelines and lifecycle, see&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/windows11-release-information" data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 11 release information&lt;/a&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="/en-us/lifecycle/faq/windows" data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Lifecycle FAQ - Windows&lt;/a&gt;, and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/?terms=windows" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Microsoft Lifecycle Policy search tool&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/lifecycle/announcements/windows-11-21h2-end-of-servicing" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3127</id><title type="html">Windows client roadmap update: July 2023</title><updated>2023-07-13T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Windows client roadmap updates help guide organizations with their planning processes. A new article announces that you’ll be able to update Windows 11, version 22H2 to version 23H2 via an enablement package (eKB). It means that you can continue (or begin) your Windows 11 rollout with version 22H2 now, without worrying about app or device compatibility in the fourth quarter of 2023. Additionally, IT admins can consider a new option for Windows 10 IoT Enterprise LTSC 2021. Starting August 1st, it will be available through Volume Licensing. Read these announcements and recommendations in &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-client-roadmap-update-july-2023/ba-p/3871736" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows client roadmap update: July 2023&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-client-roadmap-update-july-2023/ba-p/3871736" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3123</id><title type="html">Take action: July 2023 security update is now available</title><updated>2023-07-11T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The July 2023 security update release is now available for Windows 11 and all supported versions of Windows 10. We recommend that you install these updates promptly. For more information about the contents of this update, see the release notes, which are easily accessible from the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5028185" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5028166"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;update history pages. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://aka.ms/Windows/MonthlyUpdates" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows monthly updates explained&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on Twitter &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/windowsupdate" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;&lt;u&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11 update:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;This update includes broad availability of the &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://blogs.windows.com/windowsexperience/2023/05/23/announcing-new-windows-11-innovation-with-features-for-secure-efficient-it-management-and-intuitive-user-experience/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;innovations in privacy, security, and productivity&lt;/a&gt; we announced at the end of May, which bring the following:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Short on time? Watch our short &lt;a href="https://youtu.be/VPJtsmSlt6Y" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 11 update&lt;/a&gt; release notes video for this month's tips.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5028185" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3125</id><title type="html">Take action: July 11, 2023 starts the Second Deployment Phase to address CVE-2023-24932 for devices using Secure Boot</title><updated>2023-07-11T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The release of the July 11, 2023 security updates for Windows starts the Second Deployment Phase in &lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5025885" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;KB5025885: How to manage the Windows Boot Manager revocations for Secure Boot changes associated with CVE-2023-24932&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5025885" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;KB5025885&lt;/a&gt; contain the manual steps to verify your environment is ready for the changes and steps to enable the security hardening changes to protect against vulnerabilities tracked by &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2023-24932"&gt;CVE-2023-24932&lt;/a&gt; that can bypass the Secure Boot security feature using the BlackLotus UEFI bootkit.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The Second Deployment Phase in updates for Windows released July 11, 2023 or later add the following:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;For information on how to apply the revocations and what is required before you apply the revocations, see &lt;a data-linktype="external" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5025885"&gt;KB5025885: How to manage the Windows Boot Manager revocations for Secure Boot changes associated with CVE-2023-24932&lt;/a&gt;. We recommend that all Windows users review this documentation carefully, including both IT administrators and consumers.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5025885" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3124</id><title type="html">Reminder: Security hardening changes for Netlogon and Kerberos effective July 11, 2023</title><updated>2023-07-11T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The November 8, 2022 and later Windows releases include security updates that address security vulnerabilities affecting Windows Server domain controllers (DC). These protections follow a hardening change calendar and are released in phases. As previously announced, administrators should observe the following changes which are coming into effect following Windows updates released on and after June 13, 2023:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Netlogon protocol changes:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kerberos protocol changes:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;All domain-joined, machine accounts are affected by these vulnerabilities. Review the below KB entries to understand the options available for configuring these changing security requirements in your environment, as well as monitor for warnings and issues.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://yumetodo.github.io/unofficial-windows-message-center-rss/feed/atom10.xml" rel="self" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3119</id><title type="html">June skilling snacks: Bite-sized learning for IT pros</title><updated>2023-06-30T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Catch up on our special learning series for continued professional development in IT pro topics. These weekly selections of already existing, public resources are packaged in a way that is easy to consume in under two hours each. It’s meant for all skill levels: those who are new to IT and seasoned vets looking for refresher or mentoring materials. Take advantage of the following learning bites published in the month of June:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Bookmark our growing topics library for personalized learning of what and when you want: &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-skilling-snacks-bite-sized-learning-for-it-pros/ba-p/3725923" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows skilling snacks: bite-sized learning for IT pros&lt;/a&gt;. Please note that new topics are now published on a biweekly basis.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-skilling-snacks-bite-sized-learning-for-it-pros/ba-p/3725923" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3122</id><title type="html">Expedite KPI in Windows Update for Business reports</title><updated>2023-06-29T22:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;A new capability is available to IT admins to better monitor key performance indicators (KPI) of expedited security updates. The new KPI card under Windows Update for Business reports shows the progress across all devices within the deployments that target the latest security update. To check for this card in your tenant, visit &lt;strong&gt;Azure monitor &amp;gt; Workbooks &amp;gt; Windows Update for Business reports &amp;gt; Quality update&lt;/strong&gt;. A new article provides guidance to track each expedited update deployment, view alerts, examine the device state, and to query the logs. Read it in &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/expedite-kpi-in-windows-update-for-business-reports/ba-p/3860250" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Expedite KPI in Windows Update for Business reports&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/expedite-kpi-in-windows-update-for-business-reports/ba-p/3860250" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3117</id><title type="html">The June 2023 Windows non-security preview update is now available</title><updated>2023-06-28T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The June 2023 non-security preview update is now available. These optional non-security previews are released only for Windows 10, version 22H2 and Windows 11, versions 21H2 and 22H2. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article. Information about the contents of this update is available from the release notes, which are accessible from the &lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5027303"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt; and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5027293" data-linktype="external" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;update history pages. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see &lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://aka.ms/Windows/MonthlyUpdates"&gt;Windows monthly updates explained&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on Twitter &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://twitter.com/windowsupdate" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;&lt;u&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11, version 22H2 update:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5027303" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3118</id><title type="html">Manage Windows driver and firmware updates with Microsoft Intune</title><updated>2023-06-26T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;We’re excited to announce the general availability of Windows driver and firmware update management policies and reports in Microsoft Intune. If you’re an IT admin with an Enterprise license, learn about new capabilities, benefits, and upcoming improvements in &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://aka.ms/DriversAndFirmwareIntune" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;Manage Windows driver and firmware updates with Microsoft Intune&lt;/a&gt;. See how to create and manage driver update policies, as well as how to monitor and remediate issues with built-in reporting. These capabilities are built on the Windows Update for Business deployment service and are now integrated with Windows Autopatch.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://aka.ms/DriversAndFirmwareIntune" rel="alternate" /></entry></feed>