<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/yumetodo/unofficial-windows-message-center-rss</id><title>Windows message center - Recent announcements</title><updated>2025-01-26T00:33:31Z</updated><author><name>direek</name></author><author><name>Microsoft</name></author><link href="https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center" type="text/html" /><link href="https://yumetodo.github.io/unofficial-windows-message-center-rss/feed/atom10.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3474</id><title type="html">90-day reminder: Deprecation of WSUS driver synchronization</title><updated>2025-01-24T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you’re using driver synchronization updates via Windows Server Update Services (WSUS), prepare for change. This service is scheduled for deprecation on April 18, 2025. For on-premises contexts, drivers will be available on the Microsoft Update catalog, but you won’t be able to import them into WSUS. You’ll need to use any of the available alternative solutions, such as &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/windows-hardware/manufacture/desktop/device-drivers-and-deployment-overview" data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank"&gt;Device Driver Packages&lt;/a&gt;, or transition to cloud-based driver services for your organization, such as Microsoft Intune and Windows Autopatch. Read the original announcement, including links to alternatives, at &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/blog/windows-itpro-blog/deprecation-of-wsus-driver-synchronization/4177831" data-linktype="external"&gt;Deprecation of WSUS driver synchronization&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/blog/windows-itpro-blog/deprecation-of-wsus-driver-synchronization/4177831" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3467</id><title type="html">The January 2025 Windows security update is now available</title><updated>2025-01-14T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The January 2025 security update is now available for all supported versions of Windows. We recommend that you install these updates promptly. For more information about the contents of this update, see the release notes, which are easily accessible from the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5050009" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt; and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5049981" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;update history pages. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article.&amp;nbsp;To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://aka.ms/Windows/MonthlyUpdates"&gt;Windows monthly updates explained&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on X &lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" href="https://x.com/windowsupdate"&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11, version 24H2 update:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Short on time? Watch our &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gei0otVeueA" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 11 release notes video&lt;/a&gt; for this month's tips.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5050009" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3470</id><title type="html">Windows Office Hours: January 16, 2025</title><updated>2025-01-09T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you are an IT admin with questions about managing and updating Windows, we want to help. Every third Thursday of the month, we host a live chat-based event on the Tech Community called Windows Office Hours. Members of the Windows, Intune, Windows Autopilot, Windows Autopatch, and Windows 365 engineering teams will be standing by to answer your questions. We also have experts from FastTrack, the Customer Acceleration Team, and Microsoft public sector teams.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Want to attend the&amp;nbsp;January 16&amp;nbsp;session of Office Hours?&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/s/gxcuf89792/attachments/gxcuf89792/WindowsEvents/5239/1/Windows%20Office%20Hours%20-%20January%2016%202025.ics" data-linktype="external" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Add it to your calendar&lt;/a&gt; and select Attend on the &lt;a href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/event/windowsevents/windows-office-hours-january-16-2024/4358417" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;event page&lt;/a&gt; to let us know you’re coming.&amp;nbsp;There is no video or live meeting component. Simply visit the event page, log in to the Tech Community, and leave your questions in the Comments section. You can also bookmark&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://aka.ms/Windows/OfficeHours" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;https://aka.ms/Windows/OfficeHours&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;for upcoming dates (and the ability to add this event to your calendar). We look forward to helping you.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/event/windowsevents/windows-office-hours-january-16-2024/4358417" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3459</id><title type="html">Get started with December 2024 improvements in Windows 11</title><updated>2024-12-19T22:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you’re an IT professional or decision maker, start using the newest Windows 11 capabilities with helpful tips and actionable steps summarized in one place. &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" href="https://aka.ms/WindowsNewsYouCanUse/December2024" target="_blank"&gt;This month&lt;/a&gt;, learn how to get started with some of the innovations announced at Microsoft Ignite, among other security and productivity improvements. Dive deeper into Windows Autopatch unification, hotpatching for Windows client and server, latest security tips, as well as AI and cloud innovations.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://aka.ms/WindowsNewsYouCanUse/December2024" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3458</id><title type="html">Quarterly skilling snacks: Bite-sized learning for IT pros</title><updated>2024-12-17T22:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Visit our updated learning series on all things Windows. This quarter, we published the following learning bites on a new monthly cadence:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Our &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-skilling-snacks-bite-sized-learning-for-it-pros/ba-p/3725923" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;growing skilling snack library&lt;/a&gt; now contains 47 learning journeys. Each one of these consists of specially selected articles, videos, and other resources, designed for you to consume in about two hours or less. This professional development opportunity is appropriate for all skill levels and is updated monthly.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-11-news-you-can-use-july-2024/ba-p/4204680" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3461</id><title type="html">60-day reminder: Full Enforcement mode for Certificate-based authentication changes on Windows DCs</title><updated>2024-12-17T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you are a domain administrator for your organization, learn about the latest changes to certificate-based authentication. A series of changes started on May 2022 to enhance security and followed a planned timeline of Enablement Phases.&amp;nbsp;On September 10, 2024, changes to the Full Enforcement mode key dates were made to reflect new dates. In February 2025 or later, devices will move to Full Enforcement mode. However, you can move back to&amp;nbsp;Compatibility&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;mode until September 2025. Full registry key support will now end in September 2025.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;For more information, see &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://support.microsoft.com/topic/ad2c23b0-15d8-4340-a468-4d4f3b188f16" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;KB5014754: Certificate-based authentication changes on Windows domain controllers&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5014754" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3462</id><title type="html">(Updated) Notice: Content on Windows release health is temporarily limited to English</title><updated>2024-12-16T23:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;Updated on December 18, 2024: The issue affecting translation and localization of content on the Windows release health site has been resolved. If your browser’s default language is one of the 11 supported languages, you will continue to see content in your preferred language as expected. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Content published to the Windows release health website will be limited to English temporarily starting on December 17, 2024, due to an issue affecting the site’s translation and localization. This issue affects content on this page and other pages on the Windows release health site, including&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Windows message center, known issues and release information pages. We will update this message once this issue is resolved and translation resumes.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;This site is usually available in 11 languages: English, Traditional Chinese, Simplified Chinese, French (France), German, Italian, Japanese, Korean, Portuguese (Brazil), Russian, and Spanish (Spain). All text will appear in English if your browser’s default language is not one of the 11 supported languages.&amp;nbsp;If your browser is set to any language other than English, you will not see any new text added to these pages starting on December 17, 2024, until this issue is resolved.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;If you prefer to see the latest content in English until we address this localization issue, you can manually change this site’s display language. Just scroll down to the bottom of this page, select the current language displayed on the bottom left of the page, and select “English”. If you are an IT pro supporting an organization, visit Windows release health on the &lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/windows/deployment/update/check-release-health" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Microsoft 365 admin center&lt;/a&gt; to access more information on Windows planned changes, known issues, and new resources.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://yumetodo.github.io/unofficial-windows-message-center-rss/feed/atom10.xml" rel="self" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3457</id><title type="html">Windows Tech Community Live: December 11</title><updated>2024-12-10T23:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you are an IT admin managing Windows devices and updates, post your questions today for a new Windows edition of &lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://aka.ms/TCL/Windows" data-linktype="external"&gt;Tech Community Live&lt;/a&gt;. Microsoft product teams will be answering live and listening to your feedback about what you need to successfully adopt the latest Windows features and capabilities. Topics will include Windows security, update management, hotpatching, AI-powered enhancements, and Copilot+ PCs.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://aka.ms/TCL/Windows" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3454</id><title type="html">The December 2024 Windows security update is now available</title><updated>2024-12-10T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The December 2024 security update is now available for all supported versions of Windows. We recommend that you install these updates promptly. For more information about the contents of this update, see the release notes, which are easily accessible from the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5048667" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5048652" data-linktype="external" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;update history pages. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article.&amp;nbsp;To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see &lt;a href="https://aka.ms/Windows/MonthlyUpdates" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows monthly updates explained&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on X &lt;a data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://x.com/windowsupdate" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11, version 24H2 update:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Short on time? Watch our &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=W5XqKAC8lZo" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 11 release notes video&lt;/a&gt; for this month's tips.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IMPORTANT &lt;/strong&gt;Because of minimal operations during the Western holidays and the upcoming new year, there will be no December 2024 non-security preview update. Normal monthly servicing for both security and non-security preview updates will resume in January 2025.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5048667" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3453</id><title type="html">TPM 2.0 – a necessity for a secure and future-proof Windows 11</title><updated>2024-12-03T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Learn more about one of the key minimum system requirements for Windows 11: Trusted Platform Module (TPM) 2.0. A &lt;a href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/blog/windows-itpro-blog/why-windows-11-supports-only-tpm-2-0/4339066" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;new article&lt;/a&gt; describes how TPM 2.0 tackles new security challenges with improved industry standard cryptography, increased isolation, and seamless integration with Windows security capabilities. Follow enclosed recommendations to check the TPM status of devices in your organization using Microsoft Intune or Microsoft Configuration Manager. For devices that don’t already have TPM 2.0, read how you can prepare for the Windows 11 upgrade.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/blog/windows-itpro-blog/why-windows-11-supports-only-tpm-2-0/4339066" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3450</id><title type="html">Administrator protection on Windows 11</title><updated>2024-11-27T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Enhance your organization’s Windows security with Administrator protection through Windows Hello. Available to Windows Insiders first, it will verify your identity before allowing any action that requires administrator privileges. This minimizes the risk of the user making a system-level change by mistake. Additionally, it helps prevent malware from making silent changes to the system without the user knowing. You can configure Administrator protection using Group Policy, through the settings catalog in Microsoft Intune, or with other tools coming soon. Learn more in &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/blog/windows-itpro-blog/administrator-protection-on-windows-11/4303482" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Administrator protection on Windows 11&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/blog/windows-itpro-blog/administrator-protection-on-windows-11/4303482" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3451</id><title type="html">Hotpatch for client comes to Windows 11 Enterprise</title><updated>2024-11-26T22:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Protect your organization faster with hotpatch updates for Windows 11 Enterprise, version 24H2. This public preview offers the same level of security patching as the standard monthly security updates without restarting devices or disrupting the users. To get the latest new features, eligible devices will install the standard monthly security update and restart the first month of each quarter. You can use a new Windows quality update policy in Microsoft Intune and Windows Autopatch to opt devices in or out. To learn more, read &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/blog/windows-itpro-blog/hotpatch-for-client-comes-to-windows-11-enterprise/4302717"&gt;Hotpatch for client comes to Windows 11 Enterprise&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/blog/windows-itpro-blog/hotpatch-for-client-comes-to-windows-11-enterprise/4302717" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3449</id><title type="html">Get started with November 2024 improvements in Windows 11</title><updated>2024-11-26T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you’re an IT professional or decision maker, start using the newest Windows 11 capabilities with helpful tips and actionable steps summarized in one place. &lt;a data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://aka.ms/WindowsNewsYouCanUse/November2024" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;This month&lt;/a&gt;, learn how to get started with Windows Server 2025, hotpatching in Windows client, multiple tools to manage or transition to the cloud, do more with Copilot+ PCs and AI, and many more security and productivity improvements. With each topic, find relevant Microsoft Ignite sessions included for on-demand watching.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://aka.ms/WindowsNewsYouCanUse/November2024" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3418</id><title type="html">The November 2024 Windows non-security preview update is now available</title><updated>2024-11-21T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The November 2024 non-security preview update is now available for Windows 11, versions 24H2, 23H2, and 22H2, as well as Windows 10, version 22H2. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" data-linktype="external"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article. Information about the contents of this update is available from the release notes, which are accessible from the &lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5044380" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5045594"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;update history pages. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://aka.ms/Windows/MonthlyUpdates" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows monthly updates explained&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on X &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://x.com/windowsupdate" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11, versions 24H2 update:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IMPORTANT&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Because of minimal operations during the Western holidays and the upcoming new year, there will be no December 2024 non-security preview update. There will be a monthly security update for December 2024. Normal monthly servicing for both security and non-security preview updates will resume in January 2025.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5046740" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3443</id><title type="html">Calendar and To Do widgets are no longer available in the Microsoft Store</title><updated>2024-11-19T22:30:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;In our ongoing efforts to improve the Widgets Board, the Calendar and To Do widgets have been removed from the Widgets collection in the Microsoft Store for now.&amp;nbsp;Note: In some regions, Photos, Family and Microsoft 365 Feed widgets were also removed.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;While we work on bringing them back, check out the other Widgets available in the &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://apps.microsoft.com/collections/MerchandiserContent/Apps/WidgetCollection/Widgetsforeverything" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Microsoft Store&lt;/a&gt; for alternatives. Learn more about at &lt;a href="https://www.microsoft.com/windows/learning-center/what-are-widgets" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;What are Widgets, and How Do I Use Them?&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/stay-up-to-date-with-widgets-7ba79aaa-dac6-4687-b460-ad16a06be6e4" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Stay up to date with widgets&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://apps.microsoft.com/collections/MerchandiserContent/Apps/WidgetCollection/Widgetsforeverything" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3442</id><title type="html">The November 2024 Windows security update is now available</title><updated>2024-11-12T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The November 2024 security update is now available for all supported versions of Windows. We recommend that you install these updates promptly. For more information about the contents of this update, see the release notes, which are easily accessible from the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5046617" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5046613" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;update history pages. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article.&amp;nbsp;To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see &lt;a href="https://aka.ms/Windows/MonthlyUpdates" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows monthly updates explained&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on X &lt;a href="https://x.com/windowsupdate" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11, version 24H2 update:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Short on time? Watch our &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://youtu.be/RqZRgKdE4U8" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 11 release notes video&lt;/a&gt; for this month's tips.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IMPORTANT &lt;/strong&gt;Because of minimal operations during the Western holidays and the upcoming new year, there will be no December 2024 non-security preview update. There will be a monthly security update for December 2024. Normal monthly servicing for both security and non-security preview updates will resume in January 2025.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5046617" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3441</id><title type="html">Windows Server 2025 is now generally available </title><updated>2024-11-04T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Generally available today, &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://www.microsoft.com/windows-server/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows Server 2025&lt;/a&gt; builds on the Microsoft mission to deliver a secure and high-performance Windows Server platform tailored to meet diverse business needs. Windows Server 2025 offers advanced security, improved performance, and cloud agility. This release will enable IT administrators to deploy apps in any environment, whether on premises, hybrid environments, or in the cloud.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;This platform features advanced multilayered security, modern hybrid cloud capabilities, and the ability to handle the most demanding workloads, including AI and machine learning. To learn more, read the complete announcement on the &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://www.microsoft.com/windows-server/blog/" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows Server Blog&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://aka.ms/WindowsServer2025" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3438</id><title type="html">Get started with October 2024 improvements in Windows 11</title><updated>2024-10-31T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you’re an IT professional or decision maker, start using the newest Windows 11 capabilities with helpful tips and actionable steps summarized in one place. Read &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://aka.ms/WindowsNewsYouCanUse/October2024" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;this month’s recap&lt;/a&gt; of improvements in Windows client and server security, device and update management, AI, productivity, and collaboration.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Get started with Windows 11, version 24H2 feature update, cybersecurity resources, Windows Protected Print mode, Copilot+ PC updates, Windows Admin Center for Windows Server, and other improvements released in October.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://aka.ms/WindowsNewsYouCanUse/October2024" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3433</id><title type="html">How to prepare for Windows 10 end of support by moving to Windows 11</title><updated>2024-10-31T16:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;As the end of support for Windows 10 approaches, Microsoft wants to ensure you are well-prepared for the transition to Windows 11. This end of support on October 14, 2025* marks an important step in our mission to provide the most modern and secure computing experience possible for you, whether at work, school, or home. It also reflects our commitment to continually improving Windows security as part of &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://www.microsoft.com/trust-center/security/secure-future-initiative" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Microsoft Secure Future Initiative&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Today we published a &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" href="https://blogs.windows.com/windowsexperience/?p=179154" target="_blank"&gt;new blog post&lt;/a&gt; to help you prepare for Windows 10 end of support and outlined options for moving to Windows 11. The options include:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;*Note:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; Long-Term Servicing Branch (LTSB) and Long-Term Servicing Channel (LTSC) releases are subject to different lifecycle support policies. Check out the &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/?terms=Windows 10" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Microsoft lifecycle website&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; for more information. &lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://blogs.windows.com/windowsexperience/?p=179154" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3422</id><title type="html">The October 2024 Windows non-security preview update is now available for Windows 11, version 24H2</title><updated>2024-10-24T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The October 2024 non-security preview update is now available for Windows 11, version 24H2. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article. Information about the contents of this update is available from the release notes, which are accessible from the &lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5044384" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt; update history page. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://aka.ms/Windows/MonthlyUpdates" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows monthly updates explained&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on X &lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://x.com/windowsupdate" target="_blank"&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11, version 24H2 update:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5044384" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3420</id><title type="html">Windows 11, version 24H2 improved update fundamentals</title><updated>2024-10-23T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;With Windows 11, version 24H2, you get reduced installation time, restart time, and central processing unit (CPU) usage for Windows monthly updates. Additionally, feature updates now have smaller download sizes. That’s due to the extension of conditional downloads to Microsoft Edge. Learn about the details behind these improvements in a new article, &lt;a href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-11-version-24h2-improved-update-fundamentals/ba-p/4274431" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Windows 11, version 24H2 improved update fundamentals&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-11-version-24h2-improved-update-fundamentals/ba-p/4274431" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#268</id><title type="html">Reminder: Share your feedback on the Windows release health website.</title><updated>2024-10-23T16:45:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Your opinion matters! There's still time to participate in our survey to help improve the design and utility of the Windows release health site. &lt;a href="/en-us/windows/release-health/" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank"&gt;Windows release health&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;offers official information on Windows announcements, updates, servicing milestones, known issues, safeguards, and helpful resources. Your anonymous feedback will help us prioritize improving the features that are most important to you.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Our short survey will just take a couple of minutes of your time. Get started here:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" href="https://aka.ms/WRHsurvey2024" target="_blank"&gt;Windows release health website feedback&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://aka.ms/WRHsurvey2024" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3426</id><title type="html">(Updated) The October 2024 Windows non-security preview update is now available for some supported versions of Windows</title><updated>2024-10-22T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;Updated on October 25, 2024: This post was updated as we previously shared a highlight that is no longer available. This improvement will be available in a future update.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The October 2024 non-security preview update is now available for Windows 11, versions 23H2 and 22H2, and Windows 10, version 22H2. The non-security preview update for Windows 11, version 24H2 will be available soon. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" target="_blank"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article. Information about the contents of this update is available from the release notes, which are accessible from the &lt;a data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5044380" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5045594" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;update history pages. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see &lt;a href="https://aka.ms/Windows/MonthlyUpdates" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows monthly updates explained&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on X &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://x.com/windowsupdate" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11, versions 23H2 and 22H2 update:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5044380" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3419</id><title type="html">Windows Office Hours: October 17th, 2024</title><updated>2024-10-10T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you are an IT admin with questions about managing and updating Windows, we want to help. Every third Thursday of the month, we host a live chat-based event on the Tech Community called Windows Office Hours. Members of the Windows, Intune, Windows Autopilot, Windows Autopatch, and Windows 365 engineering teams will be standing by to answer your questions. We also have experts from FastTrack, the Customer Acceleration Team, and Microsoft public sector teams.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Want to attend the&amp;nbsp;October 17th&amp;nbsp;session of Office Hours? &lt;a href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-events/windows-office-hours-october-17-2024/ec-p/4218172" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;RSVP on the event page&lt;/a&gt; and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/gxcuf89792/downloadCalendar?message.id=4218172" data-linktype="external"&gt;click here to add it to your calendar&lt;/a&gt;. There is no video or live meeting component. Simply visit the event page, log in to the Tech Community, and leave your questions in the Comments section. You can also bookmark&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://aka.ms/Windows/OfficeHours" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;https://aka.ms/Windows/OfficeHours&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;for upcoming dates (and the ability to add this event to your calendar). We look forward to helping you.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-events/windows-office-hours-october-17-2024/ec-p/4218172" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3416</id><title type="html">The October 2024 Windows security update is now available</title><updated>2024-10-08T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The October 2024 security update is now available for all supported versions of Windows. We recommend that you install these updates promptly. For more information about the contents of this update, see the release notes, which are easily accessible from the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5044284"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5044273" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;update history pages. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="external" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article.&amp;nbsp;To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see &lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" href="https://aka.ms/Windows/MonthlyUpdates"&gt;Windows monthly updates explained&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on X &lt;a href="https://x.com/windowsupdate" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11, version 24H2 update:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Short on time? Watch our &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://aka.ms/Windows11/ReleaseNotes/Video/2410" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 11 release notes video&lt;/a&gt; for this month's tips.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;REMINDER&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;The October 2024 security update is the last security release for&amp;nbsp;Enterprise and Education editions of&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="/en-us/windows/release-health/windows11-release-information" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Windows 11, version 21H2&lt;/a&gt; and Home and Pro editions of&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="/en-us/windows/release-health/windows11-release-information" data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 11, version 22H2&lt;/a&gt;. After this date, devices running these editions will no longer receive monthly security and preview updates containing protections from the latest security threats. Supported editions of Windows 11 will continue to have support through their specific lifecycle dates, which can be found at the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/windows11-release-information" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Windows 11 release information page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5044284" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3408</id><title type="html">Some editions of Windows 11, versions 21H2 and 22H2 have reached end of servicing</title><updated>2024-10-08T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Starting today, October 8, 2024, Windows 11, version 21H2 (&lt;a href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-11-enterprise-and-education" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Enterprise&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-11-enterprise-and-education" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Education&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-11-iot-enterprise" target="_blank"&gt;IoT Enterprise&lt;/a&gt; editions) and Windows 11, version 22H2 (&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-11-home-and-pro" data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank"&gt;Home and Pro&lt;/a&gt; editions) have reached end of servicing. The October 2024 security update is the last update available for these editions. After today, devices running these editions will no longer receive monthly security and preview updates containing protections from the latest security threats.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;To help keep you protected and productive, Windows Update will automatically initiate a feature update for Windows 11 Home and Pro devices that are not managed by IT departments when these are nearing end of servicing. Moving to the &lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://aka.ms/how-to-get-24H2"&gt;latest version of Windows 11&lt;/a&gt; keeps your device supported and receiving monthly updates that are critical to security and ecosystem health.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;For detailed information, see the &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-11-enterprise-and-education" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Windows 11 Enterprise and Education&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-11-iot-enterprise" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 11 IoT Enterprise&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-11-home-and-pro"&gt;Windows 11 Home and Pro&lt;/a&gt; lifecycle pages. For information about servicing timelines and lifecycle, see &lt;a href="/en-us/windows/release-health/windows11-release-information" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Windows 11 release information&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank" href="/en-us/lifecycle/faq/windows" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Lifecycle FAQ - Windows&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/?terms=windows" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Microsoft Lifecycle Policy search tool&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows11-release-information" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3413</id><title type="html">Change to the Enforced by Default phase timeline for Kerberos signature validation risks</title><updated>2024-10-04T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Windows updates dated April 9, 2024, or later add new behaviors that start the process of addressing a security risk in the &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/openspecs/windows_protocols/ms-apds/82b7b7c6-413d-4d66-b6b7-4a9224549782" data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank"&gt;Kerberos PAC Validation Protocol&lt;/a&gt;. These improvements are deployed in three phases (see below). The timeline of the second phase, &lt;strong&gt;Enforced by Default&lt;/strong&gt;, has changed. This phase will occur in January 2025.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;To help protect your environment, see &lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5037754" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" target="_blank"&gt;KB5037754: How to manage PAC Validation changes related to CVE-2024-26248 and CVE-2024-29056&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5037754" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3403</id><title type="html">How to get new experiences for Windows 11</title><updated>2024-10-01T14:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Today we begin to release the Windows 11 2024 Update (also known as Windows 11, version 24H2) and &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" href="https://aka.ms/W11/NewExperiences" target="_blank"&gt;announce new Copilot+ PC innovations&lt;/a&gt; that enable you to engage with your device in a natural, conversational way. The Windows 11 2024 Update contains new features to help deliver transformational AI experiences and exceptional performance. You can learn more about all the new features, including enhanced battery saver, Bluetooth LE Audio, HDR background support, and support for Wi-Fi 7 in &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/inside-this-update-93c5c27c-f96e-43c2-a08e-5812d92f220d" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;What’s new inside this update&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are taking a phased approach with the 2024 Update rollout, based on when data shows your device is ready and you will have a great experience. We will begin with eligible devices running Windows 11, version 22H2 and 23H2 for those who have previously opted in to be amongst the first to experience new enhancements. (How can you be among the first to experience new features? Navigate to &lt;strong&gt;Settings &amp;gt; Windows Update&lt;/strong&gt;, and turn on “&lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/get-windows-updates-as-soon-as-they-re-available-for-your-device-cad7b32b-001e-435b-9110-f18309b54168"&gt;Get the latest updates as soon as they’re available&lt;/a&gt;.”) For more information on ways to get the update, see &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://aka.ms/how-to-get-24H2" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;How to get new experiences for Windows 11&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://aka.ms/video/W11/how-to-get-24H2" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;watch this video&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;IT administrators are encouraged to review &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://aka.ms/new-in-24H2"&gt;What’s new for IT pros in Windows 11, version 24H2&lt;/a&gt; for detailed information on commercial release channels, deployment tools, and enhancements for enterprises.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://aka.ms/how-to-get-24H2" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3409</id><title type="html">Get started with September 2024 improvements in Windows 11</title><updated>2024-09-30T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you’re an IT professional or decision maker, start using the newest Windows 11 capabilities with helpful tips and actionable steps summarized in one place. Read &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://aka.ms/WindowsNewsYouCanUse/September2024"&gt;this month’s recap&lt;/a&gt; of improvements in Windows client and server security, device and update management, Microsoft Copilot, productivity, and collaboration. Get started with the unified Windows Autopatch solution, new update compliance alerts in Microsoft Intune and Windows Update for Business reports, security improvements for Copilot+ PCs and Windows Server, new app solutions, among others. Additionally, try preview opportunities for Azure Arc-connected hotpatching for Windows Server 2025 and other improvements released in September.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://aka.ms/WindowsNewsYouCanUse/September2024" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3388</id><title type="html">The September 2024 Windows non-security preview update is now available for Windows 11, versions 23H2 and 22H2</title><updated>2024-09-26T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The September 2024 non-security preview update is now available for Windows 11, versions 23H2 and 22H2. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article. Information about the contents of this update is available from the release notes, which are accessible from the &lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5043145" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt; update history page. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see &lt;a data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://aka.ms/Windows/MonthlyUpdates" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows monthly updates explained&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on X &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://x.com/windowsupdate" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11, versions 23H2 and 22H2 update:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;REMINDER&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;The October 2024 security update is the last security release for&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-11-enterprise-and-education" target="_blank"&gt;Enterprise and Education editions&lt;/a&gt; of&amp;nbsp;Windows 11, version 21H2 and &lt;a href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-11-home-and-pro" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Home and Pro editions&lt;/a&gt; of&amp;nbsp;Windows 11, version 22H2. After this date, devices running these editions will no longer receive monthly security and preview updates containing protections from the latest security threats. Supported editions of Windows 11, versions 23H2 and 22H2 will continue to have support through their specific lifecycle dates, which can be found at the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="/en-us/windows/release-health/windows11-release-information" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 11 release information page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5043145" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3406</id><title type="html">The September 2024 Windows non-security preview update is now available for Windows 10, version 22H2</title><updated>2024-09-24T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The September 2024 non-security preview update is now available for Windows 10, version 22H2. The non-security preview update for Windows 11, versions 23H2 and 22H2 will be available soon. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" target="_blank"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article. Information about the contents of this update is available from the release notes, which are accessible from the &lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5043131" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;update history page. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see &lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://aka.ms/Windows/MonthlyUpdates"&gt;Windows monthly updates explained&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on X &lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://x.com/windowsupdate"&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 10, version 22H2 update:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;REMINDER&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;The October 2024 security update is the last security release for&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-11-enterprise-and-education" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Enterprise and Education editions&lt;/a&gt; of&amp;nbsp;Windows 11, version 21H2 and &lt;a target="_blank" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-11-home-and-pro" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Home and Pro editions&lt;/a&gt; of&amp;nbsp;Windows 11, version 22H2. After this date, devices running these editions will no longer receive monthly security and preview updates containing protections from the latest security threats. Supported editions of Windows 11, versions 23H2 and 22H2 will continue to have support through their specific lifecycle dates, which can be found at the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/windows11-release-information" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Windows 11 release information page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5043131" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3407</id><title type="html">Unified: Windows Autopatch and Windows Update for Business deployment service</title><updated>2024-09-23T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you manage Windows updates for your enterprise, you can do so with a single solution, Windows Autopatch. The functionality formerly known as Windows Update for Business deployment service has been woven into Windows Autopatch. A new, unified dashboard in the Microsoft Intune admin center now has four main sections: update policies, update groups, update status, and update reports. Your current license rights and functionalities under either Windows Autopatch or Windows Update for Business deployment service will remain the same. Learn more at &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/consolidating-update-management-for-enterprises/ba-p/4246896" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Consolidating update management for enterprises&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/consolidating-update-management-for-enterprises/ba-p/4246896" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3394</id><title type="html">Key dates updated for Certificate-based authentication changes on Windows domain controllers</title><updated>2024-09-20T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you are a domain administrator for your organization, learn about the latest changes to certificate-based authentication. On September 10, 2024, changes to the Full Enforcement mode key dates were made to reflect new dates. In February 2025 or later, devices will move to Full Enforcement mode. However, you can move back to &lt;strong&gt;Compatibility &lt;/strong&gt;mode until September 2025. Full registry key support will now end in September 2025.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;For more information, see &lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/topic/ad2c23b0-15d8-4340-a468-4d4f3b188f16"&gt;&lt;u&gt;KB5014754: Certificate-based authentication changes on Windows domain controllers&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/topic/ad2c23b0-15d8-4340-a468-4d4f3b188f16" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3393</id><title type="html">New alerts for Windows updates in Microsoft Intune</title><updated>2024-09-18T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you use Microsoft Intune to deploy Windows updates in your organization, streamline your reporting with two new device alerts. You can now find and troubleshoot devices that aren’t reporting correct update progress because they aren’t sending diagnostic data. The new alerts are DeviceDiagnosticDataNotReceived and MinimumOSBuildNotMet. Learn what they mean, where to find them in Microsoft Intune, and how to remediate the underlying issues. Get all the details in &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/new-alerts-for-windows-updates-in-microsoft-intune/ba-p/4248278" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;New alerts for Windows updates in Microsoft Intune&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/new-alerts-for-windows-updates-in-microsoft-intune/ba-p/4248278" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3396</id><title type="html">Enhancing data protection with Windows and Microsoft Copilot</title><updated>2024-09-16T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;We are ramping up data protection to help organizations advance their security goals while ensuring that people have seamless access to the AI productivity tools they need to stay ahead of the curve. With this effort, Copilot experiences in Windows are changing for managed PCs running Windows 11 Pro or Enterprise. Explore &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/enhanced-data-protection-with-windows-and-microsoft-copilot/ba-p/4246428" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;enhanced data protection with Windows and Microsoft Copilot&lt;/a&gt;. Looking for more information on today’s Microsoft 365 Copilot announcements? Get to know the &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://www.microsoft.com/microsoft-365/blog/2024/09/16/microsoft-365-copilot-wave-2-pages-python-in-excel-and-agents/"&gt;next phase of Microsoft 365 Copilot innovation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/enhanced-data-protection-with-windows-and-microsoft-copilot/ba-p/4246428" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3383</id><title type="html">Windows Office Hours: September 19th, 2024</title><updated>2024-09-13T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you are an IT admin with questions about managing and updating Windows, we want to help. Every third Thursday of the month, we host a live chat-based event on the Tech Community called Windows Office Hours. Members of the Windows, Intune, Windows Autopilot, Windows Autopatch, and Windows 365 engineering teams will be standing by to answer your questions. We also have experts from FastTrack, the Customer Acceleration Team, and Microsoft public sector teams.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Want to attend the&amp;nbsp;September 19th&amp;nbsp;session of Office Hours? &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-events/windows-office-hours-september-19-2024/ec-p/4218168" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;RSVP on the event page&lt;/a&gt; and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/gxcuf89792/downloadCalendar?message.id=4218168" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;click here to add it to your calendar&lt;/a&gt;. There is no video or live meeting component. Simply visit the event page, log in to the Tech Community, and leave your questions in the Comments section. You can also bookmark&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://aka.ms/Windows/OfficeHours" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;https://aka.ms/Windows/OfficeHours&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;for upcoming dates (and the ability to add this event to your calendar). We look forward to helping you.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-events/windows-office-hours-september-19-2024/ec-p/4218168" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3382</id><title type="html">The September 2024 Windows security update is now available</title><updated>2024-09-10T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The September&amp;nbsp;2024 security update is now available for all supported versions of Windows. We recommend that you install these updates promptly. For more information about the contents of this update, see the release notes, which are easily accessible from the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="external" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5043076"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5043064" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;update history pages. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" data-linktype="external"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article.&amp;nbsp;To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see &lt;a href="https://aka.ms/Windows/MonthlyUpdates" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Windows monthly updates explained&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on X &lt;a href="https://x.com/windowsupdate" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11, versions 23H2 and 22H2 update:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Short on time? Watch our &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qXsKJhhh43s" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 11 release notes video&lt;/a&gt; for this month's tips.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;REMINDER&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;The October 2024 security update is the last security release for&amp;nbsp;Enterprise and Education editions of&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="/en-us/windows/release-health/windows11-release-information" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 11, version 21H2&lt;/a&gt; and Home and Pro editions of&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="/en-us/windows/release-health/windows11-release-information" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Windows 11, version 22H2&lt;/a&gt;. After this date, devices running these editions will no longer receive monthly security and preview updates containing protections from the latest security threats. Supported editions of Windows 11, versions 23H2 and 22H2 will continue to have support through their specific lifecycle dates, which can be found at the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/windows11-release-information" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Windows 11 release information page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5043076" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3369</id><title type="html">30-Day Reminder: Upcoming end of servicing date for some editions of Windows 11, versions 21H2 and 22H2</title><updated>2024-09-09T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;On October 8, 2024, Windows 11, version 21H2 (&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-11-enterprise-and-education" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Enterprise&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-11-enterprise-and-education" target="_blank"&gt;Education&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-11-iot-enterprise" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;IoT Enterprise&lt;/a&gt; editions) and Windows 11, version 22H2 (&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-11-home-and-pro"&gt;Home and Pro&lt;/a&gt; editions) will reach end of servicing. The upcoming October 2024 security update, to be released on October 8, 2024, will be the last update available for these editions. After this date, devices running these editions will no longer receive monthly security and preview updates containing protections from the latest security threats.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;To help keep you protected and productive, Windows Update will automatically initiate a feature update for Windows 11 Home and Pro devices that are not managed by IT departments when these are nearing end of servicing. Moving to &lt;a href="https://aka.ms/W11/how-to-get-23H2" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 11, version 23H2&lt;/a&gt; keeps your device supported and receiving monthly updates that are critical to security and ecosystem health.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;For detailed information, see the &lt;a href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-11-enterprise-and-education" data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 11 Enterprise and Education&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-11-iot-enterprise" data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 11 IoT Enterprise&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-11-home-and-pro"&gt;Windows 11 Home and Pro&lt;/a&gt; lifecycle pages. For information about servicing timelines and lifecycle, see &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/windows11-release-information"&gt;Windows 11 release information&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/lifecycle/faq/windows" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Lifecycle FAQ - Windows&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/?terms=windows" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Microsoft Lifecycle Policy search tool&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows11-release-information" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3379</id><title type="html">The August 2024 Windows non-security preview update is now available for Windows 10, version 22H2</title><updated>2024-08-29T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The August 2024 non-security preview update is now available for Windows 10, version 22H2. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" target="_blank"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article. Information about the contents of this update is available from the release notes, which are accessible from the &lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5041582" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;update history page. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see &lt;a href="https://aka.ms/Windows/MonthlyUpdates" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows monthly updates explained&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on X &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://x.com/windowsupdate" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 10, version 22H2 update:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5041582" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3381</id><title type="html">Get started with August 2024 improvements in Windows 11</title><updated>2024-08-29T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you’re an IT professional or decision maker, start using the newest Windows 11 capabilities with helpful tips and actionable steps summarized in one place. Read &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://aka.ms/WindowsNewsYouCanUse/August2024" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;this month’s recap&lt;/a&gt; of improvements in Windows security, device and update management, Windows Server, productivity, and collaboration. Get started with the new Windows 365 features and offerings, security improvements, as well as solutions for specific scenarios in Windows Autopatch, Microsoft Intune, and app management, among others. Additionally, find preview opportunities for Windows Server 2025 hotpatching, the new Windows App, and other improvements released in August.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://aka.ms/WindowsNewsYouCanUse/August2024" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3380</id><title type="html">August skilling snacks: Bite-sized learning for IT pros</title><updated>2024-08-28T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Visit our updated learning series on all things Windows. This month, we published the following learning bites:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Our &lt;a href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-skilling-snacks-bite-sized-learning-for-it-pros/ba-p/3725923" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;growing skilling snack library&lt;/a&gt; now contains 44 learning journeys. Each one of these consists of specially selected articles, videos, and other resources, designed for you to consume in about two hours or less. This professional development opportunity is appropriate for all skill levels and is updated every other week.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-skilling-snacks-bite-sized-learning-for-it-pros/ba-p/3725923" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3371</id><title type="html">The August 2024 Windows non-security preview update is now available for Windows 11, versions 23H2 and 22H2</title><updated>2024-08-27T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The August 2024 non-security preview update is now available for Windows 11, versions 23H2 and 22H2. The non-security preview update for Windows 10, version 22H2 will be available soon. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" target="_blank"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article. Information about the contents of this update is available from the release notes, which are accessible from the &lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5041587" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt; update history page. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://aka.ms/Windows/MonthlyUpdates" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows monthly updates explained&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on X &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://x.com/windowsupdate" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11, versions 23H2 and 22H2 update:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;REMINDER&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;The October 2024 security update is the last security release for&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-11-enterprise-and-education" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Enterprise and Education editions&lt;/a&gt; of&amp;nbsp;Windows 11, version 21H2 and &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-11-home-and-pro" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Home and Pro editions&lt;/a&gt; of&amp;nbsp;Windows 11, version 22H2. After this date, devices running these editions will no longer receive monthly security and preview updates containing protections from the latest security threats. Supported editions of Windows 11, versions 23H2 and 22H2 will continue to have support through their specific lifecycle dates, which can be found at the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/windows11-release-information" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Windows 11 release information page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5041587" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3338</id><title type="html">Windows Autopatch: Auto-remediation with PowerShell scripts</title><updated>2024-08-26T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you use Windows Autopatch to manage Windows updates in your organization, you can sometimes experience deployment issues due to conflicts with Microsoft Intune policies. These issues are common in environments that rely on Configuration Manager (ConfigMgr) and Group Policy Objects (GPO). When this happens, you can use PowerShell detection and remediation scripts to easily rectify the problem. Read more about our recommended solution in &lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-autopatch-auto-remediation-with-powershell-scripts/ba-p/4228854" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows Autopatch: Auto-remediation with PowerShell scripts&lt;/a&gt;. This solution is for you if you currently use Microsoft Intune and don’t use third-party application patching solutions with Configuration Manager.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-autopatch-auto-remediation-with-powershell-scripts/ba-p/4228854" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3378</id><title type="html">Changes to Windows Boot Manager revocations for Secure Boot, effective July 9, 2024</title><updated>2024-08-26T17:30:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Follow the new guidelines to deploy changes across enterprises and understand how the new Windows Boot Manager self-revocation works. These new guidelines are part of a plan with five phases to deploy protections against the publicly disclosed Secure Boot security feature bypass (CVE-2023-24932).&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The Deployment Phase is now in effect and documented in the updated &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5025885" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;&lt;u&gt;KB5025885&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. The July 2024 Windows security update adds support for Secure Version Number (SVN) to block older Boot Managers. Additionally, learn how to set the updated SVN in the firmware.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The new Boot Manager deployed in the July update has a new self-revocation feature built in. When the Boot Manager starts to run, it performs a self-check by comparing the SVN that is stored in the firmware with the SVN built into the Boot Manager.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Learn more at &lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5025885" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;&lt;u&gt;KB5025885: How to manage the Windows Boot Manager revocations for Secure Boot changes associated with CVE-2023-24932&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5025885" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3372</id><title type="html">Reminder: Share your feedback on the Windows release health website.</title><updated>2024-08-23T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Please take a moment to participate in this quick survey to help us improve the design and utility of the Windows release health site.&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Windows release health&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;offers official information on Windows announcements, updates, servicing milestones, known issues, safeguards, and helpful resources. Your anonymous feedback will help us prioritize improving the features that are most important to you. Get started here:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://aka.ms/WRHsurvey2024" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows release health website feedback&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://aka.ms/WRHsurvey2024" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3364</id><title type="html">Protect against security risks and NPS connection failures that affect RADIUS server environments</title><updated>2024-08-16T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;IT admins should be aware of a security risk that exists in the Remote Authentication Dial-In User Service (RADIUS) protocol. &lt;a href="/en-us/dotnet/api/system.security.cryptography.md5?view=net-8.0" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;MD5&lt;/a&gt; collision problems affect &lt;a href="/en-us/windows-server/networking/technologies/nps/nps-udp-ports-configure" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;User Datagram Protocol&lt;/a&gt; or UDP-based RADIUS traffic over the internet. Data packets are at risk of forgery or changes to them during transit. For more information, see&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2024-3596" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" target="_blank"&gt;CVE-2024-3596&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/topic/kb5040268-how-to-manage-the-access-request-packets-attack-vulnerability-associated-with-cve-2024-3596-a0e2f0b1-f200-4a7b-844f-48d1d5ab9e66" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;KB5040268&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note &lt;/strong&gt;This security risk requires physical access to the RADIUS network and the &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/windows-server/networking/technologies/nps/nps-top" data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank"&gt;Network Policy Server&lt;/a&gt; (NPS). Also, the risk does not apply when RADIUS traffic goes over VPN.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As of July 9, 2024, Windows updates support the &lt;strong&gt;Message-Authenticator&lt;/strong&gt; attribute in &lt;strong&gt;Access-Request&lt;/strong&gt; packets. The new RADIUS standards mandate this change.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;However, if you install the July 2024, or later, updates, NPS connection failures can happen. This update does not cause these connection failures. This only occurs if your company’s firewall or RADIUS solution does not support this attribute. To learn more, see &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://support.microsoft.com/topic/kb5043417-radius-authentication-to-nps-might-fail-with-the-july-2024-security-update-and-later-updates-1a9d6cd4-5f8a-40eb-b2d6-f3a11cc0c308" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;KB5043417&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We recommend that you enable the &lt;strong&gt;Message-Authenticator&lt;/strong&gt; attribute in &lt;strong&gt;Access-Request&lt;/strong&gt; packets. Doing this addresses the security risk and the NPS issue. To learn more, see &lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://support.microsoft.com/topic/kb5040268-how-to-manage-the-access-request-packets-attack-vulnerability-associated-with-cve-2024-3596-a0e2f0b1-f200-4a7b-844f-48d1d5ab9e66" target="_blank"&gt;KB5040268&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5040268" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3346</id><title type="html">Windows Office Hours: August 15th, 2024</title><updated>2024-08-13T22:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you are an IT admin with questions about managing and updating Windows, we want to help. Every third Thursday of the month, we host a live chat-based event on the Tech Community called Windows Office Hours. Members of the Windows, Intune, Windows Autopilot, Windows Autopatch, and Windows 365 engineering teams will be standing by to answer your questions. We also have experts from FastTrack, the Customer Acceleration Team, and Microsoft public sector teams.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Want to attend the&amp;nbsp;August 15th&amp;nbsp;session of Office Hours? &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-events/windows-office-hours-august-15-2024/ec-p/4218164" data-linktype="external"&gt;RSVP on the event page&lt;/a&gt; and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/gxcuf89792/downloadCalendar?message.id=4218164" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;click here to add it to your calendar&lt;/a&gt;. There is no video or live meeting component. Simply visit the event page, log in to the Tech Community, and leave your questions in the Comments section. You can also bookmark&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://aka.ms/Windows/OfficeHours"&gt;https://aka.ms/Windows/OfficeHours&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;for upcoming dates (and the ability to add this event to your calendar). We look forward to helping you.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-events/windows-office-hours-august-15-2024/ec-p/4218164" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3366</id><title type="html">The August 2024 Windows security update is now available</title><updated>2024-08-13T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The August 2024 security update is now available for all supported versions of Windows. We recommend that you install these updates promptly. For more information about the contents of this update, see the release notes, which are easily accessible from the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5041585" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5041580"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;update history pages. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article.&amp;nbsp;To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see &lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://aka.ms/Windows/MonthlyUpdates"&gt;Windows monthly updates explained&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on X &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://x.com/windowsupdate"&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11, versions 23H2 and 22H2 update:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Short on time? Watch our &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mJjbwSXvpYw" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 11 release notes video&lt;/a&gt; for this month's tips.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;REMINDER&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;The October 2024 security update is the last security release for&amp;nbsp;Enterprise and Education editions of&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="/en-us/windows/release-health/windows11-release-information" data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 11, version 21H2&lt;/a&gt; and Home and Pro editions of&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="/en-us/windows/release-health/windows11-release-information" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 11, version 22H2&lt;/a&gt;. After this date, devices running these editions will no longer receive monthly security and preview updates containing protections from the latest security threats. Supported editions of Windows 11, versions 23H2 and 22H2 will continue to have support through their specific lifecycle dates, which can be found at the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/windows11-release-information"&gt;Windows 11 release information page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5041585" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3367</id><title type="html">60-Day Reminder: Upcoming end of servicing date for some editions of Windows 11, versions 21H2 and 22H2</title><updated>2024-08-08T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;On October 8, 2024, Windows 11, version 21H2 (&lt;a href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-11-enterprise-and-education" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Enterprise&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-11-enterprise-and-education" target="_blank"&gt;Education&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-11-iot-enterprise" target="_blank"&gt;IoT Enterprise&lt;/a&gt; editions) and Windows 11, version 22H2 (&lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-11-home-and-pro" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Home and Pro&lt;/a&gt; editions) will reach end of servicing. The upcoming October 2024 security update, to be released on October 8, 2024, will be the last update available for these editions. After this date, devices running these editions will no longer receive monthly security and preview updates containing protections from the latest security threats.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;To help keep you protected and productive, Windows Update will automatically initiate a feature update for Windows 11 Home and Pro devices that are not managed by IT departments when these are nearing end of servicing. Moving to &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://aka.ms/W11/how-to-get-23H2"&gt;Windows 11, version 23H2&lt;/a&gt; keeps your device supported and receiving monthly updates that are critical to security and ecosystem health.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;For detailed information, see the &lt;a href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-11-enterprise-and-education" data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 11 Enterprise and Education&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-11-iot-enterprise" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 11 IoT Enterprise&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/windows-11-home-and-pro" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 11 Home and Pro&lt;/a&gt; lifecycle pages. For information about servicing timelines and lifecycle, see &lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/windows11-release-information" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 11 release information&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/lifecycle/faq/windows" target="_blank"&gt;Lifecycle FAQ - Windows&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a target="_blank" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/?terms=windows" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Microsoft Lifecycle Policy search tool&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows11-release-information" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3362</id><title type="html">Get started with July 2024 improvements in Windows 11</title><updated>2024-07-31T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you’re an IT professional or decision maker, start using the newest Windows 11 capabilities with helpful tips and actionable steps summarized in one place. Read &lt;a href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-11-news-you-can-use-july-2024/ba-p/4204680" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;this month’s recap&lt;/a&gt; of improvements in Windows security, device management, Windows Server, productivity and collaboration, lifecycle milestones, and preview opportunities. Get started with Secure Boot protections, checkpoint cumulative updates, security baselines and cross-region disaster recovery for Windows 365, Windows Server preview opportunities, IoT LTSC, and other improvements released in July.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-11-news-you-can-use-july-2024/ba-p/4204680" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3363</id><title type="html">July skilling snacks: Bite-sized learning for IT pros</title><updated>2024-07-31T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Visit our updated learning series on all things Windows. This month, we published the following learning bites:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Our &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-skilling-snacks-bite-sized-learning-for-it-pros/ba-p/3725923"&gt;growing skilling snack library&lt;/a&gt; now contains 42 learning journeys. Each one of these consists of specially selected articles, videos, and other resources, designed for you to consume in about two hours or less. This professional development opportunity is appropriate for all skill levels and is updated every other week.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-skilling-snacks-bite-sized-learning-for-it-pros/ba-p/3725923" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3359</id><title type="html">Windows resiliency: Best practices and the path forward</title><updated>2024-07-25T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The broad, open nature and scale of the Windows computing ecosystem is part of what makes it a powerful and unmatched choice across the globe. The recent &lt;a href="https://blogs.microsoft.com/blog/2024/07/20/helping-our-customers-through-the-crowdstrike-outage/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;CrowdStrike incident&lt;/a&gt; underscores the need for mission-critical resiliency within every organization, and our unique ability to support the change required. This incident shows that Windows must prioritize change and innovation in the area of end-to-end resilience. Our goal is to be your trusted partner as you leverage technology and the end-to-end Microsoft stack to deliver amazing value for your workforce, your customers, and your partners. &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://aka.ms/WindowsResiliency"&gt;Read more&lt;/a&gt; about how we are working in close cooperation to improve resiliency across the Windows ecosystem and explore best practices you can use to support resiliency in your organization.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://aka.ms/WindowsResiliency" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3353</id><title type="html">(Updated) CrowdStrike issue impacting Windows endpoints causing an error message on a blue screen</title><updated>2024-07-25T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Updated on July 25, 2024: &lt;/strong&gt;Microsoft released further guidance on &lt;a href="https://aka.ms/WindowsResiliency" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows resiliency: Best practices and the path forward&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;. &lt;/strong&gt;Read more about how we are working in close cooperation to improve resiliency across the Windows ecosystem and explore best practices you can use to support resiliency in your organization.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Updated on July 22, 2024:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Microsoft has released a third mitigation option for the CrowdStrike Falcon agent issue impacting Windows clients and servers. If devices are unable to recover with the two previous options, IT admins can use PXE to remediate. See the revised&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/intune-customer-success/new-recovery-tool-to-help-with-crowdstrike-issue-impacting/ba-p/4196959" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;New Recovery Tool to help with CrowdStrike issue impacting Windows endpoints&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;for detailed instructions on prerequisites and configurations to use PXE Recovery.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Updated on July 21, 2024: &lt;/strong&gt;As a follow-up to the CrowdStrike Falcon agent issue impacting Windows clients and servers, Microsoft has released an&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;updated&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;recovery tool with&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;two repair options&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;to help IT admins expedite the repair process. Based on customer feedback, this new release includes a new option for recovery using safe boot, the option to generate ISO or USB, a fix for ADK detection when the Windows Driver Kit is installed, and a fix for the USB disk size check. See the revised &lt;a href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/intune-customer-success/new-recovery-tool-to-help-with-crowdstrike-issue-impacting/ba-p/4196959" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;New Recovery Tool to help with CrowdStrike issue impacting Windows endpoints&lt;/a&gt; for detailed instructions on using the &lt;a href="https://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?linkid=2280386" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;signed Microsoft Recovery Tool&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Updated on July 20, 2024:&lt;/strong&gt; Microsoft has released &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/topic/0d7741f7-aca1-4487-8a54-bd431cb49455" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;KB5042426&lt;/a&gt;, which contains step-by-step guidance for Windows Servers hosted on-premises that are running the CrowdStrike Falcon agent and encountering a 0x50 or 0x7E error message on a blue screen. We will continue to work with CrowdStrike to provide the most up-to-date information available on this issue.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;A new USB Recovery Tool is available to help IT admins expedite the repair process. The new tool can be found in the &lt;a href="https://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?linkid=2280386" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Microsoft Download Center&lt;/a&gt;. Read more about the new recovery tool and usage instructions at &lt;a href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/intune-customer-success/new-recovery-tool-to-help-with-crowdstrike-issue-impacting/ba-p/4196959" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;New Recovery Tool to help with CrowdStrike issue impacting Windows endpoints&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Updated on July 19, 2024:&lt;/strong&gt; A new Knowledge Base article, &lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/topic/b1c700e0-7317-4e95-aeee-5d67dd35b92f" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;KB5042421&lt;/a&gt;, with additional step-by-step guidance is now available for Windows 11 and Windows 10 clients. We will continue to work with CrowdStrike to provide up-to-date mitigation information as it becomes available.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Microsoft has identified an issue impacting Windows endpoints that are running the CrowdStrike Falcon agent.&amp;nbsp;These endpoints may encounter an error message on a blue screen and experience a continual restarting state.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We have received reports of successful recovery from some customers attempting multiple restart operations on affected Windows endpoints.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;To mitigate this issue, follow these steps:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;For Windows Virtual Machines running on Azure follow the mitigation steps in &lt;a href="https://azure.status.microsoft/status" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;Azure status&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Additional details from CrowdStrike are available here: &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://www.crowdstrike.com/blog/statement-on-windows-sensor-update/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Statement on Windows Sensor Update - CrowdStrike Blog&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/intune-customer-success/new-recovery-tool-to-help-with-crowdstrike-issue-impacting/ba-p/4196959" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#3347</id><title type="html">The July 2024 Windows non-security preview update is now available for Windows 11, versions 23H2 and 22H2</title><updated>2024-07-25T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The July&amp;nbsp;2024 non-security preview update is now available for Windows 11, versions 23H2 and 22H2. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article. Information about the contents of this update is available from the release notes, which are accessible from the &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5040527" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt; update history page. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see &lt;a href="https://aka.ms/Windows/MonthlyUpdates" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows monthly updates explained&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on X &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://x.com/windowsupdate" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11, versions 23H2 and 22H2 update:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;REMINDER&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;The October 2024 security update is the last security release for&amp;nbsp;Enterprise and Education editions of&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/windows11-release-information" data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 11, version 21H2&lt;/a&gt; and Home and Pro editions of&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/windows11-release-information" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Windows 11, version 22H2&lt;/a&gt;. After this date, devices running these editions will no longer receive monthly security and preview updates containing protections from the latest security threats. Supported editions of Windows 11, versions 23H2 and 22H2 will continue to have support through their specific lifecycle dates, which can be found at the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/windows11-release-information"&gt;Windows 11 release information page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5040527" rel="alternate" /></entry></feed>