<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/yumetodo/unofficial-windows-message-center-rss</id><title>Windows message center - Recent announcements</title><updated>2022-12-19T01:45:34Z</updated><author><name>direek</name></author><author><name>Microsoft</name></author><link href="https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center" type="text/html" /><link href="https://yumetodo.github.io/unofficial-windows-message-center-rss/feed/atom10.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2985</id><title>New details on IE11 desktop application permanent disablement scheduled for February 14, 2023</title><updated>2022-12-16T16:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The out-of-support Internet Explorer 11 (IE11) desktop application is scheduled to be permanently disabled on&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://aka.ms/IEModeFAQ" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;certain versions of Windows 10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;devices on February 14, 2023, through a Microsoft Edge update, not a Windows update as previously communicated. All remaining devices that have not already been redirected from IE11 to Microsoft Edge are scheduled to be redirected with the Microsoft Edge update scheduled for February 14, 2023. The change to use Microsoft Edge update to disable IE is intended to provide a better user experience and help organizations transition their last remaining IE11 users to Microsoft Edge. As a reminder, IE11 has been out of support since June 15, 2022.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Organizations that have already transitioned from IE11 to Microsoft Edge with IE mode will not be impacted when the IE11 desktop application is scheduled to be permanently disabled on February 14, 2023. Note: If you would like to remove the IE visual references such as on the taskbar or Start Menu, you will need to use the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://aka.ms/Disable_IE_Policy" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Disable IE policy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;before February 14, 2023. If your organization still has dependencies on IE11, you must take steps now to complete your transition before February 14, 2023, or risk business disruption at scale when users lose access to IE11-dependent applications.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;IE11 visual references, such as the IE11 icons on the Start Menu and taskbar, will be removed by the June 2023 Windows monthly security update release (‘B’ release) scheduled for June 13, 2023. They will also be removed by the non-security preview release on certain Windows 10 versions scheduled for May 23, 2023.&amp;nbsp;For more information, please &lt;a href="https://aka.ms/IEModeFAQ" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;read&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;the FAQ.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://aka.ms/IEModeFAQ" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2984</id><title>Feature and expedited update management generally available in Intune</title><updated>2022-12-16T16:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The general availability of feature and expedited quality updates in Microsoft Intune brings with it new features that allow you to easily manage updates and accompanying reports.&amp;nbsp;These features use the Windows Update for Business deployment service to provide greater control over specifying updates to devices. Additional rich reporting provides detailed status and error state for each device in the policy. Learn about these capabilities and best practices for managing Windows updates in Intune in the new blog post &lt;a href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/feature-and-expedited-updates-in-intune-generally-available/ba-p/3697614" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;Generally available: feature and expedited updates in Intune&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/feature-and-expedited-updates-in-intune-generally-available/ba-p/3697614" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2973</id><title>Microsoft Edge version 109 will be the last version to support Windows 7 ESU and Windows 8</title><updated>2022-12-14T22:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The upcoming Microsoft Edge version 109 - scheduled for release on the week of January 12th, 2023 - will be the last version to support Windows 7 Extended Security Update (ESU) and Windows 8/8.1. This also applies to WebView2 Runtime version 109, which is releasing this same week and is also ending support on these Windows versions.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;This aligns with the end of support for Windows 7 ESU and Windows 8/8.1 on January 10th, 2023.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Microsoft Edge and WebView2 versions 109 and earlier will continue to work on Windows 7 and Windows 8/8.1, but will not receive new features or future security updates. To get new versions of Microsoft Edge or the WebView2 Runtime with up-to-date functionality and security, please upgrade to Windows 10 or later. For additional details on support for various operating systems, see &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://blogs.windows.com/msedgedev/2022/12/09/microsoft-edge-and-webview2-ending-support-for-windows-7-and-windows-8-8-1/" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Microsoft Edge and WebView2 ending support for Windows 7 and Windows 8/8.1&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://blogs.windows.com/msedgedev/2022/12/09/microsoft-edge-and-webview2-ending-support-for-windows-7-and-windows-8-8-1/" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2975</id><title>Recommendations for scenarios requiring Transport Layer Security (TLS) 1.1 and below</title><updated>2022-12-14T22:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Beginning September 2022, Microsoft disabled Transport Layer Security (TLS) 1.0 and 1.1 by default for Internet Explorer and EdgeHTML. Please note, Microsoft has not deprecated these versions of TLS - they are only disabled by default.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Although organizations and home users have the option to turn it back on through Group Policy or Internet Options, we do not recommend doing so. TLS 1.1 and below are vulnerable to various attacks, and are no longer considered secure. If an application fails due to the new TLS default, please check if a newer version of the application is available before enabling TLS 1.1 and 1.0. If one is not available, consider asking the app developer to make configuration changes in the app to remove dependency on these versions of TLS.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;TLS fallback is also an option to help keep devices secure by enabling applications to fall back to TLS1.0 and below if connections are made using a TLS version with secure protocols (TLS 1.2 and above). To enable TLS fallback, changes are required on the Windows registry. For instructions on these changes, see our updated documentation at &lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/topic/kb5017811-manage-transport-layer-security-tls-1-0-and-1-1-after-default-behavior-change-on-september-20-2022-e95b1b47-9c7c-4d64-9baf-610604a64c3e" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" target="_blank"&gt;KB5017811 - Manage Transport Layer Security (TLS) 1.0 and 1.1 after default behavior change in September 20, 2022&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/topic/kb5017811-manage-transport-layer-security-tls-1-0-and-1-1-after-default-behavior-change-on-september-20-2022-e95b1b47-9c7c-4d64-9baf-610604a64c3e" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2979</id><title>December 2022 security update available for all supported versions of Windows</title><updated>2022-12-13T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The December 2022 security update release, referred to as our "B" release, is now available for Windows 11 and all supported versions of Windows 10. We recommend that you install these updates promptly. For more information about the contents of this update, see the release notes, which are easily accessible from the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5021255" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5021233"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;update history pages. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see our&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-quality-updates-primer/ba-p/2569385" data-linktype="external" target="_blank"&gt;Windows quality updates primer&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on Twitter&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://twitter.com/windowsupdate" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IMPORTANT: &lt;/strong&gt;There will be no preview, non-security “C” releases for Windows 10 or Windows 11 during the month of December. The "C" releases normally target the third week of the month.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11 update:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Short on time? Watch our short monthly release notes video for a summary of &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://youtu.be/C59FZ1NM5rQ" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;this month’s&amp;nbsp;Windows 11 update&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5021255" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2981</id><title>Windows 10, version 21H1 has reached end of servicing</title><updated>2022-12-13T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;As of December 13, 2022,&amp;nbsp;all editions&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;of&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/lifecycle/announcements/windows-10-21h1-end-of-servicing"&gt;Windows 10, version 21H1&lt;/a&gt; have reached end of servicing. The &lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2979" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;December 2022 security update&lt;/a&gt;, released on December 13, is the last update available for this version. Devices running this version will no longer receive monthly security and preview updates containing protections from the latest security threats.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;To help keep you protected and productive, Windows Update will automatically initiate a feature update to &lt;a href="https://aka.ms/W11/how-to-get-22H2" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 10, version 22H2&lt;/a&gt; for consumer devices and non-managed business devices when they are nearing or have reached end of servicing. This allows your device to continue to receive monthly updates that are critical to security and ecosystem health. For this automatic installation, you can &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/get-updates-when-you-re-away-from-your-pc-with-active-hours-in-windows-09b5376c-7647-4361-1423-c29aa692a8c4#WindowsVersion=Windows_10" data-linktype="external"&gt;choose a convenient time&lt;/a&gt; for your device to restart and complete the update.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As always, we recommend that you update&amp;nbsp;your&amp;nbsp;devices to the latest version of&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://aka.ms/W10/how-to-get-22H2" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt;, or upgrade eligible devices to&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://aka.ms/W11/how-to-get-22H2" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt;. For detailed information, see the entry for &lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="/en-us/lifecycle/announcements/windows-10-21h1-end-of-servicing"&gt;Windows 10, version 21H1 end of servicing&lt;/a&gt; at the learn.microsoft.com lifecycle page, and &lt;a href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/reminder-end-of-servicing-for-windows-10-version-21h1/ba-p/3671327" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Reminder: End of servicing for Windows 10, version 21H1&lt;/a&gt; at Windows IT Pro blog. For information about servicing timelines and lifecycle, see&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/release-information"&gt;Windows 10 release information&lt;/a&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/windows11-release-information" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Windows 11 release information&lt;/a&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/lifecycle/faq/windows"&gt;Lifecycle FAQ - Windows&lt;/a&gt;, and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/?terms=windows" target="_blank"&gt;Microsoft Lifecycle Policy search tool&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/reminder-end-of-servicing-for-windows-10-version-21h1/ba-p/3671327" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2980</id><title>Try an improved Quick Assist experience</title><updated>2022-12-13T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Install the Windows 11 or Windows 10 December 2022 quality update for a seamless and improved Quick Assist experience. Whether you use the Microsoft Store app or the original app, you can help your clients, colleagues, family, and friends with their PC problems over a remote connection. This update ensures the best experience no matter the source of your app and introduces a new requirement: Edge WebView2. Learn about the details and resources that you need to start using the improved Quick Assist in our new IT Pro blog post&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://aka.ms/QuickAssistImprovements" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Try an improved Quick Assist experience&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://aka.ms/QuickAssistImprovements" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2977</id><title>Reminder: Windows 8.1 support ends on January 10, 2023</title><updated>2022-12-12T22:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;As previously announced, Windows 8.1 will reach the end of support on January 10, 2023. Technical assistance and software updates will no longer be provided beyond this date. If you have devices running Windows 8.1, we recommend upgrading them to a more current, in-service, and supported Windows release. If a device does not meet the technical requirements to run a more current release of Windows, we recommend that you replace the device with one that supports Windows 11. Microsoft will not be offering an Extended Security Update (ESU) program for Windows 8.1. Continuing to use Windows 8.1 after January 10, 2023, might increase an organization’s exposure to security risks or impact its ability to meet compliance obligations.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Review the details and answers to questions at the Microsoft Support entry&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/windows-8-1-support-will-end-on-january-10-2023-3cfd4cde-f611-496a-8057-923fba401e93"&gt;Windows 8.1 support will end on January 10, 2023&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/windows-8-1-support-will-end-on-january-10-2023-3cfd4cde-f611-496a-8057-923fba401e93" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2958</id><title>New features coming to Windows 11 widgets</title><updated>2022-12-12T22:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Windows 11 continues to improve widgets experiences with additions to widget viewing options, badging, and layout.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;To get this updated feature, you should &lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/how-to-update-the-windows-web-experience-pack-in-the-microsoft-store-a16c9bf1-f042-4dc9-a523-740cca1e1e60" data-linktype="external" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;update the Windows Web Experience Pack from the Microsoft Store&lt;/a&gt;. This occurs automatically for most devices.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Please note, if you have installed the latest quality updates for Windows 11, versions 21H2 or 22H2, but still don’t see all the new widgets features, it might be because some will roll out over several weeks, and might not be available to everyone at once. Learn more about the newest widgets experiences in &lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/stay-up-to-date-with-widgets-7ba79aaa-dac6-4687-b460-ad16a06be6e4"&gt;Stay up to date with widgets&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/stay-up-to-date-with-widgets-7ba79aaa-dac6-4687-b460-ad16a06be6e4" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2976</id><title>Reminder: January 2023 changes for the Windows Diagnostic data processor configuration</title><updated>2022-12-09T22:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Beginning with the January 2023 release preview cumulative update for Windows 10, versions 20H2, 21H2 and 22H2, and Windows 11, versions 21H2 and 22H2, we’re introducing a significant change for enterprise Windows devices that have diagnostic data turned on. In support of our plan to&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://blogs.microsoft.com/eupolicy/2021/05/06/eu-data-boundary/" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;store and process EU Data for European enterprise customers in the EU&lt;/a&gt;, we will stop using policies, such as the “Allow commercial data pipeline” policy, to configure data processor options and introduce an organization-wide configuration based on Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) to determine Microsoft’s role in the data processing.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;For information on these changes and details on how to enable the Windows diagnostic data processor configuration option, see&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/windows/privacy/changes-to-windows-diagnostic-data-collection#significant-changes-coming-to-the-windows-diagnostic-data-processor-configuration" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Significant changes coming to the Windows diagnostic data processor configuration&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/privacy/changes-to-windows-diagnostic-data-collection#significant-changes-coming-to-the-windows-diagnostic-data-processor-configuration" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2974</id><title>Advance your security posture with Microsoft Intune from chip to cloud</title><updated>2022-12-09T22:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;&lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/training/modules/m365-advance-organization-security-posture/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Advance your security posture with Microsoft Intune from chip to cloud&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;is now available on MS Learn to IT admins, security engineers, and security operations analysts for up to 1200 experience points. This new&amp;nbsp;learning module encourages a proactive approach to Windows servicing by providing step-by-step guidance with screenshots and assessments. After completing this module, you&amp;nbsp;will better understand Microsoft Intune as one of the modern device management tools, learn how to enable Zero Trust from chip to cloud, and advance and measure your&amp;nbsp;organization's security posture. Visit our IT Pro Blog summary at &lt;a data-linktype="external" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://aka.ms/MSLearnSecurityPosture"&gt;New on Microsoft Learn: Advance your security posture from chip to cloud&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://aka.ms/MSLearnSecurityPosture" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2972</id><title>Update Compliance is no longer available. Use Windows Update for Business reports. </title><updated>2022-12-08T22:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Update Compliance is no longer an active solution, giving way to Windows Update for Business reports instead. We no longer allow new enrollments into Update Compliance nor the option to regenerate or generate a new CommercialID. To facilitate transition, current users can continue to use Update Compliance until March 31, 2023.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Windows Update for Business reports is built based on the feedback of many Update Compliance users and all who have participated in the preview. With a revamped user experience, richer update deployment data and better alert monitoring, we are confident that these new reports will help you better manage your update compliance goals. Learn how to transition to the new and improved solution at &lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/now-generally-available-windows-update-for-business-reports/ba-p/3677018" data-linktype="external"&gt;Now generally available: Windows Update for Business reports&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/now-generally-available-windows-update-for-business-reports/ba-p/3677018" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2971</id><title>Reminder: Windows Distributed Component Object Model (DCOM) hardening changes as of November 8, 2022</title><updated>2022-12-07T21:30:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;As previously announced, security requirements have increased for Windows devices that use the Distributed Component Object Model (DCOM) or Remote Procedure Call (RPC) server technologies. DCOM clients attempting to establish connections to DCOM servers which have applied updates released June 14, 2022, or later, must either support an authentication level of RPC_C_AUTHN_LEVEL_PKT_INTEGRITY and higher.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Updates released November 8, 2022, and later automatically raise authentication level for requests from DCOM clients to RPC_C_AUTHN_LEVEL_PKT_INTEGRITY. Most Windows DCOM client applications will automatically work with the server side DCOM hardening change without modification to the DCOM client applications.&amp;nbsp;As a reminder, it's possible to temporarily disable this authentication level enforcement by creating a registry key in the DCOM server. However, this will no longer be possible beginning March 14, 2023. We strongly recommend that IT administrators conduct testing by enabling hardening changes before this date to confirm normal operations.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Our documentation has been updated with a new summary, as well as expanded details on the installation of the registry key implementation. See &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/topic/kb5004442-manage-changes-for-windows-dcom-server-security-feature-bypass-cve-2021-26414-f1400b52-c141-43d2-941e-37ed901c769c" target="_blank"&gt;KB5004442—Manage changes for Windows DCOM Server Security Feature Bypass (CVE-2021-26414)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/topic/kb5004442-manage-changes-for-windows-dcom-server-security-feature-bypass-cve-2021-26414-f1400b52-c141-43d2-941e-37ed901c769c" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2894</id><title>We welcome your feedback</title><updated>2022-12-07T21:30:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Please take a moment and participate in this &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://aka.ms/WRH-survey" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;quick&amp;nbsp;survey&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;we’ve prepared as part of our continued effort to evolve the design and utility of the Windows release health hub.&amp;nbsp;We greatly appreciate your feedback&amp;nbsp;so we can focus on what matters most!&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/"&gt;Windows release health&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;offers you official information on Windows releases and servicing milestones, known issues and safeguards, and helpful resources.&amp;nbsp;This survey should only take about five minutes of your time to complete and will be available to fill out for a few extra days.&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://aka.ms/WRH-survey" target="_blank"&gt;Get started here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://aka.ms/WRH-survey" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2968</id><title>November 2022 Windows non-security preview release available for all supported versions for Windows</title><updated>2022-11-29T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The November 2022 non-security preview release is now available for all supported versions of Windows. Information about the contents of this update is available from the release notes, which are accessible from &lt;a data-linktype="external" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5020044"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5020030" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt; history pages. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see our &lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-quality-updates-primer/ba-p/2569385"&gt;Windows quality updates primer&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on Twitter &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/windowsupdate" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;&lt;u&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IMPORTANT: &lt;/strong&gt;There will be no preview, non-security releases for Windows 10 or Windows 11 during the month of December. Preview releases normally target the third week of the month. There will be a December security update release, as usual.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11, version 22H2 update:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5020044" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2965</id><title>Fiji 2022 time zone update now available</title><updated>2022-11-22T19:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;On October 27, 2022, the Fijian government announced that Daylight Saving Time (DST) in the Republic of Fiji will not be observed in 2022. This DST change is included in the November 2022 non-security preview updates for the latest versions of Windows 10, Windows 11, and Windows Server 2022. For organizations with devices in the Republic of Fiji on other Windows versions, a manual workaround is available between November 13, 2022 and December 13, 2022. Please visit &lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/daylight-saving-time-time-zone/fiji-2022-time-zone-update-now-available/ba-p/3677879" data-linktype="external"&gt;Fiji 2022 time zone update now available&lt;/a&gt; for further details around specific Windows versions and temporary solution guidance.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/daylight-saving-time-time-zone/fiji-2022-time-zone-update-now-available/ba-p/3677879" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2962</id><title>Organizational messages for Windows 11 (public preview)</title><updated>2022-11-17T22:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Organizations can now communicate with employees natively on their Windows 11 devices. Messages can be delivered just above the taskbar, in the Windows notifications area, or in the Get Started app. Keep employees informed of important information. Integrate onboarding information for employees on new device. &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/organizational-messages-for-windows-11-now-in-public-preview/ba-p/3678228"&gt;Explore the messaging capabilities&lt;/a&gt; available in the public preview, then learn how to get started configuring messages in Microsoft Intune.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/organizational-messages-for-windows-11-now-in-public-preview/ba-p/3678228" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2960</id><title> Migrate from .NET Core 3.1 to .NET 7 or other supported version by December 13, 2022</title><updated>2022-11-17T00:30:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;.NET Core 3.1 (LTS) will reach end of support on December 13, 2022. If you’re using .NET Core 3.1 (LTS), please migrate to .NET 6 (LTS) or .NET 7 as soon as possible. &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/announcing-dotnet-7/" data-linktype="external"&gt;.NET 7 is Available Today&lt;/a&gt; Read more at &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/net-core-3-1-will-reach-end-of-support-on-december-13-2022/" data-linktype="external"&gt;.NET Core 3.1 will reach End of Support on December 13, 2022&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/net-core-3-1-will-reach-end-of-support-on-december-13-2022/" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2959</id><title>Now generally available: Windows Update for Business reports</title><updated>2022-11-15T23:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Windows Update for Business reports is now generally available. This evolution of Update Compliance combines organizational and device-level reporting with actionable data and insights. The new blog post provides guidance on how to enroll in or transition to Windows Update for Business reports from Update Compliance by January 15, 2023. Take an inside look at revamped reporting capabilities for quality and feature updates and follow guidance to transition as soon as possible. Read &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://aka.ms/WUfBreportsGA" data-linktype="external" target="_blank"&gt;Now generally available: Windows Update for Business reports&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://aka.ms/WUfBreportsGA" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2957</id><title>November 2022 Windows non-security preview release is available for some versions of Windows</title><updated>2022-11-15T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The November 2022 non-security preview release is now available for Windows 11, version 21H2, and all supported versions of Windows 10. The preview update for Windows 11, version 22H2, will be available in the near term. Information about the contents of this update is available from the release notes, which are accessible from &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5019157"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5020030"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt; history pages. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see our &lt;a href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-quality-updates-primer/ba-p/2569385" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows quality updates primer&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on Twitter &lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://twitter.com/windowsupdate" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IMPORTANT: &lt;/strong&gt;There will be no preview, non-security releases for Windows 10 or Windows 11 during the month of December. Preview releases normally target the third week of the month. There will be a December security update release, as usual.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11, version 21H2 update:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5019157" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2949</id><title>Reminder: Windows 8.1 support ends on January 10, 2023</title><updated>2022-11-10T22:30:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;As a reminder, Windows 8.1 will reach the end of support on January 10, 2023, at which point technical assistance and software updates will no longer be provided. If you have devices running Windows 8.1, we recommend upgrading them to a more current, in-service, and supported Windows release. If a device does not meet the technical requirements to run a more current release of Windows, we recommend that you replace the device with one that supports Windows 11. Microsoft will not be offering an Extended Security Update (ESU) program for Windows 8.1. Continuing to use Windows 8.1 after January 10, 2023, might increase an organization’s exposure to security risks or impact its ability to meet compliance obligations.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Review the details and answers to questions at the Microsoft Support entry &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/windows-8-1-support-will-end-on-january-10-2023-3cfd4cde-f611-496a-8057-923fba401e93"&gt;Windows 8.1 support will end on January 10, 2023&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/windows-8-1-support-will-end-on-january-10-2023-3cfd4cde-f611-496a-8057-923fba401e93" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2948</id><title>Take action: November 2022 security update available for all supported versions of Windows</title><updated>2022-11-08T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The November 2022 security update release, referred to as our "B" release, is now available for Windows 11 and all supported versions of Windows 10. We recommend that you install these updates promptly. For more information about the contents of this update, see the release notes, which are easily accessible from the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5018427"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5019959" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;update history pages. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see our&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-quality-updates-primer/ba-p/2569385" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows quality updates primer&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on Twitter&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/windowsupdate" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IMPORTANT: &lt;/strong&gt;There will be no preview, non-security “C” releases for Windows 10 or Windows 11 during the month of December. The "C" releases normally target the third week of the month. There will be a December "B" security update release, as usual.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11 update:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Short on time? Watch our short monthly release notes video for a summary of &lt;a href="https://youtu.be/srJjdxw6Gi0" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;this month’s&amp;nbsp;Windows 11 update&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5019980" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2951</id><title>Reminder: End of servicing for Windows 10, version 21H1, on December 13, 2022</title><updated>2022-11-08T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;On December 13, 2022, all editions of Windows 10, version 21H1 will reach end of servicing. The upcoming December 2022 security update, to be released on December 13, 2022, will be the last update available for this version. After that date, devices running this version will no longer receive monthly security and quality updates containing protection from the latest security threats.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;To help keep you protected and productive, Windows Update will automatically initiate a feature update for Windows 10 consumer devices and non-managed business devices that are at, or within several months of reaching end of servicing. This keeps your device supported and receiving monthly updates that are critical to security and ecosystem health. For these devices, you will be able to choose a convenient time for your device to restart and complete the update.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;For detailed information, see the entry for &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/lifecycle/announcements/windows-10-21h1-end-of-servicing" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Windows 10, version 21H1 end of servicing&lt;/a&gt; at learn.microsoft.com lifecycle page, and &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/reminder-end-of-servicing-for-windows-10-version-21h1/ba-p/3671327" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Reminder: End of servicing for Windows 10, version 21H1&lt;/a&gt; at Windows IT Pro blog.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As always, we recommend that you update&amp;nbsp;your&amp;nbsp;devices to the latest version of&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://blogs.windows.com/windowsexperience/2021/11/16/how-to-get-the-windows-10-november-2021-update/" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt;, or upgrade eligible devices to&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" href="https://blogs.windows.com/windowsexperience/2021/10/04/how-to-get-windows-11/"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt;. For information about servicing timelines and lifecycle, see&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/release-information" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 10 release information&lt;/a&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/windows11-release-information"&gt;Windows 11 release information&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="/en-us/lifecycle/faq/windows"&gt;Lifecycle FAQ - Windows&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/?terms=windows" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Microsoft Lifecycle Policy search tool&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/reminder-end-of-servicing-for-windows-10-version-21h1/ba-p/3671327" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2943</id><title>Try Windows Update for Business with Microsoft Graph </title><updated>2022-10-31T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Microsoft Graph allows IT admins to flexibly manage device workflows in the Windows Update for Business deployment service. With this service, you can manage devices and view, deploy, and expedite updates in a manner that best achieves your business goals. Get visual and step-by-step instructions on how exactly to use Graph Explorer or PowerShell SDK, and even how to build your own custom application from within Teams. Learn more about these experiences and your readiness to leverage them for your organization in &lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/try-windows-update-for-business-with-microsoft-graph/ba-p/3663728"&gt;Try Windows Update for Business with Microsoft Graph&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/try-windows-update-for-business-with-microsoft-graph/ba-p/3663728" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2944</id><title>Deliver organizational messages with Windows 11 and Microsoft Intune </title><updated>2022-10-31T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;IT admins can soon configure native Windows 11 onboarding and information update messages for improved user engagement. The public preview of organizational messages with Microsoft Intune and Windows 11, version 22H2 is coming in November. This includes a variety of templated messages with your organization’s logo delivered through the user’s taskbar, Notification center, and Get Started app.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;For additional capabilities and Microsoft Intune instructions, please read &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/deliver-organizational-messages-with-windows-11-and-microsoft/ba-p/3651011" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Deliver organizational messages with Windows 11 and Microsoft Intune&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/deliver-organizational-messages-with-windows-11-and-microsoft/ba-p/3651011" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2942</id><title>Take action: Understand domain join hardening changes and avoid potential operational issues</title><updated>2022-10-28T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Windows updates released on and after &lt;a target="_blank" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/status-windows-11-22h2#2940msgdesc" data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;October 11, 2022&lt;/a&gt;, contain additional protections introduced by &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2022-38042" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;CVE-2022-38042&lt;/a&gt;. These protections intentionally prevent domain join operations from reusing an existing computer account in the target domain in some scenarios. See &lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5020276" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;KB5020276 - Netjoin: Domain join hardening changes&lt;/a&gt; to learn more about the new behavior, including additional security checks and the steps to avoid operational issues.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href="/en-us/windows/release-health/status-windows-11-22h2#2940msgdesc" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Domain join operations might intentionally fail&lt;/a&gt; with error "0xaac (2732): NERR_AccountReuseBlockedByPolicy" and text "An account with the same name exists in Active Directory. Re-using the account was blocked by security policy." If you encounter this message, see&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5020276" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;KB5020276&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;to understand how to address the error. We have added insights to this KB, and are evaluating whether optimizations can be made in a future Windows update.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5020276" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2941</id><title>Take action: Out-of-band update to address issues with OneDrive after installing the October 2022 updates</title><updated>2022-10-28T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Microsoft is releasing Out-of-band updates today, October 28, 2022, for some versions of Windows. This update addresses a known issue in which &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/resolved-issues-windows-10-22h2#2939msgdesc" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Microsoft OneDrive app might unexpectedly close&lt;/a&gt;. If you are not encountering the issue described in &lt;a href="/en-us/windows/release-health/resolved-issues-windows-10-22h2#2939msgdesc" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Microsoft OneDrive app might unexpectedly close&lt;/a&gt;, you do not need to install these out-of-band updates.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;All versions are available only on the Microsoft Update Catalog and will not be offered through Windows Update. For instructions, see the release notes for your OS listed below. &lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; Organizations can manually import these updates into Windows Server Update Services (WSUS) and Microsoft Endpoint Configuration Manager.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Cumulative updates:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; You do not need to apply any previous update before installing these cumulative updates.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/resolved-issues-windows-10-22h2#2939msgdesc" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2938</id><title>Reminder: Important changes coming January 2023 for the Windows Diagnostic data processor configuration</title><updated>2022-10-28T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;As previously announced, we’re introducing a significant change for enterprise Windows devices that have diagnostic data turned on. In support of our plan to &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://blogs.microsoft.com/eupolicy/2021/05/06/eu-data-boundary/" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;store and process EU Data for European enterprise customers in the EU&lt;/a&gt;, we will stop using policies, such as the “Allow commercial data pipeline” policy, to configure data processor options and introduce an organization-wide configuration based on Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) to determine Microsoft’s role in the data processing.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The change will roll out with the January 2023 release preview cumulative update for Windows 10, versions 20H2, 21H2 and 22H2, and Windows 11, versions 21H2 and 22H2.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;For information on these changes and details on how to enable the Windows diagnostic data processor configuration option, see &lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/windows/privacy/changes-to-windows-diagnostic-data-collection#significant-changes-coming-to-the-windows-diagnostic-data-processor-configuration" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Significant changes coming to the Windows diagnostic data processor configuration&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/privacy/changes-to-windows-diagnostic-data-collection#significant-changes-coming-to-the-windows-diagnostic-data-processor-configuration" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2925</id><title>The Internet Explorer 11 desktop app will be permanently disabled as part of February 2023 updates</title><updated>2022-10-27T23:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;As previously announced, the Internet Explorer 11 (IE11) desktop app has been retired as of June 15, 2022. IE11 retirement is occurring through two phases: (1) a redirection phase, currently in progress with devices progressively redirected from IE11 to Microsoft Edge, and (2) an upcoming Windows Update phase that includes IE11 being permanently disabled. This permanent disablement of IE11 is scheduled to begin with the January non-security preview release (also known as 1C) scheduled for January 17, 2023, and the February security release (also known as 2B) scheduled for February 14, 2023. Disablement will be included in all subsequent Windows Updates after these releases.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;For organizations which have not yet transitioned away from IE11, continued reliance on IE11 when the Windows Update becomes available may cause business disruption. For organizations that are ready to remove IE11, it is strongly recommended to use the Disable IE policy to remove IE11 while controlling the timing of permanent IE11 disablement before the Windows Update. Visit Techcommunity to learn how to &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://aka.ms/Disable_IE_Policy" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Control IE retirement on your own schedule with the Disable IE Policy&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://aka.ms/IEModeFAQ" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;read our FAQ&lt;/a&gt; to help answer questions.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://aka.ms/Disable_IE_Policy" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2926</id><title>October 2022 Windows non-security preview release available for all supported versions of Windows</title><updated>2022-10-25T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The October 2022 non-security preview release is now available for all supported versions of Windows. Information about the contents of this update is available from the release notes, which are accessible from &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5018496" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5017380" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt; history pages. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see our &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-quality-updates-primer/ba-p/2569385" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows quality updates primer&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on Twitter &lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://twitter.com/windowsupdate"&gt;&lt;u&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11, version 22H2 update:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5018496" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2936</id><title>Public preview of Unified Update Platform on premises </title><updated>2022-10-24T20:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The public preview of the Unified Update Platform is now available&amp;nbsp;to help you manage updates on premises. This improvement involves a seamless integration with Configuration Manager and Windows Server Updates Services (WSUS).&amp;nbsp;See how UUP simplifies quality and feature update deployment, including upgrading your devices from Windows 10 to Windows 11. In preparation for complete transition to UUP servicing in early 2023, follow enclosed instructions to enroll in &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/public-preview-of-unified-update-platform-on-premises/ba-p/3659708" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Public&amp;nbsp;preview of Unified Update Platform on premises&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/public-preview-of-unified-update-platform-on-premises/ba-p/3659708" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2937</id><title>Expedite Windows quality updates: Troubleshooting tips </title><updated>2022-10-24T20:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Bookmark these troubleshooting tips to take full advantage of the existing Intune capability to expedite&amp;nbsp;Windows quality updates. Those enrolled in Windows Update for Business deployment service can fast-track installation of security updates without modifying&amp;nbsp;the existing configurations of Windows update rings. To do so, the article &lt;a href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/get-the-most-out-of-expedited-windows-quality-updates/ba-p/3659741" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" target="_blank"&gt;Expedite&amp;nbsp;Windows quality updates: Troubleshooting tips&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;provides&amp;nbsp;guidance on&amp;nbsp;checking the prerequisites, monitoring&amp;nbsp;and resolving common issues, and best practices. Follow the step-by-step guides, screen shots, and additional&amp;nbsp;reference links for your one-stop self-help to expedite&amp;nbsp;Windows quality updates.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/get-the-most-out-of-expedited-windows-quality-updates/ba-p/3659741" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2932</id><title>DCOM authentication hardening: What you need to know </title><updated>2022-10-19T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;A new blog article tells a comprehensive story of Distributed Component Object Model (DCOM) authentication hardening. Historical and contextual details inform the timeline of the phased rollout, ultimately leading to default enablement and security of servers and client devices. Review the steps to keep your organization protected with the latest Windows updates, enable or test DCOM authentication hardening, and monitor for compatibility. Follow the troubleshooting guidance for several common scenarios for Windows devices right from &lt;a href="https://aka.ms/DCOMhardening" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;DCOM authentication hardening: What you need to know&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://aka.ms/DCOMhardening" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2933</id><title>Announcing Windows Update for Business reports</title><updated>2022-10-19T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Update Compliance&amp;nbsp;is being rebranded&amp;nbsp;to Windows Update for Business reports, which was&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="external" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/public-preview-of-azure-workbooks-for-update-compliance/ba-p/3601310"&gt;previously announced&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;as Azure Workbooks for Update Compliance.&amp;nbsp;With the general availability coming up in early November,&amp;nbsp;current Update Compliance users are reminded of new eligibility requirements and the steps&amp;nbsp;necessary to get ready for the upcoming improvements. See how to get ready for general availability in the new blog&amp;nbsp;post&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" href="https://aka.ms/windowsupdateforbusinessreports" target="_blank"&gt;Announcing Windows Update for Business reports&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://aka.ms/windowsupdateforbusinessreports" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2928</id><title>Making the everyday easier with new experiences available in Windows 11 </title><updated>2022-10-18T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Today we are announcing the availability of new features in Windows 11 along with some exciting new app experiences to help you be your most productive and creative. Last month, we launched &lt;a href="https://blogs.windows.com/windowsexperience/2022/09/20/available-today-the-windows-11-2022-update/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;the Windows 11 2022 Update&lt;/a&gt; in over 190 countries. At that time, we reinforced our promise to deliver new features into Windows 11 more frequently, in addition to our annual update.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Check out the new features made available today and coming in the next weeks including the &lt;strong&gt;Tabbed File Explorer, Taskbar Overflow and easy access to Task Manager, Memories on the Photos app, &lt;/strong&gt;and&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;new &lt;strong&gt;sports and entertainment apps&lt;/strong&gt;. To&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;learn more about what’s new, see &lt;a href="https://aka.ms/MakingTheEverydayEasier" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Making the everyday easier with new experiences available in Windows 11&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://aka.ms/MakingTheEverydayEasier" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2927</id><title>Windows 10, version 22H2 is now available</title><updated>2022-10-18T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The Windows 10 2022 Update – also known as Windows 10, version 22H2 – is now available. This version is a scoped release focused on quality improvements to the overall Windows experience in existing feature areas such as quality, productivity and security, and is delivered via a familiar and reliable update experience. Version 22H2 will continue the recent Windows 10 feature update trend of being delivered in an optimized way using servicing technology.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The 2022 Update is available to users with devices running Windows 10, version 20H2 or later. If you would like to install the new release, open your &lt;strong&gt;Windows Update&lt;/strong&gt; settings and select &lt;strong&gt;Check for updates&lt;/strong&gt;. If the update appears, select &lt;strong&gt;Download and install&lt;/strong&gt; to get started. For consumer and commercial users with devices running version 20H2 or later, the 2022 Update will have a fast installation experience. We recommend that organizations begin targeted deployments to validate that their apps and infrastructure work as expected with the new release.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Learn more about this feature update in&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://aka.ms/W10/how-to-get-22H2" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;How to get the Windows 10 2022 Update&lt;/a&gt;. If you are an IT administrator, check out&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://aka.ms/W10/tools-for-22H2" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;IT tools to support Windows 10, version 22H2&lt;/a&gt; for information on commercial release channels, deployment tools, and enhancements for commercial organizations.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://aka.ms/W10/how-to-get-22H2" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2931</id><title>Take action: Out-of-band update to address issues after installing the October 2022 Windows security updates</title><updated>2022-10-17T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Updated October 18, 2022&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Microsoft is releasing Out-of-band updates today, October 17, 2022, for some versions of Windows. This update addresses a known issue that might cause &lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/resolved-issues-windows-server-2022#2924msgdesc"&gt;SSL/TLS handshakes to fail&lt;/a&gt;. Windows devices used by consumers in their home or small offices are not likely to be affected by this issue. If you are not encountering the issue described in &lt;a href="/en-us/windows/release-health/resolved-issues-windows-server-2022#2924msgdesc" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;SSL/TLS handshakes to fail&lt;/a&gt;, you do not need to install these out-of-band updates.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;All versions are available only on the Microsoft Update Catalog and will not be offered through Windows Update. For instructions, see the release notes for your OS listed below. &lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; Organizations can manually import these updates into Windows Server Update Services (WSUS) and Microsoft Endpoint Configuration Manager.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Cumulative updates:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; You do not need to apply any previous update before installing these cumulative updates.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Standalone Updates:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; If you are using security only updates for these versions of Windows Server, you only need to install these standalone updates for the month of October 2022. Security only updates are not cumulative, and you will also need to install all previous Security only updates to be fully up to date. Monthly rollup updates are cumulative and include security and all quality updates. If you are normally using Monthly rollup updates, you will need to install both the standalone updates listed above to resolve this issue, and install the Monthly rollups released October 11, 2022 to receive the quality updates for October 2022.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/resolved-issues-windows-server-2022#2924msgdesc" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2930</id><title>Expediting quality updates</title><updated>2022-10-14T22:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The expedite capability in Windows Update for Business deployment service&amp;nbsp;effectively responds to zero-day vulnerabilities by fast-tracking installation of security updates. See how&amp;nbsp;IT pros in general IT services, banking, and education&amp;nbsp;quickly and easily&amp;nbsp;maintain&amp;nbsp;a secure environment with this capability, adaptable to a variety of complex contexts and business goals. Learn more about our existing and upcoming features&amp;nbsp;in&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://aka.ms/expediterealworld" data-linktype="external" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Expediting quality updates in the real world&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://aka.ms/expediterealworld" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2920</id><title>Take action: October 2022 security update available for all supported versions of Windows</title><updated>2022-10-11T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The October 2022 security update release, referred to as our "B" release, is now available for Windows 11 and all supported versions of Windows 10. We recommend that you install these updates promptly. For more information about the contents of this update, see the release notes, which are easily accessible from the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5018427" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5018410" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;update history pages. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see our&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-quality-updates-primer/ba-p/2569385"&gt;Windows quality updates primer&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on Twitter&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/windowsupdate" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11 update:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Short on time? Watch our short monthly release notes video for a summary of &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" href="https://youtu.be/JdLooZ5-cEU" target="_blank"&gt;this month’s&amp;nbsp;Windows 11 update&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5018427" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2919</id><title>Reminder: Windows 8.1 support ends on January 10, 2023</title><updated>2022-10-11T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;As a reminder, Windows 8.1 will reach the end of support on January 10, 2023, at which point technical assistance and software updates will no longer be provided. If you have devices running Windows 8.1, we recommend upgrading them to a more current, in-service, and supported Windows release. If a device does not meet the technical requirements to run a more current release of Windows, we recommend that you replace the device with one that supports Windows 11. Microsoft will not be offering an Extended Security Update (ESU) program for Windows 8.1. Continuing to use Windows 8.1 after January 10, 2023, might increase an organization’s exposure to security risks or impact its ability to meet compliance obligations.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/windows-8-1-support-will-end-on-january-10-2023-3cfd4cde-f611-496a-8057-923fba401e93" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2918</id><title>Reminder: End of servicing for Windows 10, version 21H1, on December 13, 2022</title><updated>2022-10-11T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;On December 13, 2022, all editions of Windows 10, version 21H1 will reach end of servicing. The upcoming December 2022 security update, to be released on December 13, 2022, will be the last update available for this version. After that date, devices running this version will no longer receive monthly security and quality updates containing protection from the latest security threats.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As always, we recommend that you update&amp;nbsp;your&amp;nbsp;devices to the latest version of&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://blogs.windows.com/windowsexperience/2021/11/16/how-to-get-the-windows-10-november-2021-update/" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt;, or upgrade eligible devices to&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://blogs.windows.com/windowsexperience/2021/10/04/how-to-get-windows-11/" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt;. For information about servicing timelines and lifecycle, see&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/release-information"&gt;Windows 10 release information&lt;/a&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="/en-us/windows/release-health/windows11-release-information" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Windows 11 release information&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/lifecycle/faq/windows" data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank"&gt;Lifecycle FAQ - Windows&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="/en-us/lifecycle/products/?terms=windows" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Microsoft Lifecycle Policy search tool&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/lifecycle/announcements/windows-10-21h1-end-of-servicing" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2911</id><title>The September 2022 preview release for Windows 11, version 22H2, is now available</title><updated>2022-09-30T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The September 2022 preview release for Windows 11, version 22H2 – also referred to as the Windows 11 2022 Update – is now available. This release is designed only for devices already running the Windows 11 2022 Update and adds dynamic Widgets content to your taskbar with notification badging. It also addresses issues with Microsoft Store, adjusts daylight savings time in Chile, and reduces power consumption during Sleep mode for some devices.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;For information about the contents of this update, along with instructions on how to install this update, see the release notes which are accessible from the &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5017389" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt; history pages. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see our &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-quality-updates-primer/ba-p/2569385" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows quality updates primer&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on Twitter &lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://twitter.com/windowsupdate"&gt;&lt;u&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5017389" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2912</id><title>Faster. Smaller. Windows 11, version 22H2 update fundamentals </title><updated>2022-09-28T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The latest version of Windows 11, 22H2 brings sizeable improvements to feature and quality updates. A new IT Pro Blog post presents some results of complex engineering and testing behind smaller, faster, more reliable, and simpler updates. While quite technical, this “every byte counts” story is meant for IT pros and decision makers whose organizations are the motivators and the beneficiaries of these multiple savings. Read &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://aka.ms/UpdateFoundations" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;Faster. Smaller. Windows 11, version 22H2 update fundamentals&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://aka.ms/UpdateFoundations" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2908</id><title>The Windows 11 2022 Update is now available </title><updated>2022-09-20T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://aka.ms/Windows11/2022Update" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 11 2022 Update is now available&lt;/a&gt; for eligible Windows 10 and Windows 11 devices. If you have an eligible device and are interested in experiencing the latest feature update, open Windows Update Settings and select &lt;strong&gt;Check for updates&lt;/strong&gt;. For detailed guidance on how to get the 2022 Update and our gradual rollout approach, visit the &lt;a href="https://aka.ms/W11/how-to-get-22H2" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows Experience Blog&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://aka.ms/video/W11/how-to-get-22H2"&gt;watch this video&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;If you are an IT administrator, see &lt;a href="https://aka.ms/new-in-22H2" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;What's new for IT pros in Windows 11, version 22H2&lt;/a&gt; for information on commercial release channels, deployment tools, and enhancements for commercial organizations.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://aka.ms/Windows11/2022Update" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2899</id><title>September 2022 Windows non-security preview "C" release available for all supported versions of Windows</title><updated>2022-09-20T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The September 2022 non-security preview release, referred to as our "C" release, is now available for all supported versions of Windows. Information about the contents of this update is available from the release notes, which are accessible from &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5017383" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5017380"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt; history pages. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see our &lt;a href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-quality-updates-primer/ba-p/2569385" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows quality updates primer&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on Twitter &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://twitter.com/windowsupdate" data-linktype="external"&gt;&lt;u&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5017383" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2909</id><title>Reminder: Disabling Transport Layer Security (TLS) 1.0 and 1.1 by default for Internet Explorer and EdgeHTML </title><updated>2022-09-20T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;As previously communicated, Microsoft has disabled &lt;a href="/en-us/windows-server/security/tls/transport-layer-security-protocol" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank"&gt;Transport Layer Security (TLS)&lt;/a&gt; 1.0 and 1.1 by default for Internet Explorer and&amp;nbsp;EdgeHTML starting today, September 20, 2022. This is the rendering engine for the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" href="/en-us/uwp/api/windows.ui.xaml.controls.webview?view=winrt-19041" data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;WebView control&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Please note, Microsoft is &lt;strong&gt;not &lt;/strong&gt;deprecating TLS 1.0 and TLS 1.1 support. It is being disabled by default, and organizations have the option to turn it back on through&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://admx.help/?Category=InternetExplorer&amp;amp;Policy=Microsoft.Policies.InternetExplorer::Advanced_SetWinInetProtocols" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;Group Policy&lt;/a&gt; if needed for compatibility reasons. Users have the option turn it back on for their personal devices by navigating to&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Tools&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Internet Options&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Advanced&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;in Internet Explorer.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;For more information, see &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5017811" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Manage Transport Layer Security (TLS) 1.0 and 1.1 after default behavior change in September 20, 2022&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5017811" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2880</id><title>Take action: September 2022 security update available for all supported versions of Windows </title><updated>2022-09-13T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The September 2022 security update release, referred to as our "B" release, is now available for Windows 11 and all supported versions of Windows 10. We recommend that you install these updates promptly. For more information about the contents of this update, see the release notes, which are easily accessible from the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5017328" data-linktype="external" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5017308" data-linktype="external" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;update history pages. For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;article. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see our&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-quality-updates-primer/ba-p/2569385" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows quality updates primer&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on Twitter&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://twitter.com/windowsupdate" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Improvements for the Windows 11 update:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Short on time? Watch our short monthly release notes video for a summary of this month’s&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://www.microsoft.com/videoplayer/embed/RE55RIZ" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 11 update&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5017328" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#337</id><title>Adding file types for Unified Update Platform on premises </title><updated>2022-09-08T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Two file types are required for IT admins enrolled in the private preview of Unified Update Platform (UUP) for on-premises update management. Those using Windows Server Update Services (WSUS) must add .msu&amp;nbsp;and .wim&amp;nbsp;MIME file types to support the private preview capabilities. The new blog post outlines steps you can follow to add these file types manually or using PowerShell. If your organization is not yet enrolled in this private preview, consider joining it before you start getting Windows updates in a unified format through various channels.&amp;nbsp;Learn more about the preview of UUP for on-premises update management in the&amp;nbsp;Windows IT Pro Blog, at &lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/preview-unified-update-platform-for-on-premises-update/ba-p/3579889"&gt;Preview Unified Update Platform for on-premises update management&lt;/a&gt;. For detailed information on the file type requirements for UUP, please see &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/adding-file-types-for-unified-update-platform-on-premises/ba-p/3620876"&gt;Adding file types for Unified Update Platform on premises&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/preview-unified-update-platform-for-on-premises-update/ba-p/3579889" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2891</id><title>Guidance for installing the security update for Secure Boot DBX: August 9, 2022</title><updated>2022-08-27T00:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Microsoft released&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5012170" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;KB5012170&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;on August 9, 2022,&amp;nbsp;a standalone security update that&amp;nbsp;provides support for Secure Boot Forbidden Signature Database (DBX).&amp;nbsp;Windows 8.1 and newer clients and Windows Server 2012 and newer servers must install this update regardless of whether BitLocker is enabled or supported on&amp;nbsp;these&amp;nbsp;devices.&amp;nbsp;When attempting to&amp;nbsp;install the update, you might receive error “0x800f0922”. See the known issues section in&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5012170" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;KB5012170: Security update for Secure Boot DBX: August 9, 2022.&lt;/a&gt; Your device might start up in&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank" href="/en-us/previous-versions/windows/it-pro/windows-server-2012-R2-and-2012/dn383583(v=ws.11)" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;BitLocker recovery mode&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;after the update is installed. If you encounter this situation, check the following articles for guidance:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/status-windows-11-21h2#2888msgdesc" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Some devices might start up into BitLocker Recovery&lt;/a&gt; and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/finding-your-bitlocker-recovery-key-in-windows-6b71ad27-0b89-ea08-f143-056f5ab347d6"&gt;Finding your BitLocker recovery key in Windows&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5012170" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2863</id><title>August 2022 Windows non-security preview "C" release available for all supported versions of Windows </title><updated>2022-08-26T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The August 2022 non-security preview release, referred to as our "C" release, is now available for all supported versions of Windows. Information about the contents of this update is available from the release notes, which are accessible from &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5016691" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5016688" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt; history pages. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see our &lt;a href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-quality-updates-primer/ba-p/2569385" data-linktype="external" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows quality updates primer&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on Twitter &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://twitter.com/windowsupdate" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5016691" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#250</id><title>Reminder of helpful resources for Windows 11 upgrade and experience</title><updated>2022-08-26T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Leverage three existing resources to help you plan for, test, and validate Windows 11 in your environment. The &lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://aka.ms/windows11labkit" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 11 and Office 365 Deployment Lab Kit&lt;/a&gt; contains a complete lab environment including evaluation versions of Windows 11 Enterprise, Windows Server 2022, and a collection of tools which allow you to test and conduct a proof of concept for Windows 11 deployment. The &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://aka.ms/windowsonboardingkit"&gt;Windows 11 Onboarding Kit&lt;/a&gt; provides a collection of materials that you can use to help prepare your users and ensure that they get the most out of Windows 11. Finally, review the July &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/new-guided-simulations-for-windows-11-enterprise/ba-p/3576654" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;blog post&lt;/a&gt; to experience Windows 11 improvements and productivity in an interactive and visual way.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/new-guided-simulations-for-windows-11-enterprise/ba-p/3576654" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2848</id><title> August 2022 Windows non-security preview "C" release available for Windows 11</title><updated>2022-08-25T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The August 2022 non-security preview release, referred to as our "C" release, is now available for Windows 11. The preview update for other supported versions of Windows 10 will be available in the near term. Information about the contents of this update is available from the release notes, which are accessible from &lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5016691"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt; history pages. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see our &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-quality-updates-primer/ba-p/2569385"&gt;Windows quality updates primer&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on Twitter&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://twitter.com/windowsupdate" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11 update&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5016691" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2890</id><title>August 2022 Windows non-security preview "C" release available for Windows 10, version 1809</title><updated>2022-08-23T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The August 2022 non-security preview release, referred to as our "C" release, is now available for Windows 10, version 1809. The preview update for Windows 11 and other supported versions of Windows 10 will be available in the near term. Information about the contents of this update is available from the release notes, which are accessible from the&amp;nbsp;Windows 10&amp;nbsp;update history pages. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see our&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-quality-updates-primer/ba-p/2569385" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" target="_blank"&gt;Windows quality updates primer&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on Twitter&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/windowsupdate" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5016690" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2886</id><title>Public Preview of Azure Workbooks for Update Compliance </title><updated>2022-08-17T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Azure Workbooks for Update Compliance reporting is now available! Easily monitor Windows Updates and patch compliance with this public preview, before transitioning to it as a required solution later this year. Whether you are a generalist, an IT specialist, or a builder, the Update Compliance workbook template is here to make your job easier. See the new &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/public-preview-of-azure-workbooks-for-update-compliance/ba-p/3601310" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;blog post&lt;/a&gt; to visualize the revamped user experience and Azure AD integration, as well as how to enable the public preview today.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/public-preview-of-azure-workbooks-for-update-compliance/ba-p/3601310" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2884</id><title>August 2022 Windows non-security preview "C" release is available for Windows Server 2022</title><updated>2022-08-16T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The August 2022 non-security preview release, referred to as our "C" release, is now available for Windows Server 2022. The preview update for Windows 11 and other supported versions of Windows10 will be available in the near term. Information about the contents of this update is available from the release notes, which are accessible from the &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5016693" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows Server 2022&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;update history pages. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see our&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-quality-updates-primer/ba-p/2569385"&gt;Windows quality updates primer&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on Twitter &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/windowsupdate" data-linktype="external" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5016693" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2879</id><title>Introducing Widget notifications</title><updated>2022-08-16T18:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;Last updated: 8/19/22&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Windows 11 is bringing you more live content on your taskbar. This change allows you to see live updates from other widgets such as sports, finance, and breaking news. Your taskbar should show weather most of the time, but when something important happens related to one of your other widgets you may see an announcement&amp;nbsp;from that widget on your taskbar.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;To get this updated feature, you should &lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/how-to-update-the-windows-web-experience-pack-in-the-microsoft-store-a16c9bf1-f042-4dc9-a523-740cca1e1e60"&gt;update the Windows Web Experience Pack from the Microsoft Store&lt;/a&gt;. This occurs automatically for most devices.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;These announcements are meant to be quick and glanceable, and if you don’t interact with them, the taskbar will return to showing you the weather. Explore the changes in &lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/stay-up-to-date-with-widgets-7ba79aaa-dac6-4687-b460-ad16a06be6e4" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Stay up to date with widgets&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;At this time, Widget notifications cannot be turned off. Microsoft is&amp;nbsp;constantly listening and learning, and welcomes customer feedback that helps shape Windows.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note&lt;/strong&gt;: If you have the latest version of Windows&amp;nbsp;but still don’t see all widgets features, it may be because some features are&amp;nbsp;being rolled out over several weeks and aren't&amp;nbsp;available to all customers at once.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/stay-up-to-date-with-widgets-7ba79aaa-dac6-4687-b460-ad16a06be6e4" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2881</id><title>Disabling Transport Layer Security (TLS) 1.0 and 1.1 by default for Internet Explorer and EdgeHTML</title><updated>2022-08-15T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Starting September 13, 2022, Microsoft&amp;nbsp;will disable Transport Layer Security (TLS) 1.0 and 1.1 by default for Internet Explorer and EdgeHTML, the rendering engine for the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/uwp/api/windows.ui.xaml.controls.webview?view=winrt-19041" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;WebView&amp;nbsp;control&lt;/a&gt;. If you wish to disable TLS 1.0 and TLS 1.1 before that date, you might do so by using Group Policy. The Microsoft Edge Legacy desktop application is no longer in scope for this timeframe, as it reached&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://blogs.windows.com/msedgedev/2021/03/09/microsoft-edge-legacy-end-of-support/" target="_blank"&gt;end of support&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;on March 9, 2021.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note&lt;/strong&gt;: Microsoft is not&amp;nbsp;deprecating&amp;nbsp;TLS 1.0 and TLS 1.1 support. We are disabling it by default, and your organization has the option to turn it back on through&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://admx.help/?Category=InternetExplorer&amp;amp;Policy=Microsoft.Policies.InternetExplorer::Advanced_SetWinInetProtocols" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Group&amp;nbsp;Policy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;(if needed, for compatibility reasons). Users have the option turn it back on for their personal devices by navigating to&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Tools&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Internet Options&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Advanced&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;in Internet Explorer.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;For more information, see &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://blogs.windows.com/msedgedev/2020/03/31/tls-1-0-tls-1-1-schedule-update-edge-ie11/"&gt;Plan for change: TLS 1.0 and TLS 1.1 soon to be disabled by default.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://blogs.windows.com/msedgedev/2020/03/31/tls-1-0-tls-1-1-schedule-update-edge-ie11/" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2872</id><title>Take action: August 2022 security update available for all supported versions of Windows</title><updated>2022-08-09T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The August 2022 security update release, referred to as our "B" release, is now available for Windows 11 and all supported versions of Windows 10. We recommend that you install these updates promptly. For more information about the contents of this update, see the release notes, which are easily accessible from the &lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5016629" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5016616" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt; update history pages.&amp;nbsp;For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt; article. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see our &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-quality-updates-primer/ba-p/2569385"&gt;Windows quality updates primer&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on Twitter&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://twitter.com/windowsupdate" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11 update:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Short on time? Watch our short monthly release notes video for a summary of this month’s &lt;a href="https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/videoplayer/embed/RE53z8h" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 11 update&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5016629" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2874</id><title>Reminder: Removal of temporary mitigation in Windows updates requires compliant printing and scanning devices</title><updated>2022-08-09T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Firmware on smartcard-authenticating printers and scanners must be compatible with section 3.2.1 of&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://www.ietf.org/rfc/rfc4556.txt" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;RFC 4556&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;in order to successfully authenticate with Active Directory domain controllers before installing the&amp;nbsp;August 2022 security update.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Windows Updates released on July 13, 2021 introduced protections&amp;nbsp;for&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://nam06.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmsrc.microsoft.com%2Fupdate-guide%2Fvulnerability%2FCVE-2021-33764&amp;amp;data=05%7C01%7CMabel.Gomes%40microsoft.com%7Ca864f2e83bef4d5450b908da7a2b64e1%7C72f988bf86f141af91ab2d7cd011db47%7C0%7C0%7C637956624071646464%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C3000%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=Hh8rSGcih%2BeY3jPWZeLi4nhp2H8QPt05hREctNobfsE%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;CVE-2021-33764&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;which required all devices&amp;nbsp;with a key exchange during the PKINIT Kerberos authentication, including smartcard authenticating printers, to either support:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Windows updates released between July 27, 2021, and July 26, 2022 supported temporary mitigation that allowed non-RFC compliant devices to authenticate with Active Directory.&amp;nbsp;As of&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;August 9, 2022&lt;/strong&gt;, or later, Windows update removes all temporary mitigation released to&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Windows Server 2019, Windows Server 2016, Windows Server 2012 R2, Windows Server 2012, Windows Server 2008 R2 SP1, and Windows Server 2008 SP2&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;See the complete guidance in&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/topic/kb5005408-smart-card-authentication-might-cause-print-and-scan-failures-514f0bc5-ecde-4e5e-8c5a-2a776d7fb89a"&gt;KB5005408&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/topic/kb5005408-smart-card-authentication-might-cause-print-and-scan-failures-514f0bc5-ecde-4e5e-8c5a-2a776d7fb89a" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2871</id><title>Security update for Secure Boot DBX: August 9, 2022</title><updated>2022-08-09T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The August 9th, 2022 security update makes&amp;nbsp;improvements&amp;nbsp;to Secure Boot DBX for the following supported versions of Windows:&lt;strong&gt; Windows Server 2012, Windows 8.1 and Windows Server 2012 R2, Windows 10, version 1507, Windows 10, version 1607 and Windows Server 2016, Windows 10, version 1809 and Windows Server 2019, Windows 10, version 20H2, Windows 10, version 21H1, Windows 10, version 21H2, Windows Server 2022, Windows 11, version 21H2 (original release), Azure Stack HCI, version 1809, and Azure Data Box, version 1809 (ASDB).&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;This security update addresses the vulnerability by adding the signatures of the known vulnerable UEFI modules to the DBX. For more information, see &lt;a data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5012170" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;KB5012170: Security update for Secure Boot DBX: August 9, 2022&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5012170" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2875</id><title>Safeguard holds with the Windows Update for Business deployment service</title><updated>2022-08-04T00:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Safeguard holds are one of several protection features of the Windows Update for Business deployment service. This feature is informed by partners, customers, and the latest Microsoft machine learning efforts to protect device populations not only from known issues, but also from likely issues. The new blog post offers a closeup look at what known issues and likely issues are, how the safeguard holds work behind the scenes, and how IT pros can enable and monitor safeguard holds. Learn more in &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/safeguard-holds-with-the-windows-update-for-business-deployment/ba-p/3590463" data-linktype="external"&gt;Safeguard holds with the Windows Update for Business deployment service&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/safeguard-holds-with-the-windows-update-for-business-deployment/ba-p/3590463" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2860</id><title>Reminder: Active Directory Domain Services Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability hardening changes as of April 11, 2023</title><updated>2022-07-28T17:30:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;In 2021, Microsoft addressed a security vulnerability bypass &lt;a href="https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2021-42291" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Active Directory Domain Services Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability&lt;/a&gt; This bypass allows certain users to set arbitrary values on security-sensitive attributes of specific objects stored in Active Directory (AD). To exploit this vulnerability, a user must have sufficient privileges to create a computer account, such as a user granted CreateChild permissions for computer objects. That user could create a computer account using a Lightweight Directory Access Protocol (LDAP) Add call that allows overly permissive access to the&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;securityDescriptor&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;attribute. Additionally, creators and owners can modify security-sensitive attributes after creating an account.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Enforcement of new security requirements will be enabled by default in an upcoming update no sooner than April 11, 2023. Action may be required in order to prevent outages and system interruptions. For more information, see &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/topic/kb5008383-active-directory-permissions-updates-cve-2021-42291-536d5555-ffba-4248-a60e-d6cbc849cde1" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;KB5008383: Active Directory permissions updates (CVE-2021-42291)&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/topic/kb5008383-active-directory-permissions-updates-cve-2021-42291-536d5555-ffba-4248-a60e-d6cbc849cde1" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2837</id><title>Reminder: Significant changes coming to the Windows Diagnostic data processor configuration</title><updated>2022-07-27T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;To enable efficiencies and help us implement our plan to &lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" href="https://blogs.microsoft.com/eupolicy/2021/05/06/eu-data-boundary/"&gt;store and process EU Data for European enterprise customers in the EU&lt;/a&gt;, we will be introducing a significant change for enterprise Windows devices that have diagnostic data turned on.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;We’ll stop using policies, such as the “Allow commercial data pipeline” policy, to configure the processor option. Instead, we’ll be introducing an organization-wide configuration based on Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) to determine Microsoft’s role in the data processing&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;This change is releasing to Windows devices enrolled in the &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/windows-insider/flighting#dev-channel" data-linktype="absolute-path" target="_blank"&gt;Dev Channel&lt;/a&gt; of the Windows Insider program the week of July 24, 2022. Any Windows build on or after &lt;strong&gt;25169 &lt;/strong&gt;will contain the changes. For other Windows devices (not in the Dev Channel), additional details on supported versions of Windows 11 and Windows 10 will be announced at a later date. These changes will roll out no earlier than the last quarter of the calendar year 2022.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;For information on these changes and how to enable the Windows diagnostic data processor configuration option, refer to the &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="/en-us/windows/privacy/changes-to-windows-diagnostic-data-collection#significant-changes-coming-to-the-windows-diagnostic-data-processor-configuration" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Significant changes coming to the Windows diagnostic data processor configuration&lt;/a&gt; documentation topic.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/privacy/changes-to-windows-diagnostic-data-collection#significant-changes-coming-to-the-windows-diagnostic-data-processor-configuration" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2865</id><title>July 2022 Windows non-security preview "C" release available for all supported versions of Windows</title><updated>2022-07-26T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The July 2022 non-security preview release, referred to as our "C" release, is now available for all supported versions of Windows. Information about the contents of this update is available from the release notes, which are accessible from the &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5015882"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5015878" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;update history pages. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see our&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-quality-updates-primer/ba-p/2569385" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Windows quality updates primer&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on Twitter &lt;a data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://twitter.com/windowsupdate" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;For instructions on how to install this update for your operating system, see the KB for your OS listed below:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5015878" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2870</id><title>Preview Unified Update Platform for on-premises update management </title><updated>2022-07-23T00:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Sign up for the private preview of the Unified Update Platform (UUP) for on-premises update management&amp;nbsp;for commercial organizations. UUP on premises is an integration with Windows Server Update Services (WSUS)&amp;nbsp;and Microsoft Endpoint Configuration Manager, and it&amp;nbsp;will be generally available in early 2023. This new capability simplifies Windows content management and streamlines the process for upgrading to Windows 11 for those who manage Windows devices with these update management platforms. For further background and details on how to sign up for the private preview, see &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/preview-unified-update-platform-for-on-premises-update/ba-p/3579889" data-linktype="external"&gt;Preview Unified Update Platform for on-premises update management&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/preview-unified-update-platform-for-on-premises-update/ba-p/3579889" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2859</id><title>Reminder: Removal of temporary mitigation in Windows updates will require compliant printing and scanning devices </title><updated>2022-07-21T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;As previously announced, Microsoft released hardening changes for &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2021-33764" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;CVE-2021-33764&lt;/a&gt; in Windows updates starting on July 13, 2021. When these updates are installed on a domain controller (DC), smart card (PIV) authentication might cause print and scan failures. A temporary mitigation, released in Windows Updates between July 29, 2021, and July 12, 2022, was made available for organizations that encountered this issue and couldn't bring devices into compliance as required for CVE-2021-33764.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Starting on July 21, 2022, this temporary mitigation will not be usable in security updates. The Windows July 2022 preview update will remove the temporary mitigation and will require compliant printing and scanning devices. To learn more, see&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/topic/kb5005408-smart-card-authentication-might-cause-print-and-scan-failures-514f0bc5-ecde-4e5e-8c5a-2a776d7fb89a" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;KB5005408: Smart card authentication might cause print and scan failures.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/topic/kb5005408-smart-card-authentication-might-cause-print-and-scan-failures-514f0bc5-ecde-4e5e-8c5a-2a776d7fb89a" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#320</id><title>Reminder: End of servicing for Windows Server, version 20H2 on August 9, 2022</title><updated>2022-07-21T00:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;On August 9, 2022, all editions of Windows Server, version 20H2 will reach end of servicing. The upcoming August 2022 security update, to be released on August 9, 2022, will be the last update available for this version. After that date, devices running this version will no longer receive monthly security and quality updates containing protection from the latest security threats.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;This will also be the retirement of &lt;a data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/windows-server/get-started/servicing-channels-comparison#semi-annual-channel" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows Server Semi-Annual Channel (SAC)&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/lifecycle/announcements/windows-server-20h2-retiring" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;There will be no future SAC releases of Windows Server&lt;/a&gt;. Windows Server is moving to the Long-Term Servicing Channel (LTSC) as the primary release channel.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Customers using Windows Server SAC should move to&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="/en-us/azure-stack/hci/" target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Azure Stack HCI&lt;/a&gt;. Alternatively, customers may use the Long-Term Servicing Channel of Windows Server. For more information, see&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path" href="/en-us/windows-server/get-started/windows-server-release-info" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows Server Release Information&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/lifecycle/announcements/windows-server-20h2-retiring" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2861</id><title>July 2022 Windows non-security preview "C" release available for Windows Server 2022</title><updated>2022-07-19T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The July 2022 non-security preview release, referred to as our "C" release, is now available for Windows Server 2022. The preview update for Windows 11 and other supported versions of Windows 10 will be available in the near term. Information about the contents of this update is available from the release notes, which are accessible from the &lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5015879" target="_blank"&gt;Windows Server 2022&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;update history pages. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see our&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-quality-updates-primer/ba-p/2569385" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" target="_blank"&gt;Windows quality updates primer&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on Twitter &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://twitter.com/windowsupdate" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5015879" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2858</id><title>Hardening changes coming 07/2022: Smart card authentication might cause print and scan failures</title><updated>2022-07-13T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;On July 13, 2021, Microsoft released hardening changes for &lt;a href="https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2021-33764" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows Key Distribution Center Information Disclosure Vulnerability&lt;/a&gt;, CVE-2021-33764. With these changes, smart card (PIV) authentication might cause print and scan failures when you install updates released on July 13, 2021, or later versions on a domain controller (DC). The affected devices are smart card authenticating printers, scanners, and multifunction devices that don’t support either Diffie-Hellman (DH) for key exchange during PKINIT Kerberos authentication or don’t advertise support for des-ede3-cbc ("triple DES”) during the Kerberos &lt;strong&gt;AS&lt;/strong&gt; request.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;A temporary mitigation, released in Windows Updates between July 29, 2021, and July 12, 2022, was made available for organizations that encountered this issue and couldn't bring devices into compliance as required for CVE-2021-33764. However, starting in July 2022, this temporary mitigation will not be usable in security updates. The Windows July 2022 preview update will remove the temporary mitigation and will require compliant printing and scanning devices.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As of &lt;strong&gt;July 19, 2022&lt;/strong&gt;, there will be no further fallback option in later updates, and all non-compliant devices must be identified using the &lt;strong&gt;audit events starting in January 2022 &lt;/strong&gt;and updated or replaced by the mitigation removal&lt;strong&gt;. &lt;/strong&gt;To learn more, see &lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/topic/kb5005408-smart-card-authentication-might-cause-print-and-scan-failures-514f0bc5-ecde-4e5e-8c5a-2a776d7fb89a" target="_blank"&gt;KB5005408: Smart card authentication might cause print and scan failures.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/topic/kb5005408-smart-card-authentication-might-cause-print-and-scan-failures-514f0bc5-ecde-4e5e-8c5a-2a776d7fb89a" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2857</id><title>Take action: July 2022 security update available for all supported versions of Windows</title><updated>2022-07-12T17:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The July 2022 security update release, referred to as our "B" release, is now available for Windows 11 and all supported versions of Windows 10. We recommend that you install these updates promptly. For more information about the contents of this update, see the release notes, which are easily accessible from the &lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5015814" target="_blank"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5015807"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt; update history pages.&amp;nbsp;For instructions on how to install this update on your home device, check the &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a#WindowsVersion=Windows_11"&gt;Update Windows&lt;/a&gt; article. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see our &lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-quality-updates-primer/ba-p/2569385"&gt;Windows quality updates primer&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on Twitter&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://twitter.com/windowsupdate" data-linktype="external"&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11 update:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Short on time? Watch our short monthly release notes video for a summary of this month’s &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/videoplayer/embed/RE50TxI " rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 11 update&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5015814" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2854</id><title>June 2022 Windows non-security preview "C" release available for all supported versions of Windows</title><updated>2022-06-28T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The June 2022 non-security preview release, referred to as our "C" release, is now available for Windows 11&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;and all other supported versions of Windows. Information about the contents of this update is available from the release notes, which are accessible from the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5014668" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5014666" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;update history pages. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see our&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-quality-updates-primer/ba-p/2569385" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows quality updates primer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5014666" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2849</id><title>June 2022 Windows non-security preview "C" release available for Windows 11 and some versions of Windows 10</title><updated>2022-06-23T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;The June 2022 non-security preview release, referred to as our "C" release, is now available for Windows 11, Windows 10 version 1809. The preview update for other supported versions of Windows 10 will be available in the near term. Information about the contents of this update is available from the release notes, which are accessible from the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5014668" target="_blank" data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows 11&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5014669" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows 10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;update history pages. To learn more about the different types of monthly quality updates, see our&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/windows-quality-updates-primer/ba-p/2569385" data-linktype="external"&gt;Windows quality updates primer&lt;/a&gt;. To be informed about the latest updates and releases, follow us on Twitter &lt;a data-linktype="external" href="https://twitter.com/windowsupdate" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;@WindowsUpdate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Highlights for the Windows 11 update:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5014668" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2841</id><title>New! Introducing the search highlights feature</title><updated>2022-06-23T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;We’ll be introducing the search highlights feature to Windows 11 over the next several weeks. The search highlights feature presents notable and interesting moments of what’s special about each day, —like holidays, anniversaries, and other educational moments in time both globally and in your region. To see search highlights, click or tap on the search icon on your taskbar.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;For enterprise customers, search highlights will also feature the latest updates from your organization and suggest people, files, and more.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;For group configuration information,&amp;nbsp;see&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-linktype="external" href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/windows-it-pro-blog/group-configuration-search-highlights-in-windows/ba-p/3263989"&gt;Group configuration: search highlights in Windows&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://aka.ms/Windows11/SearchHighlights" rel="alternate" /></entry><entry><id>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/release-health/windows-message-center#2851</id><title>Take action: Out-of-band security update to address an issue with Azure Active Directory services on Arm-based devices</title><updated>2022-06-20T21:00:00Z</updated><content type="html">&lt;div&gt;Microsoft is releasing Out-of-band (OOB) security updates today, June 20, 2022, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;only&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; for Arm-based Windows devices. This update addresses a &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/windows/release-health/resolved-issues-windows-11-21h2#2847msgdesc"&gt;known issue&lt;/a&gt; that only affects Windows Arm-based devices and might prevent you from signing in using Azure Active Directory (AAD). Apps and services that use AAD to sign in, such as VPN connections, Microsoft Teams, and Microsoft Outlook, might also be affected.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Important&lt;/strong&gt; This issue &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;only&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; affects Windows devices that use Arm processors. No other platforms will receive this out-of-band update. This OOB update is cumulative. We recommend that you install this OOB update instead of the June 14, 2022 security update for affected devices.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;All updates listed below are available on &lt;a href="https://support.microsoft.com/windows/update-windows-3c5ae7fc-9fb6-9af1-1984-b5e0412c556a" data-linktype="external" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Windows Update&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a target="_blank" data-linktype="absolute-path" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/windows/deployment/update/waas-manage-updates-wufb"&gt;Windows Update for Business&lt;/a&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="/en-us/windows-server/administration/windows-server-update-services/get-started/windows-server-update-services-wsus" data-linktype="absolute-path"&gt;Windows Server Update Services (WSUS)&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a data-linktype="external" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://www.catalog.update.microsoft.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Microsoft Update Catalog&lt;/a&gt;. For instructions, see the release notes for your OS listed below.&lt;/div&gt;</content><link href="https://support.microsoft.com/help/5016138" rel="alternate" /></entry></feed>